const essentialQuestions = {
"level 1" : [
    {"Question": "qo'rqmoq", "RightAnswer": "afraid", "options": ["hunt","hide","finally"]},
{"Question": "rozi bo'lmoq", "RightAnswer": "agree", "options": ["afraid","hunt","hide"]},
{"Question": "jahlda", "RightAnswer": "angry", "options": ["agree","afraid","hunt"]},
{"Question": "yetib kelmoq", "RightAnswer": "arrive", "options": ["angry","agree","afraid"]},
{"Question": "hujum qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "attack", "options": ["arrive","angry","agree"]},
{"Question": "tagi osti", "RightAnswer": "bottom", "options": ["attack","arrive","angry"]},
{"Question": "aqlli", "RightAnswer": "clever", "options": ["bottom","attack","arrive"]},
{"Question": "shafqatsiz", "RightAnswer": "cruel", "options": ["clever","bottom","attack"]},
{"Question": "nihoyat", "RightAnswer": "finally", "options": ["cruel","clever","bottom"]},
{"Question": "yashirmoq", "RightAnswer": "hide", "options": ["finally","cruel","clever"]},
{"Question": "ovlamoq", "RightAnswer": "hunt", "options": ["hide","finally","cruel"]},
{"Question": "ko'p", "RightAnswer": "lot", "options": ["hunt","hide","finally"]},
{"Question": "o'rta", "RightAnswer": "middle", "options": ["lot","hunt","hide"]},
{"Question": "lahza", "RightAnswer": "moment", "options": ["middle","lot","hunt"]},
{"Question": "mamnun", "RightAnswer": "pleased", "options": ["moment","middle","lot"]},
{"Question": "va'da bermoq", "RightAnswer": "promise", "options": ["pleased","moment","middle"]},
{"Question": "javob bermoq", "RightAnswer": "reply", "options": ["promise","pleased","moment"]},
{"Question": "xavfsiz", "RightAnswer": "safe", "options": ["reply","promise","pleased"]},
{"Question": "hiyla", "RightAnswer": "trick", "options": ["safe","reply","promise"]},
{"Question": "yaxshi", "RightAnswer": "well", "options": ["trick","safe","reply"]}],	
"level 2" : [
    {"Question": "sarguzasht", "RightAnswer": "adventure", "options": ["well","trick","safe"]},
{"Question": "yaqinlashmoq", "RightAnswer": "approach", "options": ["adventure","well","trick"]},
{"Question": "ehtiyotkorlik bilan", "RightAnswer": "carefully", "options": ["approach","adventure","well"]},
{"Question": "kimyoviy", "RightAnswer": "chemical", "options": ["carefully","approach","adventure"]},
{"Question": "yaratmoq", "RightAnswer": "create", "options": ["chemical","carefully","approach"]},
{"Question": "yomonlik", "RightAnswer": "evil", "options": ["create","chemical","carefully"]},
{"Question": "tajriba", "RightAnswer": "experiment", "options": ["evil","create","chemical"]},
{"Question": "o'ldirmoq", "RightAnswer": "kill", "options": ["experiment","evil","create"]},
{"Question": "laboratoriya", "RightAnswer": "laboratory", "options": ["kill","experiment","evil"]},
{"Question": "kulmoq", "RightAnswer": "laugh", "options": ["laboratory","kill","experiment"]},
{"Question": "baland ovozda", "RightAnswer": "loud", "options": ["laugh","laboratory","kill"]},
{"Question": "asabiy", "RightAnswer": "nervous", "options": ["loud","laugh","laboratory"]},
{"Question": "shovqin", "RightAnswer": "noise", "options": ["nervous","loud","laugh"]},
{"Question": "loyiha", "RightAnswer": "project", "options": ["noise","nervous","loud"]},
{"Question": "qo'rqitmoq", "RightAnswer": "scare", "options": ["project","noise","nervous"]},
{"Question": "sir", "RightAnswer": "secret", "options": ["scare","project","noise"]},
{"Question": "baqirmoq", "RightAnswer": "shout", "options": ["secret","scare","project"]},
{"Question": "hid", "RightAnswer": "smell", "options": ["shout","secret","scare"]},
{"Question": "qo'rqinchli", "RightAnswer": "terrible", "options": ["smell","shout","secret"]},
{"Question": "yomonroq", "RightAnswer": "worse", "options": ["terrible","smell","shout"]}],	
"level 3" : [
    {"Question": "begona", "RightAnswer": "alien", "options": ["worse","terrible","smell"]},
{"Question": "orasida", "RightAnswer": "among", "options": ["alien","worse","terrible"]},
{"Question": "grafik ,jadval", "RightAnswer": "chart", "options": ["among","alien","worse"]},
{"Question": "bulut", "RightAnswer": "cloud", "options": ["chart","among","alien"]},
{"Question": "tushunmoq", "RightAnswer": "comprehend", "options": ["cloud","chart","among"]},
{"Question": "ta'riflamoq", "RightAnswer": "describe", "options": ["comprehend","cloud","chart"]},
{"Question": "qachon bo'lsa ham", "RightAnswer": "ever", "options": ["describe","comprehend","cloud"]},
{"Question": "muvaffaqiyatsizlikka uchramoq", "RightAnswer": "fail", "options": ["ever","describe","comprehend"]},
{"Question": "do'stona", "RightAnswer": "friendly", "options": ["fail","ever","describe"]},
{"Question": "baho", "RightAnswer": "grade", "options": ["friendly","fail","ever"]},
{"Question": "o'rniga", "RightAnswer": "instead", "options": ["grade","friendly","fail"]},
{"Question": "kutubxona", "RightAnswer": "library", "options": ["instead","grade","friendly"]},
{"Question": "sayyora", "RightAnswer": "planet", "options": ["library","instead","grade"]},
{"Question": "hisobot", "RightAnswer": "report", "options": ["planet","library","instead"]},
{"Question": "bir nechta", "RightAnswer": "several", "options": ["report","planet","library"]},
{"Question": "hal qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "solve", "options": ["several","report","planet"]},
{"Question": "to'satdan", "RightAnswer": "suddenly", "options": ["solve","several","report"]},
{"Question": "faraz qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "suppose", "options": ["suddenly","solve","several"]},
{"Question": "olam", "RightAnswer": "universe", "options": ["suppose","suddenly","solve"]},
{"Question": "ko'rinish", "RightAnswer": "view", "options": ["universe","suppose","suddenly"]}],	
"level 4" : [
    {"Question": "muvofiq", "RightAnswer": "appropriate", "options": ["view","universe","suppose"]},
{"Question": "oldini olmoq, saqlanmoq", "RightAnswer": "avoid", "options": ["appropriate","view","universe"]},
{"Question": "o'zini tutmoq", "RightAnswer": "behave", "options": ["avoid","appropriate","view"]},
{"Question": "sokin", "RightAnswer": "calm", "options": ["behave","avoid","appropriate"]},
{"Question": "tashvishlanmoq", "RightAnswer": "concern", "options": ["calm","behave","avoid"]},
{"Question": "mamnun", "RightAnswer": "content", "options": ["concern","calm","behave"]},
{"Question": "kutmoq", "RightAnswer": "expect", "options": ["content","concern","calm"]},
{"Question": "tez-tez", "RightAnswer": "frequently", "options": ["expect","content","concern"]},
{"Question": "odat", "RightAnswer": "habit", "options": ["frequently","expect","content"]},
{"Question": "ko'rsatma bermoq", "RightAnswer": "instruct", "options": ["habit","frequently","expect"]},
{"Question": "masala", "RightAnswer": "issue", "options": ["instruct","habit","frequently"]},
{"Question": "hech biri", "RightAnswer": "none", "options": ["issue","instruct","habit"]},
{"Question": "sabrli", "RightAnswer": "patient", "options": ["none","issue","instruct"]},
{"Question": "ijobiy", "RightAnswer": "positive", "options": ["patient","none","issue"]},
{"Question": "jazolamoq", "RightAnswer": "punish", "options": ["positive","patient","none"]},
{"Question": "vakillik qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "represent", "options": ["punish","positive","patient"]},
{"Question": "silkitmoq", "RightAnswer": "shake", "options": ["represent","punish","positive"]},
{"Question": "tarqalmoq", "RightAnswer": "spread", "options": ["shake","represent","punish"]},
{"Question": "sayrga chiqmoq", "RightAnswer": "stroll", "options": ["spread","shake","represent"]},
{"Question": "qishloq", "RightAnswer": "village", "options": ["stroll","spread","shake"]}],	
"level 5" : [
    {"Question": "xabardor", "RightAnswer": "aware", "options": ["village","stroll","spread"]},
{"Question": "yomon", "RightAnswer": "badly", "options": ["aware","village","stroll"]},
{"Question": "tegishli bo'lmoq", "RightAnswer": "belong", "options": ["badly","aware","village"]},
{"Question": "davom etmoq", "RightAnswer": "continue", "options": ["belong","badly","aware"]},
{"Question": "xato", "RightAnswer": "error", "options": ["continue","belong","badly"]},
{"Question": "tajriba", "RightAnswer": "experience", "options": ["error","continue","belong"]},
{"Question": "maydon", "RightAnswer": "field", "options": ["experience","error","continue"]},
{"Question": "jarohat olmoq", "RightAnswer": "hurt", "options": ["field","experience","error"]},
{"Question": "hukm baho", "RightAnswer": "judgment", "options": ["hurt","field","experience"]},
{"Question": "ehtimol", "RightAnswer": "likely", "options": ["judgment","hurt","field"]},
{"Question": "oddiy", "RightAnswer": "normal", "options": ["likely","judgment","hurt"]},
{"Question": "noyob", "RightAnswer": "rare", "options": ["normal","likely","judgment"]},
{"Question": "rohatlanmoq", "RightAnswer": "relax", "options": ["rare","normal","likely"]},
{"Question": "so'ramoq", "RightAnswer": "request", "options": ["relax","rare","normal"]},
{"Question": "yashamoq", "RightAnswer": "reside", "options": ["request","relax","rare"]},
{"Question": "natija", "RightAnswer": "result", "options": ["reside","request","relax"]},
{"Question": "dumalamoq", "RightAnswer": "roll", "options": ["result","reside","request"]},
{"Question": "chunki", "RightAnswer": "since", "options": ["roll","result","reside"]},
{"Question": "ko'rinadigan", "RightAnswer": "visible", "options": ["since","roll","result"]},
{"Question": "yovvoyi", "RightAnswer": "wild", "options": ["visible","since","roll"]}],	
"level 6" : [
    {"Question": "afzallik", "RightAnswer": "advantage", "options": ["wild","visible","since"]},
{"Question": "sababi", "RightAnswer": "cause", "options": ["advantage","wild","visible"]},
{"Question": "tanlov", "RightAnswer": "choice", "options": ["cause","advantage","wild"]},
{"Question": "jamoa", "RightAnswer": "community", "options": ["choice","cause","advantage"]},
{"Question": "o'lik", "RightAnswer": "dead", "options": ["community","choice","cause"]},
{"Question": "masofa", "RightAnswer": "distance", "options": ["dead","community","choice"]},
{"Question": "qochmoq", "RightAnswer": "escape", "options": ["distance","dead","community"]},
{"Question": "yuz", "RightAnswer": "face", "options": ["escape","distance","dead"]},
{"Question": "amal qilmoq, ortidan bormoq", "RightAnswer": "follow", "options": ["face","escape","distance"]},
{"Question": "qo'rquv", "RightAnswer": "fright", "options": ["follow","face","escape"]},
{"Question": "arvoh", "RightAnswer": "ghost", "options": ["fright","follow","face"]},
{"Question": "shaxs", "RightAnswer": "individual", "options": ["ghost","fright","follow"]},
{"Question": "uy hayvoni", "RightAnswer": "pet", "options": ["individual","ghost","fright"]},
{"Question": "erishmoq, yetib bormoq", "RightAnswer": "reach", "options": ["pet","individual","ghost"]},
{"Question": "qaytmoq", "RightAnswer": "return", "options": ["reach","pet","individual"]},
{"Question": "omon qolmoq", "RightAnswer": "survive", "options": ["return","reach","pet"]},
{"Question": "xafa", "RightAnswer": "upset", "options": ["survive","return","reach"]},
{"Question": "ovoz", "RightAnswer": "voice", "options": ["upset","survive","return"]},
{"Question": "ob-havo", "RightAnswer": "weather", "options": ["voice","upset","survive"]},
{"Question": "dono", "RightAnswer": "wise", "options": ["weather","voice","upset"]}],	
"level 7" : [
    {"Question": "ruxsat bermoq", "RightAnswer": "allow", "options": ["wise","weather","voice"]},
{"Question": "e'lon qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "announce", "options": ["allow","wise","weather"]},
{"Question": "yonida", "RightAnswer": "beside", "options": ["announce","allow","wise"]},
{"Question": "qiyinchilik", "RightAnswer": "challenge", "options": ["beside","announce","allow"]},
{"Question": "takidlamoq", "RightAnswer": "claim", "options": ["challenge","beside","announce"]},
{"Question": "holat", "RightAnswer": "condition", "options": ["claim","challenge","beside"]},
{"Question": "hissa qo'shmoq", "RightAnswer": "contribute", "options": ["condition","claim","challenge"]},
{"Question": "farq", "RightAnswer": "difference", "options": ["contribute","condition","claim"]},
{"Question": "bo'lmoq", "RightAnswer": "divide", "options": ["difference","contribute","condition"]},
{"Question": "mutaxassis", "RightAnswer": "expert", "options": ["divide","difference","contribute"]},
{"Question": "mashhur", "RightAnswer": "famous", "options": ["expert","divide","difference"]},
{"Question": "kuch", "RightAnswer": "force", "options": ["famous","expert","divide"]},
{"Question": "zarar", "RightAnswer": "harm", "options": ["force","famous","expert"]},
{"Question": "yotadi", "RightAnswer": "lay", "options": ["harm","force","famous"]},
{"Question": "tinchlik", "RightAnswer": "peace", "options": ["lay","harm","force"]},
{"Question": "shahzoda", "RightAnswer": "prince", "options": ["peace","lay","harm"]},
{"Question": "himoya qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "protect", "options": ["prince","peace","lay"]},
{"Question": "ma'no", "RightAnswer": "sense", "options": ["protect","prince","peace"]},
{"Question": "to'satdan", "RightAnswer": "sudden", "options": ["sense","protect","prince"]},
{"Question": "shuning uchun", "RightAnswer": "therefore", "options": ["sudden","sense","protect"]}],	
"level 8" : [
    {"Question": "qabul qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "accept", "options": ["therefore","sudden","sense"]},
{"Question": "tartibga solmoq", "RightAnswer": "arrange", "options": ["accept","therefore","sudden"]},
{"Question": "qatnashmoq", "RightAnswer": "attend", "options": ["arrange","accept","therefore"]},
{"Question": "muvozanat", "RightAnswer": "balance", "options": ["attend","arrange","accept"]},
{"Question": "farq", "RightAnswer": "contrast", "options": ["balance","attend","arrange"]},
{"Question": "rag'batlantirmoq", "RightAnswer": "encourage", "options": ["contrast","balance","attend"]},
{"Question": "tanish", "RightAnswer": "familiar", "options": ["encourage","contrast","balance"]},
{"Question": "changallamoq", "RightAnswer": "grab", "options": ["familiar","encourage","contrast"]},
{"Question": "osib qo'ymoq", "RightAnswer": "hang", "options": ["grab","familiar","encourage"]},
{"Question": "katta", "RightAnswer": "huge", "options": ["hang","grab","familiar"]},
{"Question": "zarur", "RightAnswer": "necessary", "options": ["huge","hang","grab"]},
{"Question": "naqsh, tartib", "RightAnswer": "pattern", "options": ["necessary","huge","hang"]},
{"Question": "taklif qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "propose", "options": ["pattern","necessary","huge"]},
{"Question": "maqsad", "RightAnswer": "purpose", "options": ["propose","pattern","necessary"]},
{"Question": "ozod qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "release", "options": ["purpose","propose","pattern"]},
{"Question": "talab qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "require", "options": ["release","purpose","propose"]},
{"Question": "yakka", "RightAnswer": "single", "options": ["require","release","purpose"]},
{"Question": "muvaffaqiyat", "RightAnswer": "success", "options": ["single","require","release"]},
{"Question": "ko'z yoshi, yirtmoq", "RightAnswer": "tear", "options": ["success","single","require"]},
{"Question": "nazariya", "RightAnswer": "theory", "options": ["tear","success","single"]}],	
"level 9" : [
    {"Question": "qarshi", "RightAnswer": "against", "options": ["theory","tear","success"]},
{"Question": "sohil", "RightAnswer": "beach", "options": ["against","theory","tear"]},
{"Question": "zarar", "RightAnswer": "damage", "options": ["beach","against","theory"]},
{"Question": "kashf qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "discover", "options": ["damage","beach","against"]},
{"Question": "hissiyot", "RightAnswer": "emotion", "options": ["discover","damage","beach"]},
{"Question": "tuzatmoq", "RightAnswer": "fix", "options": ["emotion","discover","damage"]},
{"Question": "samimiy", "RightAnswer": "frank", "options": ["fix","emotion","discover"]},
{"Question": "aniqlash", "RightAnswer": "identify", "options": ["frank","fix","emotion"]},
{"Question": "orol", "RightAnswer": "island", "options": ["identify","frank","fix"]},
{"Question": "okean", "RightAnswer": "ocean", "options": ["island","identify","frank"]},
{"Question": "ehtimol", "RightAnswer": "perhaps", "options": ["ocean","island","identify"]},
{"Question": "yoqimli", "RightAnswer": "pleasant", "options": ["perhaps","ocean","island"]},
{"Question": "oldini olmoq", "RightAnswer": "prevent", "options": ["pleasant","perhaps","ocean"]},
{"Question": "tosh", "RightAnswer": "rock", "options": ["prevent","pleasant","perhaps"]},
{"Question": "asramoq", "RightAnswer": "save", "options": ["rock","prevent","pleasant"]},
{"Question": "qadam", "RightAnswer": "step", "options": ["save","rock","prevent"]},
{"Question": "hali ham", "RightAnswer": "still", "options": ["step","save","rock"]},
{"Question": "ta'm, tatib ko'rmoq", "RightAnswer": "taste", "options": ["still","step","save"]},
{"Question": "otmoq", "RightAnswer": "throw", "options": ["taste","still","step"]},
{"Question": "to'lqin", "RightAnswer": "wave", "options": ["throw","taste","still"]}],	
"level 10" : [
    {"Question": "foyda", "RightAnswer": "benefit", "options": ["wave","throw","taste"]},
{"Question": "aniq", "RightAnswer": "certain", "options": ["benefit","wave","throw"]},
{"Question": "imkoniyat", "RightAnswer": "chance", "options": ["certain","benefit","wave"]},
{"Question": "ta'sir", "RightAnswer": "effect", "options": ["chance","certain","benefit"]},
{"Question": "muhim", "RightAnswer": "essential", "options": ["effect","chance","certain"]},
{"Question": "uzoq", "RightAnswer": "far", "options": ["essential","effect","chance"]},
{"Question": "diqqat markazi", "RightAnswer": "focus", "options": ["far","essential","effect"]},
{"Question": "vazifa", "RightAnswer": "function", "options": ["focus","far","essential"]},
{"Question": "o't", "RightAnswer": "grass", "options": ["function","focus","far"]},
{"Question": "qo'riqchi", "RightAnswer": "guard", "options": ["grass","function","focus"]},
{"Question": "rasm", "RightAnswer": "image", "options": ["guard","grass","function"]},
{"Question": "darhol", "RightAnswer": "immediate", "options": ["image","guard","grass"]},
{"Question": "asosiy", "RightAnswer": "primary", "options": ["immediate","image","guard"]},
{"Question": "mag'rur", "RightAnswer": "proud", "options": ["primary","immediate","image"]},
{"Question": "qolmoq", "RightAnswer": "remain", "options": ["proud","primary","immediate"]},
{"Question": "dam olmoq,", "RightAnswer": "rest", "options": ["remain","proud","primary"]},
{"Question": "alohida", "RightAnswer": "separate", "options": ["rest","remain","proud"]},
{"Question": "joy", "RightAnswer": "site", "options": ["separate","rest","remain"]},
{"Question": "dum", "RightAnswer": "tail", "options": ["site","separate","rest"]},
{"Question": "muammo", "RightAnswer": "trouble", "options": ["tail","site","separate"]}],	
"level 11" : [
    {"Question": "endi qaytib", "RightAnswer": "anymore", "options": ["trouble","tail","site"]},
{"Question": "uyquda", "RightAnswer": "asleep", "options": ["anymore","trouble","tail"]},
{"Question": "maymunjon", "RightAnswer": "berry", "options": ["asleep","anymore","trouble"]},
{"Question": "to'plamoq", "RightAnswer": "collect", "options": ["berry","asleep","anymore"]},
{"Question": "raqobatlashmoq", "RightAnswer": "compete", "options": ["collect","berry","asleep"]},
{"Question": "suhbat", "RightAnswer": "conversation", "options": ["compete","collect","berry"]},
{"Question": "jonzot", "RightAnswer": "creature", "options": ["conversation","compete","collect"]},
{"Question": "qaror", "RightAnswer": "decision", "options": ["creature","conversation","compete"]},
{"Question": "yoki", "RightAnswer": "either", "options": ["decision","creature","conversation"]},
{"Question": "o'rmon", "RightAnswer": "forest", "options": ["either","decision","creature"]},
{"Question": "yer", "RightAnswer": "ground", "options": ["forest","either","decision"]},
{"Question": "tanishtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "introduce", "options": ["ground","forest","either"]},
{"Question": "turmush qurmoq", "RightAnswer": "marry", "options": ["introduce","ground","forest"]},
{"Question": "tayyorlamoq", "RightAnswer": "prepare", "options": ["marry","introduce","ground"]},
{"Question": "suzmoq", "RightAnswer": "sail", "options": ["prepare","marry","introduce"]},
{"Question": "jiddiy", "RightAnswer": "serious", "options": ["sail","prepare","marry"]},
{"Question": "sarflamoq", "RightAnswer": "spend", "options": ["serious","sail","prepare"]},
{"Question": "g'alati", "RightAnswer": "strange", "options": ["spend","serious","sail"]},
{"Question": "haqiqat", "RightAnswer": "truth", "options": ["strange","spend","serious"]},
{"Question": "uyg'otmoq", "RightAnswer": "wake", "options": ["truth","strange","spend"]}],	
"level 12" : [
    {"Question": "yolg'iz", "RightAnswer": "alone", "options": ["wake","truth","strange"]},
{"Question": "xonadon", "RightAnswer": "apartment", "options": ["alone","wake","truth"]},
{"Question": "maqola", "RightAnswer": "article", "options": ["apartment","alone","wake"]},
{"Question": "rassom", "RightAnswer": "artist", "options": ["article","apartment","alone"]},
{"Question": "munosabat", "RightAnswer": "attitude", "options": ["artist","article","apartment"]},
{"Question": "solishtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "compare", "options": ["attitude","artist","article"]},
{"Question": "hukm qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "judge", "options": ["compare","attitude","artist"]},
{"Question": "jurnal", "RightAnswer": "magazine", "options": ["judge","compare","attitude"]},
{"Question": "ashyo", "RightAnswer": "material", "options": ["magazine","judge","compare"]},
{"Question": "ovqat", "RightAnswer": "meal", "options": ["material","magazine","judge"]},
{"Question": "uslub", "RightAnswer": "method", "options": ["meal","material","magazine"]},
{"Question": "qo'shni", "RightAnswer": "neighbor", "options": ["method","meal","material"]},
{"Question": "professional", "RightAnswer": "professional", "options": ["neighbor","method","meal"]},
{"Question": "foyda", "RightAnswer": "profit", "options": ["professional","neighbor","method"]},
{"Question": "sifat", "RightAnswer": "quality", "options": ["profit","professional","neighbor"]},
{"Question": "shakl", "RightAnswer": "shape", "options": ["quality","profit","professional"]},
{"Question": "bo'shliq", "RightAnswer": "space", "options": ["shape","quality","profit"]},
{"Question": "zina", "RightAnswer": "stair", "options": ["space","shape","quality"]},
{"Question": "belgi", "RightAnswer": "symbol", "options": ["stair","space","shape"]},
{"Question": "oriq", "RightAnswer": "thin", "options": ["symbol","stair","space"]}],	
"level 13" : [
    {"Question": "qon", "RightAnswer": "blood", "options": ["thin","symbol","stair"]},
{"Question": "kuymoq", "RightAnswer": "burn", "options": ["blood","thin","symbol"]},
{"Question": "hujayra, panjara", "RightAnswer": "cell", "options": ["burn","blood","thin"]},
{"Question": "o'z ichiga olmoq", "RightAnswer": "contain", "options": ["cell","burn","blood"]},
{"Question": "to'g'ri", "RightAnswer": "correct", "options": ["contain","cell","burn"]},
{"Question": "ekin", "RightAnswer": "crop", "options": ["correct","contain","cell"]},
{"Question": "talab", "RightAnswer": "demand", "options": ["crop","correct","contain"]},
{"Question": "teng", "RightAnswer": "equal", "options": ["demand","crop","correct"]},
{"Question": "boqmoq", "RightAnswer": "feed", "options": ["equal","demand","crop"]},
{"Question": "teshik", "RightAnswer": "hole", "options": ["feed","equal","demand"]},
{"Question": "o'smoq", "RightAnswer": "increase", "options": ["hole","feed","equal"]},
{"Question": "lord", "RightAnswer": "lord", "options": ["increase","hole","feed"]},
{"Question": "qarzdor", "RightAnswer": "owe", "options": ["lord","increase","hole"]},
{"Question": "orin", "RightAnswer": "position", "options": ["owe","lord","increase"]},
{"Question": "oshirmoq", "RightAnswer": "raise", "options": ["position","owe","lord"]},
{"Question": "mas'ul", "RightAnswer": "responsible", "options": ["raise","position","owe"]},
{"Question": "ko'rish", "RightAnswer": "sight", "options": ["responsible","raise","position"]},
{"Question": "dog` joy", "RightAnswer": "spot", "options": ["sight","responsible","raise"]},
{"Question": "tuzilmoq", "RightAnswer": "structure", "options": ["spot","sight","responsible"]},
{"Question": "butun", "RightAnswer": "whole", "options": ["structure","spot","sight"]}],	
"level 14" : [
    {"Question": "murabbiy", "RightAnswer": "coach", "options": ["whole","structure","spot"]},
{"Question": "boshqaruv", "RightAnswer": "control", "options": ["coach","whole","structure"]},
{"Question": "tushuntirish", "RightAnswer": "description", "options": ["control","coach","whole"]},
{"Question": "to'g'ridan-to'g'ri", "RightAnswer": "direct", "options": ["description","control","coach"]},
{"Question": "imtihon", "RightAnswer": "exam", "options": ["direct","description","control"]},
{"Question": "misol", "RightAnswer": "example", "options": ["exam","direct","description"]},
{"Question": "chegara", "RightAnswer": "limit", "options": ["example","exam","direct"]},
{"Question": "mahalliy", "RightAnswer": "local", "options": ["limit","example","exam"]},
{"Question": "sehrli", "RightAnswer": "magical", "options": ["local","limit","example"]},
{"Question": "pochta", "RightAnswer": "mail", "options": ["magical","local","limit"]},
{"Question": "roman", "RightAnswer": "novel", "options": ["mail","magical","local"]},
{"Question": "reja", "RightAnswer": "outline", "options": ["novel","mail","magical"]},
{"Question": "shoir", "RightAnswer": "poet", "options": ["outline","novel","mail"]},
{"Question": "bosib chiqarmoq", "RightAnswer": "print", "options": ["poet","outline","novel"]},
{"Question": "sahna", "RightAnswer": "scene", "options": ["print","poet","outline"]},
{"Question": "varoq", "RightAnswer": "sheet", "options": ["scene","print","poet"]},
{"Question": "ahmoqona", "RightAnswer": "silly", "options": ["sheet","scene","print"]},
{"Question": "do'kon saqlamoq", "RightAnswer": "store", "options": ["silly","sheet","scene"]},
{"Question": "azoblanmoq", "RightAnswer": "suffer", "options": ["store","silly","sheet"]},
{"Question": "texnologiya", "RightAnswer": "technology", "options": ["suffer","store","silly"]}],	
"level 15" : [
    {"Question": "kesib", "RightAnswer": "across", "options": ["technology","suffer","store"]},
{"Question": "nafas olmoq", "RightAnswer": "breathe", "options": ["across","technology","suffer"]},
{"Question": "xususiyat", "RightAnswer": "characteristic", "options": ["breathe","across","technology"]},
{"Question": "iste'mol qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "consume", "options": ["characteristic","breathe","across"]},
{"Question": "hayratlanmoq", "RightAnswer": "excite", "options": ["consume","characteristic","breathe"]},
{"Question": "haddan tashqari", "RightAnswer": "extreme", "options": ["excite","consume","characteristic"]},
{"Question": "qo'rquv", "RightAnswer": "fear", "options": ["extreme","excite","consume"]},
{"Question": "baxtli", "RightAnswer": "fortunate", "options": ["fear","extreme","excite"]},
{"Question": "sodir bo'lmoq", "RightAnswer": "happen", "options": ["fortunate","fear","extreme"]},
{"Question": "uzunlik", "RightAnswer": "length", "options": ["happen","fortunate","fear"]},
{"Question": "xato", "RightAnswer": "mistake", "options": ["length","happen","fortunate"]},
{"Question": "kuzatmoq", "RightAnswer": "observe", "options": ["mistake","length","happen"]},
{"Question": "imkoniyat", "RightAnswer": "opportunity", "options": ["observe","mistake","length"]},
{"Question": "sovrin", "RightAnswer": "prize", "options": ["opportunity","observe","mistake"]},
{"Question": "irq", "RightAnswer": "race", "options": ["prize","opportunity","observe"]},
{"Question": "tushunmoq", "RightAnswer": "realize", "options": ["race","prize","opportunity"]},
{"Question": "javob bermoq", "RightAnswer": "respond", "options": ["realize","race","prize"]},
{"Question": "xavf", "RightAnswer": "risk", "options": ["respond","realize","race"]},
{"Question": "hayron bo`lmoq", "RightAnswer": "wonder", "options": ["risk","respond","realize"]},
{"Question": "hali", "RightAnswer": "yet", "options": ["wonder","risk","respond"]}],	
"level 16" : [
    {"Question": "akademiya", "RightAnswer": "academy", "options": ["yet","wonder","risk"]},
{"Question": "qadimiy", "RightAnswer": "ancient", "options": ["academy","yet","wonder"]},
{"Question": "taxta", "RightAnswer": "board", "options": ["ancient","academy","yet"]},
{"Question": "asr", "RightAnswer": "century", "options": ["board","ancient","academy"]},
{"Question": "qo`shimcha ma`lumot", "RightAnswer": "clue", "options": ["century","board","ancient"]},
{"Question": "kontsert", "RightAnswer": "concert", "options": ["clue","century","board"]},
{"Question": "graflik", "RightAnswer": "county", "options": ["concert","clue","century"]},
{"Question": "lug'at", "RightAnswer": "dictionary", "options": ["county","concert","clue"]},
{"Question": "mavjud", "RightAnswer": "exist", "options": ["dictionary","county","concert"]},
{"Question": "tekis", "RightAnswer": "flat", "options": ["exist","dictionary","county"]},
{"Question": "jentleman", "RightAnswer": "gentleman", "options": ["flat","exist","dictionary"]},
{"Question": "maxfiy", "RightAnswer": "hidden", "options": ["gentleman","flat","exist"]},
{"Question": "balki", "RightAnswer": "maybe", "options": ["hidden","gentleman","flat"]},
{"Question": "ofitser", "RightAnswer": "officer", "options": ["maybe","hidden","gentleman"]},
{"Question": "original", "RightAnswer": "original", "options": ["officer","maybe","hidden"]},
{"Question": "funt qoqmoq", "RightAnswer": "pound", "options": ["original","officer","maybe"]},
{"Question": "jarayon", "RightAnswer": "process", "options": ["pound","original","officer"]},
{"Question": "nashr etmoq", "RightAnswer": "publish", "options": ["process","pound","original"]},
{"Question": "teatr", "RightAnswer": "theater", "options": ["publish","process","pound"]},
{"Question": "boylik", "RightAnswer": "wealth", "options": ["theater","publish","process"]}],	
"level 17" : [
    {"Question": "qadrlamoq", "RightAnswer": "appreciate", "options": ["wealth","theater","publish"]},
{"Question": "mavjud", "RightAnswer": "available", "options": ["appreciate","wealth","theater"]},
{"Question": "urmoq", "RightAnswer": "beat", "options": ["available","appreciate","wealth"]},
{"Question": "yorqin", "RightAnswer": "bright", "options": ["beat","available","appreciate"]},
{"Question": "nishonlamoq", "RightAnswer": "celebrate", "options": ["bright","beat","available"]},
{"Question": "aniqlamoq", "RightAnswer": "determine", "options": ["celebrate","bright","beat"]},
{"Question": "yo'qolmoq", "RightAnswer": "disappear", "options": ["determine","celebrate","bright"]},
{"Question": "yana boshqa", "RightAnswer": "else", "options": ["disappear","determine","celebrate"]},
{"Question": "adolatli", "RightAnswer": "fair", "options": ["else","disappear","determine"]},
{"Question": "oqim", "RightAnswer": "flow", "options": ["fair","else","disappear"]},
{"Question": "oldinga", "RightAnswer": "forward", "options": ["flow","fair","else"]},
{"Question": "tepalik", "RightAnswer": "hill", "options": ["forward","flow","fair"]},
{"Question": "daraja", "RightAnswer": "level", "options": ["hill","forward","flow"]},
{"Question": "yolg'iz", "RightAnswer": "lone", "options": ["level","hill","forward"]},
{"Question": "ko'lmak", "RightAnswer": "puddle", "options": ["lone","level","hill"]},
{"Question": "javob", "RightAnswer": "response", "options": ["puddle","lone","level"]},
{"Question": "mavsum", "RightAnswer": "season", "options": ["response","puddle","lone"]},
{"Question": "yechim", "RightAnswer": "solution", "options": ["season","response","puddle"]},
{"Question": "chiqindi", "RightAnswer": "waste", "options": ["solution","season","response"]},
{"Question": "mi yoki", "RightAnswer": "whether", "options": ["waste","solution","season"]}],	
"level 18" : [
    {"Question": "bahslashmoq", "RightAnswer": "argue", "options": ["whether","waste","solution"]},
{"Question": "muloqot qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "communicate", "options": ["argue","whether","waste"]},
{"Question": "olomon", "RightAnswer": "crowd", "options": ["communicate","argue","whether"]},
{"Question": "qaram bo`lmoq", "RightAnswer": "depend", "options": ["crowd","communicate","argue"]},
{"Question": "ovqat", "RightAnswer": "dish", "options": ["depend","crowd","communicate"]},
{"Question": "bo'sh", "RightAnswer": "empty", "options": ["dish","depend","crowd"]},
{"Question": "aniq", "RightAnswer": "exact", "options": ["empty","dish","depend"]},
{"Question": "yangi", "RightAnswer": "fresh", "options": ["exact","empty","dish"]},
{"Question": "to'plamoq", "RightAnswer": "gather", "options": ["fresh","exact","empty"]},
{"Question": "ko`rsatmoq", "RightAnswer": "indicate", "options": ["gather","fresh","exact"]},
{"Question": "buyum", "RightAnswer": "item", "options": ["indicate","gather","fresh"]},
{"Question": "taklif qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "offer", "options": ["item","indicate","gather"]},
{"Question": "narx", "RightAnswer": "price", "options": ["offer","item","indicate"]},
{"Question": "mahsulot", "RightAnswer": "product", "options": ["price","offer","item"]},
{"Question": "mulk", "RightAnswer": "property", "options": ["product","price","offer"]},
{"Question": "sotib olmoq", "RightAnswer": "purchase", "options": ["property","product","price"]},
{"Question": "tavsiya qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "recommend", "options": ["purchase","property","product"]},
{"Question": "tanlamoq", "RightAnswer": "select", "options": ["recommend","purchase","property"]},
{"Question": "asbob", "RightAnswer": "tool", "options": ["select","recommend","purchase"]},
{"Question": "davolamoq,munosabatda bo'lmoq", "RightAnswer": "treat", "options": ["tool","select","recommend"]}],	
"level 19" : [
    {"Question": "tirik", "RightAnswer": "alive", "options": ["treat","tool","select"]},
{"Question": "suyak", "RightAnswer": "bone", "options": ["alive","treat","tool"]},
{"Question": "bezovta qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "bother", "options": ["bone","alive","treat"]},
{"Question": "kapitan", "RightAnswer": "captain", "options": ["bother","bone","alive"]},
{"Question": "xulosa", "RightAnswer": "conclusion", "options": ["captain","bother","bone"]},
{"Question": "shubha", "RightAnswer": "doubt", "options": ["conclusion","captain","bother"]},
{"Question": "kashf qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "explore", "options": ["doubt","conclusion","captain"]},
{"Question": "xorijiy", "RightAnswer": "foreign", "options": ["explore","doubt","conclusion"]},
{"Question": "mamnun", "RightAnswer": "glad", "options": ["foreign","explore","doubt"]},
{"Question": "biroq", "RightAnswer": "however", "options": ["glad","foreign","explore"]},
{"Question": "adolatsizlik", "RightAnswer": "injustice", "options": ["however","glad","foreign"]},
{"Question": "xalqaro", "RightAnswer": "international", "options": ["injustice","however","glad"]},
{"Question": "yurist", "RightAnswer": "lawyer", "options": ["international","injustice","however"]},
{"Question": "eslatmoq", "RightAnswer": "mention", "options": ["lawyer","international","injustice"]},
{"Question": "siyosat", "RightAnswer": "policy", "options": ["mention","lawyer","international"]},
{"Question": "ijtimoiy", "RightAnswer": "social", "options": ["policy","mention","lawyer"]},
{"Question": "nutq", "RightAnswer": "speech", "options": ["social","policy","mention"]},
{"Question": "xodimlar", "RightAnswer": "staff", "options": ["speech","social","policy"]},
{"Question": "tomonga", "RightAnswer": "toward", "options": ["staff","speech","social"]},
{"Question": "yog'och", "RightAnswer": "wood", "options": ["toward","staff","speech"]}],	
"level 20" : [
    {"Question": "erishmoq", "RightAnswer": "achieve", "options": ["wood","toward","staff"]},
{"Question": "maslahat bermoq", "RightAnswer": "advise", "options": ["achieve","wood","toward"]},
{"Question": "allaqachon", "RightAnswer": "already", "options": ["advise","achieve","wood"]},
{"Question": "asosiy", "RightAnswer": "basic", "options": ["already","advise","achieve"]},
{"Question": "bo'lak", "RightAnswer": "bit", "options": ["basic","already","advise"]},
{"Question": "o'ylab ko'rmoq", "RightAnswer": "consider", "options": ["bit","basic","already"]},
{"Question": "yo'q qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "destroy", "options": ["consider","bit","basic"]},
{"Question": "ko'nglini ko'tarmoq", "RightAnswer": "entertain", "options": ["destroy","consider","bit"]},
{"Question": "qo'shimcha", "RightAnswer": "extra", "options": ["entertain","destroy","consider"]},
{"Question": "maqsad", "RightAnswer": "goal", "options": ["extra","entertain","destroy"]},
{"Question": "yolg'on gapirmoq", "RightAnswer": "lie", "options": ["goal","extra","entertain"]},
{"Question": "go'sht", "RightAnswer": "meat", "options": ["lie","goal","extra"]},
{"Question": "fikr", "RightAnswer": "opinion", "options": ["meat","lie","goal"]},
{"Question": "haqiqiy", "RightAnswer": "real", "options": ["opinion","meat","lie"]},
{"Question": "aks ettirmoq", "RightAnswer": "reflect", "options": ["real","opinion","meat"]},
{"Question": "deb bilmoq", "RightAnswer": "regard", "options": ["reflect","real","opinion"]},
{"Question": "xizmat qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "serve", "options": ["regard","reflect","real"]},
{"Question": "sabzavot", "RightAnswer": "vegetable", "options": ["serve","regard","reflect"]},
{"Question": "urush", "RightAnswer": "war", "options": ["vegetable","serve","regard"]},
{"Question": "qiymat", "RightAnswer": "worth", "options": ["war","vegetable","serve"]}],	
"level 21" : [
    {"Question": "paydo bo'lmoq", "RightAnswer": "appear", "options": ["worth","war","vegetable"]},
{"Question": "tayanch", "RightAnswer": "base", "options": ["appear","worth","war"]},
{"Question": "miya", "RightAnswer": "brain", "options": ["base","appear","worth"]},
{"Question": "martaba", "RightAnswer": "career", "options": ["brain","base","appear"]},
{"Question": "xizmatchi", "RightAnswer": "clerk", "options": ["career","brain","base"]},
{"Question": "harakat", "RightAnswer": "effort", "options": ["clerk","career","brain"]},
{"Question": "kirmoq", "RightAnswer": "enter", "options": ["effort","clerk","career"]},
{"Question": "ajoyib", "RightAnswer": "excellent", "options": ["enter","effort","clerk"]},
{"Question": "qahramon", "RightAnswer": "hero", "options": ["excellent","enter","effort"]},
{"Question": "shoshilmoq", "RightAnswer": "hurry", "options": ["hero","excellent","enter"]},
{"Question": "axborot bermoq", "RightAnswer": "inform", "options": ["hurry","hero","excellent"]},
{"Question": "keyinchalik", "RightAnswer": "later", "options": ["inform","hurry","hero"]},
{"Question": "tashlab ketmoq", "RightAnswer": "leave", "options": ["later","inform","hurry"]},
{"Question": "topmoq", "RightAnswer": "locate", "options": ["leave","later","inform"]},
{"Question": "hamshira", "RightAnswer": "nurse", "options": ["locate","leave","later"]},
{"Question": "operatsiya", "RightAnswer": "operation", "options": ["nurse","locate","leave"]},
{"Question": "og'riq", "RightAnswer": "pain", "options": ["operation","nurse","locate"]},
{"Question": "rad qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "refuse", "options": ["pain","operation","nurse"]},
{"Question": "garchi", "RightAnswer": "though", "options": ["refuse","pain","operation"]},
{"Question": "turli", "RightAnswer": "various", "options": ["though","refuse","pain"]}],	
"level 22" : [
    {"Question": "dolzarb haqiqiy", "RightAnswer": "actual", "options": ["various","though","refuse"]},
{"Question": "hayratlantirmoq", "RightAnswer": "amaze", "options": ["actual","various","though"]},
{"Question": "zaryadlash", "RightAnswer": "charge", "options": ["amaze","actual","various"]},
{"Question": "farovonlik", "RightAnswer": "comfort", "options": ["charge","amaze","actual"]},
{"Question": "aloqa qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "contact", "options": ["comfort","charge","amaze"]},
{"Question": "mijoz", "RightAnswer": "customer", "options": ["contact","comfort","charge"]},
{"Question": "yetkazib bermoq", "RightAnswer": "deliver", "options": ["customer","contact","comfort"]},
{"Question": "ishlab topmoq", "RightAnswer": "earn", "options": ["deliver","customer","contact"]},
{"Question": "darvoza", "RightAnswer": "gate", "options": ["earn","deliver","customer"]},
{"Question": "qo'shib qo'ymoq", "RightAnswer": "include", "options": ["gate","earn","deliver"]},
{"Question": "boshqarmoq", "RightAnswer": "manage", "options": ["include","gate","earn"]},
{"Question": "sinoat", "RightAnswer": "mystery", "options": ["manage","include","gate"]},
{"Question": "uchramoq", "RightAnswer": "occur", "options": ["mystery","manage","include"]},
{"Question": "aks qarama-qarshi", "RightAnswer": "opposite", "options": ["occur","mystery","manage"]},
{"Question": "likop", "RightAnswer": "plate", "options": ["opposite","occur","mystery"]},
{"Question": "qabul qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "receive", "options": ["plate","opposite","occur"]},
{"Question": "sovrin", "RightAnswer": "reward", "options": ["receive","plate","opposite"]},
{"Question": "qo'ymoq o'rnatmoq", "RightAnswer": "set", "options": ["reward","receive","plate"]},
{"Question": "o'g'irlamoq", "RightAnswer": "steal", "options": ["set","reward","receive"]},
{"Question": "o'g'ri", "RightAnswer": "thief", "options": ["steal","set","reward"]}],	
"level 23" : [
    {"Question": "odimlamoq", "RightAnswer": "advance", "options": ["thief","steal","set"]},
{"Question": "sportchi", "RightAnswer": "athlete", "options": ["advance","thief","steal"]},
{"Question": "o'rtacha", "RightAnswer": "average", "options": ["athlete","advance","thief"]},
{"Question": "hatti-harakat", "RightAnswer": "behavior", "options": ["average","athlete","advance"]},
{"Question": "orqasida", "RightAnswer": "behind", "options": ["behavior","average","athlete"]},
{"Question": "yo'nalish kurs", "RightAnswer": "course", "options": ["behind","behavior","average"]},
{"Question": "pasaytirmoq", "RightAnswer": "lower", "options": ["course","behind","behavior"]},
{"Question": "o'yin", "RightAnswer": "match", "options": ["lower","course","behind"]},
{"Question": "a'zo", "RightAnswer": "member", "options": ["match","lower","course"]},
{"Question": "aqliy", "RightAnswer": "mental", "options": ["member","match","lower"]},
{"Question": "yo'lovchi", "RightAnswer": "passenger", "options": ["mental","member","match"]},
{"Question": "shaxsiyat", "RightAnswer": "personality", "options": ["passenger","mental","member"]},
{"Question": "she'r", "RightAnswer": "poem", "options": ["personality","passenger","mental"]},
{"Question": "qutb, asos", "RightAnswer": "pole", "options": ["poem","personality","passenger"]},
{"Question": "olib tashlash", "RightAnswer": "remove", "options": ["pole","poem","personality"]},
{"Question": "xavfsizlik", "RightAnswer": "safety", "options": ["remove","pole","poem"]},
{"Question": "otmoq", "RightAnswer": "shoot", "options": ["safety","remove","pole"]},
{"Question": "ovoz", "RightAnswer": "sound", "options": ["shoot","safety","remove"]},
{"Question": "suzmoq", "RightAnswer": "swim", "options": ["sound","shoot","safety"]},
{"Question": "o'rgimchak to'ri", "RightAnswer": "web", "options": ["swim","sound","shoot"]}],	
"level 24" : [
    {"Question": "bo'lak", "RightAnswer": "block", "options": ["web","swim","sound"]},
{"Question": "hayqiriq", "RightAnswer": "cheer", "options": ["block","web","swim"]},
{"Question": "murakkab", "RightAnswer": "complex", "options": ["cheer","block","web"]},
{"Question": "tanqidchi", "RightAnswer": "critic", "options": ["complex","cheer","block"]},
{"Question": "voqea", "RightAnswer": "event", "options": ["critic","complex","cheer"]},
{"Question": "mashq qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "exercise", "options": ["event","critic","complex"]},
{"Question": "mos kelmoq", "RightAnswer": "fit", "options": ["exercise","event","critic"]},
{"Question": "do'stlik", "RightAnswer": "friendship", "options": ["fit","exercise","event"]},
{"Question": "yo'l ko'rsatuvchi", "RightAnswer": "guide", "options": ["friendship","fit","exercise"]},
{"Question": "kamchilik", "RightAnswer": "lack", "options": ["guide","friendship","fit"]},
{"Question": "yo'lak", "RightAnswer": "passage", "options": ["lack","guide","friendship"]},
{"Question": "ijro etmoq", "RightAnswer": "perform", "options": ["passage","lack","guide"]},
{"Question": "bosim", "RightAnswer": "pressure", "options": ["perform","passage","lack"]},
{"Question": "ehtimol", "RightAnswer": "probable", "options": ["pressure","perform","passage"]},
{"Question": "jamoat", "RightAnswer": "public", "options": ["probable","pressure","perform"]},
{"Question": "urmoq", "RightAnswer": "strike", "options": ["public","probable","pressure"]},
{"Question": "qo'llab-quvvatlamoq", "RightAnswer": "support", "options": ["strike","public","probable"]},
{"Question": "vazifa", "RightAnswer": "task", "options": ["support","strike","public"]},
{"Question": "muddat", "RightAnswer": "term", "options": ["task","support","strike"]},
{"Question": "birlashtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "unite", "options": ["term","task","support"]}],	
"level 25" : [
    {"Question": "bog'lamoq", "RightAnswer": "associate", "options": ["unite","term","task"]},
{"Question": "atrof-muhit", "RightAnswer": "environment", "options": ["associate","unite","term"]},
{"Question": "zavod", "RightAnswer": "factory", "options": ["environment","associate","unite"]},
{"Question": "xususiyat", "RightAnswer": "feature", "options": ["factory","environment","associate"]},
{"Question": "misol", "RightAnswer": "instance", "options": ["feature","factory","environment"]},
{"Question": "mashg'ul bo'lmoq", "RightAnswer": "involve", "options": ["instance","feature","factory"]},
{"Question": "dori", "RightAnswer": "medicine", "options": ["involve","instance","feature"]},
{"Question": "aralashtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "mix", "options": ["medicine","involve","instance"]},
{"Question": "tashkillashtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "organize", "options": ["mix","medicine","involve"]},
{"Question": "davr", "RightAnswer": "period", "options": ["organize","mix","medicine"]},
{"Question": "yashamoq", "RightAnswer": "populate", "options": ["period","organize","mix"]},
{"Question": "ishlab chiqarmoq", "RightAnswer": "produce", "options": ["populate","period","organize"]},
{"Question": "bir qator tur", "RightAnswer": "range", "options": ["produce","populate","period"]},
{"Question": "tanimoq", "RightAnswer": "recognize", "options": ["range","produce","populate"]},
{"Question": "muntazam", "RightAnswer": "regular", "options": ["recognize","range","produce"]},
{"Question": "belgi", "RightAnswer": "sign", "options": ["regular","recognize","range"]},
{"Question": "uch", "RightAnswer": "tip", "options": ["sign","regular","recognize"]},
{"Question": "an'ana", "RightAnswer": "tradition", "options": ["tip","sign","regular"]},
{"Question": "axlat", "RightAnswer": "trash", "options": ["tradition","tip","sign"]},
{"Question": "keng", "RightAnswer": "wide", "options": ["trash","tradition","tip"]}],	
"level 26" : [
    {"Question": "maslahat", "RightAnswer": "advice", "options": ["wide","trash","tradition"]},
{"Question": "davomida", "RightAnswer": "along", "options": ["advice","wide","trash"]},
{"Question": "diqqat", "RightAnswer": "attention", "options": ["along","advice","wide"]},
{"Question": "jalb qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "attract", "options": ["attention","along","advice"]},
{"Question": "ko'tarilmoq", "RightAnswer": "climb", "options": ["attract","attention","along"]},
{"Question": "tomchi", "RightAnswer": "drop", "options": ["climb","attract","attention"]},
{"Question": "oxirgi", "RightAnswer": "final", "options": ["drop","climb","attract"]},
{"Question": "uzoqroq", "RightAnswer": "further", "options": ["final","drop","climb"]},
{"Question": "shama qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "imply", "options": ["further","final","drop"]},
{"Question": "saqlamoq", "RightAnswer": "maintain", "options": ["imply","further","final"]},
{"Question": "na", "RightAnswer": "neither", "options": ["maintain","imply","further"]},
{"Question": "aks holda", "RightAnswer": "otherwise", "options": ["neither","maintain","imply"]},
{"Question": "jismoniy", "RightAnswer": "physical", "options": ["otherwise","neither","maintain"]},
{"Question": "isbotlamoq", "RightAnswer": "prove", "options": ["physical","otherwise","neither"]},
{"Question": "javob bermoq", "RightAnswer": "react", "options": ["prove","physical","otherwise"]},
{"Question": "uchmoq", "RightAnswer": "ride", "options": ["react","prove","physical"]},
{"Question": "joylashgan", "RightAnswer": "situated", "options": ["ride","react","prove"]},
{"Question": "jamiyat", "RightAnswer": "society", "options": ["situated","ride","react"]},
{"Question": "standart", "RightAnswer": "standard", "options": ["society","situated","ride"]},
{"Question": "taklif qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "suggest", "options": ["standard","society","situated"]}],	
"level 27" : [
    {"Question": "aslida", "RightAnswer": "actually", "options": ["suggest","standard","society"]},
{"Question": "luqma, tishlamoq", "RightAnswer": "bite", "options": ["actually","suggest","standard"]},
{"Question": "qirg'oq", "RightAnswer": "coast", "options": ["bite","actually","suggest"]},
{"Question": "kelishuv", "RightAnswer": "deal", "options": ["coast","bite","actually"]},
{"Question": "cho'l", "RightAnswer": "desert", "options": ["deal","coast","bite"]},
{"Question": "zilzila", "RightAnswer": "earthquake", "options": ["desert","deal","coast"]},
{"Question": "samarali", "RightAnswer": "effective", "options": ["earthquake","desert","deal"]},
{"Question": "o'rganmoq", "RightAnswer": "examine", "options": ["effective","earthquake","desert"]},
{"Question": "noto'g'ri", "RightAnswer": "false", "options": ["examine","effective","earthquake"]},
{"Question": "sovg'a", "RightAnswer": "gift", "options": ["false","examine","effective"]},
{"Question": "ochlik", "RightAnswer": "hunger", "options": ["gift","false","examine"]},
{"Question": "tasavvur qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "imagine", "options": ["hunger","gift","false"]},
{"Question": "sayohat", "RightAnswer": "journey", "options": ["imagine","hunger","gift"]},
{"Question": "jumboq", "RightAnswer": "puzzle", "options": ["journey","imagine","hunger"]},
{"Question": "biroz ancha", "RightAnswer": "quite", "options": ["puzzle","journey","imagine"]},
{"Question": "maqul ko'rmoq", "RightAnswer": "rather", "options": ["quite","puzzle","journey"]},
{"Question": "o'ziga xos", "RightAnswer": "specific", "options": ["rather","quite","puzzle"]},
{"Question": "sayohat", "RightAnswer": "tour", "options": ["specific","rather","quite"]},
{"Question": "safar", "RightAnswer": "trip", "options": ["tour","specific","rather"]},
{"Question": "qiymat", "RightAnswer": "value", "options": ["trip","tour","specific"]}],	
"level 28" : [
    {"Question": "musiqiy guruh", "RightAnswer": "band", "options": ["value","trip","tour"]},
{"Question": "zo'rg'a", "RightAnswer": "barely", "options": ["band","value","trip"]},
{"Question": "zerikarli", "RightAnswer": "boring", "options": ["barely","band","value"]},
{"Question": "bekor qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "cancel", "options": ["boring","barely","band"]},
{"Question": "yo'lak", "RightAnswer": "driveway", "options": ["cancel","boring","barely"]},
{"Question": "axlat", "RightAnswer": "garbage", "options": ["driveway","cancel","boring"]},
{"Question": "asbob", "RightAnswer": "instrument", "options": ["garbage","driveway","cancel"]},
{"Question": "ro'yxat", "RightAnswer": "list", "options": ["instrument","garbage","driveway"]},
{"Question": "sehrli", "RightAnswer": "magic", "options": ["list","instrument","garbage"]},
{"Question": "xabar", "RightAnswer": "message", "options": ["magic","list","instrument"]},
{"Question": "payqamoq", "RightAnswer": "notice", "options": ["message","magic","list"]},
{"Question": "ega bo'lmoq", "RightAnswer": "own", "options": ["notice","message","magic"]},
{"Question": "taxmin qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "predict", "options": ["own","notice","message"]},
{"Question": "professor", "RightAnswer": "professor", "options": ["predict","own","notice"]},
{"Question": "shoshilmoq", "RightAnswer": "rush", "options": ["professor","predict","own"]},
{"Question": "jadval", "RightAnswer": "schedule", "options": ["rush","professor","predict"]},
{"Question": "ulashmoq", "RightAnswer": "share", "options": ["schedule","rush","professor"]},
{"Question": "bosqich", "RightAnswer": "stage", "options": ["share","schedule","rush"]},
{"Question": "bo'ron", "RightAnswer": "storm", "options": ["stage","share","schedule"]},
{"Question": "ichida", "RightAnswer": "within", "options": ["storm","stage","share"]}],	
"level 29" : [
    {"Question": "reklama qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "advertise", "options": ["within","storm","stage"]},
{"Question": "tayinlamoq", "RightAnswer": "assign", "options": ["advertise","within","storm"]},
{"Question": "tomoshabin", "RightAnswer": "audience", "options": ["assign","advertise","within"]},
{"Question": "nonushta", "RightAnswer": "breakfast", "options": ["audience","assign","advertise"]},
{"Question": "musobaqa", "RightAnswer": "competition", "options": ["breakfast","audience","assign"]},
{"Question": "salqin, ajoyib", "RightAnswer": "cool", "options": ["competition","breakfast","audience"]},
{"Question": "erishmoq, ega bo'lmoq", "RightAnswer": "gain", "options": ["cool","competition","breakfast"]},
{"Question": "ahamiyat", "RightAnswer": "importance", "options": ["gain","cool","competition"]},
{"Question": "bilim", "RightAnswer": "knowledge", "options": ["importance","gain","cool"]},
{"Question": "katta", "RightAnswer": "major", "options": ["knowledge","importance","gain"]},
{"Question": "anglatmoq", "RightAnswer": "mean", "options": ["major","knowledge","importance"]},
{"Question": "afzal ko'rmoq", "RightAnswer": "prefer", "options": ["mean","major","knowledge"]},
{"Question": "prezident", "RightAnswer": "president", "options": ["prefer","mean","major"]},
{"Question": "taraqqiyot", "RightAnswer": "progress", "options": ["president","prefer","mean"]},
{"Question": "hurmat", "RightAnswer": "respect", "options": ["progress","president","prefer"]},
{"Question": "boy", "RightAnswer": "rich", "options": ["respect","progress","president"]},
{"Question": "qobiliyat", "RightAnswer": "skill", "options": ["rich","respect","progress"]},
{"Question": "qandaydir yo'l bilan", "RightAnswer": "somehow", "options": ["skill","rich","respect"]},
{"Question": "kuch-quvvat", "RightAnswer": "strength", "options": ["somehow","skill","rich"]},
{"Question": "ovoz bermoq", "RightAnswer": "vote", "options": ["strength","somehow","skill"]}],	
"level 30" : [
    {"Question": "yuqorida", "RightAnswer": "above", "options": ["vote","strength","somehow"]},
{"Question": "oldinga", "RightAnswer": "ahead", "options": ["above","vote","strength"]},
{"Question": "miqdor", "RightAnswer": "amount", "options": ["ahead","above","vote"]},
{"Question": "e'tiqod", "RightAnswer": "belief", "options": ["amount","ahead","above"]},
{"Question": "markaz", "RightAnswer": "center", "options": ["belief","amount","ahead"]},
{"Question": "umumiy", "RightAnswer": "common", "options": ["center","belief","amount"]},
{"Question": "xarajat", "RightAnswer": "cost", "options": ["common","center","belief"]},
{"Question": "namoyish qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "demonstrate", "options": ["cost","common","center"]},
{"Question": "turli", "RightAnswer": "different", "options": ["demonstrate","cost","common"]},
{"Question": "dalillar", "RightAnswer": "evidence", "options": ["different","demonstrate","cost"]},
{"Question": "halollik", "RightAnswer": "honesty", "options": ["evidence","different","demonstrate"]},
{"Question": "ibora", "RightAnswer": "idiom", "options": ["honesty","evidence","different"]},
{"Question": "mustaqil", "RightAnswer": "independent", "options": ["idiom","honesty","evidence"]},
{"Question": "ichida", "RightAnswer": "inside", "options": ["independent","idiom","honesty"]},
{"Question": "usta", "RightAnswer": "master", "options": ["inside","independent","idiom"]},
{"Question": "xotira", "RightAnswer": "memory", "options": ["master","inside","independent"]},
{"Question": "to'g'ri", "RightAnswer": "proper", "options": ["memory","master","inside"]},
{"Question": "ko'rmoq", "RightAnswer": "scan", "options": ["proper","memory","master"]},
{"Question": "bo'lim", "RightAnswer": "section", "options": ["scan","proper","memory"]},
{"Question": "sirt", "RightAnswer": "surface", "options": ["section","scan","proper"]}],	
"level 31" : [
    {"Question": "tashvishli", "RightAnswer": "anxious", "options": ["surface","section","scan"]},
{"Question": "dahshatli", "RightAnswer": "awful", "options": ["anxious","surface","section"]},
{"Question": "tashkil topmoq", "RightAnswer": "consist", "options": ["awful","anxious","surface"]},
{"Question": "xohmoq", "RightAnswer": "desire", "options": ["consist","awful","anxious"]},
{"Question": "ishtiyoqmand", "RightAnswer": "eager", "options": ["desire","consist","awful"]},
{"Question": "uy-joy", "RightAnswer": "household", "options": ["eager","desire","consist"]},
{"Question": "niyat", "RightAnswer": "intent", "options": ["household","eager","desire"]},
{"Question": "manzara", "RightAnswer": "landscape", "options": ["intent","household","eager"]},
{"Question": "ko'tarmoq", "RightAnswer": "lift", "options": ["landscape","intent","household"]},
{"Question": "yuk", "RightAnswer": "load", "options": ["lift","landscape","intent"]},
{"Question": "o'pka", "RightAnswer": "lung", "options": ["load","lift","landscape"]},
{"Question": "harakat", "RightAnswer": "motion", "options": ["lung","load","lift"]},
{"Question": "tezligi", "RightAnswer": "pace", "options": ["motion","lung","load"]},
{"Question": "muloyim", "RightAnswer": "polite", "options": ["pace","motion","lung"]},
{"Question": "ega bo'lmoq", "RightAnswer": "possess", "options": ["polite","pace","motion"]},
{"Question": "tezda", "RightAnswer": "rapidly", "options": ["possess","polite","pace"]},
{"Question": "eslatma", "RightAnswer": "remark", "options": ["rapidly","possess","polite"]},
{"Question": "izlash", "RightAnswer": "seek", "options": ["remark","rapidly","possess"]},
{"Question": "porlash", "RightAnswer": "shine", "options": ["seek","remark","rapidly"]},
{"Question": "to'kmoq", "RightAnswer": "spill", "options": ["shine","seek","remark"]}],	
"level 32" : [
    {"Question": "olib kelmoq", "RightAnswer": "bring", "options": ["spill","shine","seek"]},
{"Question": "qal'a", "RightAnswer": "castle", "options": ["bring","spill","shine"]},
{"Question": "buyruq bermoq", "RightAnswer": "command", "options": ["castle","bring","spill"]},
{"Question": "maslahat bermoq", "RightAnswer": "counsel", "options": ["command","castle","bring"]},
{"Question": "ishonch xosil qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "ensure", "options": ["counsel","command","castle"]},
{"Question": "portlash", "RightAnswer": "explosion", "options": ["ensure","counsel","command"]},
{"Question": "zargarlik buyumlari", "RightAnswer": "jewelry", "options": ["explosion","ensure","counsel"]},
{"Question": "yer", "RightAnswer": "land", "options": ["jewelry","explosion","ensure"]},
{"Question": "meteor", "RightAnswer": "meteor", "options": ["land","jewelry","explosion"]},
{"Question": "mahluq", "RightAnswer": "monster", "options": ["meteor","land","jewelry"]},
{"Question": "shimoliy", "RightAnswer": "northern", "options": ["monster","meteor","land"]},
{"Question": "uzoq", "RightAnswer": "remote", "options": ["northern","monster","meteor"]},
{"Question": "Janubiy", "RightAnswer": "southern", "options": ["remote","northern","monster"]},
{"Question": "haykal", "RightAnswer": "statue", "options": ["southern","remote","northern"]},
{"Question": "bug '", "RightAnswer": "steam", "options": ["statue","southern","remote"]},
{"Question": "taqdim etmoq, amal qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "submit", "options": ["steam","statue","southern"]},
{"Question": "ibodatxona", "RightAnswer": "temple", "options": ["submit","steam","statue"]},
{"Question": "yuqori", "RightAnswer": "upper", "options": ["temple","submit","steam"]},
{"Question": "o't", "RightAnswer": "weed", "options": ["upper","temple","submit"]},
{"Question": "qanot", "RightAnswer": "wing", "options": ["weed","upper","temple"]}],	
"level 33" : [
    {"Question": "o'q", "RightAnswer": "arrow", "options": ["wing","weed","upper"]},
{"Question": "jang", "RightAnswer": "battle", "options": ["arrow","wing","weed"]},
{"Question": "kamon", "RightAnswer": "bow", "options": ["battle","arrow","wing"]},
{"Question": "jasur", "RightAnswer": "brave", "options": ["bow","battle","arrow"]},
{"Question": "boshliq", "RightAnswer": "chief", "options": ["brave","bow","battle"]},
{"Question": "zararli tomoni", "RightAnswer": "disadvantage", "options": ["chief","brave","bow"]},
{"Question": "dushman", "RightAnswer": "enemy", "options": ["disadvantage","chief","brave"]},
{"Question": "Kirmoq", "RightAnswer": "entrance", "options": ["enemy","disadvantage","chief"]},
{"Question": "kamdan-kam", "RightAnswer": "hardly", "options": ["entrance","enemy","disadvantage"]},
{"Question": "niyat qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "intend", "options": ["hardly","entrance","enemy"]},
{"Question": "kulgu", "RightAnswer": "laughter", "options": ["intend","hardly","entrance"]},
{"Question": "jurnal, yog'och", "RightAnswer": "log", "options": ["laughter","intend","hardly"]},
{"Question": "harbiy", "RightAnswer": "military", "options": ["log","laughter","intend"]},
{"Question": "itoat qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "obey", "options": ["military","log","laughter"]},
{"Question": "xavfsiz, qo'lga kiritmoq", "RightAnswer": "secure", "options": ["obey","military","log"]},
{"Question": "barqaror", "RightAnswer": "steady", "options": ["secure","obey","military"]},
{"Question": "ishonch", "RightAnswer": "trust", "options": ["steady","secure","obey"]},
{"Question": "o'ramoq", "RightAnswer": "twist", "options": ["trust","steady","secure"]},
{"Question": "agar …masa", "RightAnswer": "unless", "options": ["twist","trust","steady"]},
{"Question": "qurol", "RightAnswer": "weapon", "options": ["unless","twist","trust"]}],	
"level 34" : [
    {"Question": "ko'krak", "RightAnswer": "chest", "options": ["weapon","unless","twist"]},
{"Question": "ishonch", "RightAnswer": "confidence", "options": ["chest","weapon","unless"]},
{"Question": "oqibat natija", "RightAnswer": "consequence", "options": ["confidence","chest","weapon"]},
{"Question": "falokat", "RightAnswer": "disaster", "options": ["consequence","confidence","chest"]},
{"Question": "bezovta qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "disturb", "options": ["disaster","consequence","confidence"]},
{"Question": "baholamoq", "RightAnswer": "estimate", "options": ["disturb","disaster","consequence"]},
{"Question": "hurmat, sharaf", "RightAnswer": "honor", "options": ["estimate","disturb","disaster"]},
{"Question": "taassurot qoldirmoq", "RightAnswer": "impress", "options": ["honor","estimate","disturb"]},
{"Question": "marafon", "RightAnswer": "marathon", "options": ["impress","honor","estimate"]},
{"Question": "tor", "RightAnswer": "narrow", "options": ["marathon","impress","honor"]},
{"Question": "rangsiz", "RightAnswer": "pale", "options": ["narrow","marathon","impress"]},
{"Question": "qo'pol", "RightAnswer": "rough", "options": ["pale","narrow","marathon"]},
{"Question": "qoniqtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "satisfy", "options": ["rough","pale","narrow"]},
{"Question": "qichqirmoq", "RightAnswer": "scream", "options": ["satisfy","rough","pale"]},
{"Question": "tasirchan", "RightAnswer": "sensitive", "options": ["scream","satisfy","rough"]},
{"Question": "soya", "RightAnswer": "shade", "options": ["sensitive","scream","satisfy"]},
{"Question": "qo'shimcha", "RightAnswer": "supplement", "options": ["shade","sensitive","scream"]},
{"Question": "daxshat", "RightAnswer": "terror", "options": ["supplement","shade","sensitive"]},
{"Question": "tahdid", "RightAnswer": "threat", "options": ["terror","supplement","shade"]},
{"Question": "qurbon", "RightAnswer": "victim", "options": ["threat","terror","supplement"]}],	
"level 35" : [
    {"Question": "ajdod", "RightAnswer": "ancestor", "options": ["victim","threat","terror"]},
{"Question": "burchak", "RightAnswer": "angle", "options": ["ancestor","victim","threat"]},
{"Question": "yuklash", "RightAnswer": "boot", "options": ["angle","ancestor","victim"]},
{"Question": "chegara", "RightAnswer": "border", "options": ["boot","angle","ancestor"]},
{"Question": "tabriklamoq", "RightAnswer": "congratulate", "options": ["border","boot","angle"]},
{"Question": "ramka", "RightAnswer": "frame", "options": ["congratulate","border","boot"]},
{"Question": "jannat", "RightAnswer": "heaven", "options": ["frame","congratulate","border"]},
{"Question": "ajoyib", "RightAnswer": "incredible", "options": ["heaven","frame","congratulate"]},
{"Question": "afsona", "RightAnswer": "legend", "options": ["incredible","heaven","frame"]},
{"Question": "maqtamoq", "RightAnswer": "praise", "options": ["legend","incredible","heaven"]},
{"Question": "davom etmoq", "RightAnswer": "proceed", "options": ["praise","legend","incredible"]},
{"Question": "sof, toza", "RightAnswer": "pure", "options": ["proceed","praise","legend"]},
{"Question": "nisbiy, qarindosh", "RightAnswer": "relative", "options": ["pure","proceed","praise"]},
{"Question": "katta", "RightAnswer": "senior", "options": ["relative","pure","proceed"]},
{"Question": "jim, tinch", "RightAnswer": "silent", "options": ["senior","relative","pure"]},
{"Question": "cho'kmoq", "RightAnswer": "sink", "options": ["silent","senior","relative"]},
{"Question": "ustun, katta", "RightAnswer": "superior", "options": ["sink","silent","senior"]},
{"Question": "o'rab olmoq", "RightAnswer": "surround", "options": ["superior","sink","silent"]},
{"Question": "qalin", "RightAnswer": "thick", "options": ["surround","superior","sink"]},
{"Question": "o'ramoq", "RightAnswer": "wrap", "options": ["thick","surround","superior"]}],	
"level 36" : [
    {"Question": "chet el", "RightAnswer": "abroad", "options": ["wrap","thick","surround"]},
{"Question": "g'azab", "RightAnswer": "anger", "options": ["abroad","wrap","thick"]},
{"Question": "kelin", "RightAnswer": "bride", "options": ["anger","abroad","wrap"]},
{"Question": "qisqacha", "RightAnswer": "brief", "options": ["bride","anger","abroad"]},
{"Question": "ketidan quvmoq", "RightAnswer": "chase", "options": ["brief","bride","anger"]},
{"Question": "ko'nglini qoldirmoq", "RightAnswer": "disappoint", "options": ["chase","brief","bride"]},
{"Question": "sho'ng'imoq", "RightAnswer": "dive", "options": ["disappoint","chase","brief"]},
{"Question": "almashtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "exchange", "options": ["dive","disappoint","chase"]},
{"Question": "yaxshilik", "RightAnswer": "favor", "options": ["exchange","dive","disappoint"]},
{"Question": "haq", "RightAnswer": "fee", "options": ["favor","exchange","dive"]},
{"Question": "abadiy", "RightAnswer": "forever", "options": ["fee","favor","exchange"]},
{"Question": "yigit", "RightAnswer": "guy", "options": ["forever","fee","favor"]},
{"Question": "ajoyib", "RightAnswer": "lovely", "options": ["guy","forever","fee"]},
{"Question": "kayfiyat", "RightAnswer": "mood", "options": ["lovely","guy","forever"]},
{"Question": "saroy", "RightAnswer": "palace", "options": ["mood","lovely","guy"]},
{"Question": "ruxsat bermoq", "RightAnswer": "permit", "options": ["palace","mood","lovely"]},
{"Question": "norozilik qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "protest", "options": ["permit","palace","mood"]},
{"Question": "haykal", "RightAnswer": "sculpture", "options": ["protest","permit","palace"]},
{"Question": "qabila", "RightAnswer": "tribe", "options": ["sculpture","protest","permit"]},
{"Question": "yoshlar", "RightAnswer": "youth", "options": ["tribe","sculpture","protest"]}],	
"level 37" : [
    {"Question": "asos", "RightAnswer": "basis", "options": ["youth","tribe","sculpture"]},
{"Question": "biologiya", "RightAnswer": "biology", "options": ["basis","youth","tribe"]},
{"Question": "qafas", "RightAnswer": "cage", "options": ["biology","basis","youth"]},
{"Question": "hamkasb", "RightAnswer": "colleague", "options": ["cage","biology","basis"]},
{"Question": "koloniya", "RightAnswer": "colony", "options": ["colleague","cage","biology"]},
{"Question": "munozara", "RightAnswer": "debate", "options": ["colony","colleague","cage"]},
{"Question": "ketmoq", "RightAnswer": "depart", "options": ["debate","colony","colleague"]},
{"Question": "tushkunlikka solmoq", "RightAnswer": "depress", "options": ["depart","debate","colony"]},
{"Question": "haqiqiy", "RightAnswer": "factual", "options": ["depress","depart","debate"]},
{"Question": "hayratda qoldirmoq", "RightAnswer": "fascinate", "options": ["factual","depress","depart"]},
{"Question": "missiya", "RightAnswer": "mission", "options": ["fascinate","factual","depress"]},
{"Question": "Shunga qaramay", "RightAnswer": "nevertheless", "options": ["mission","fascinate","factual"]},
{"Question": "istilo kasb", "RightAnswer": "occupation", "options": ["nevertheless","mission","fascinate"]},
{"Question": "dengiz orti", "RightAnswer": "overseas", "options": ["occupation","nevertheless","mission"]},
{"Question": "ishontirmoq", "RightAnswer": "persuade", "options": ["overseas","occupation","nevertheless"]},
{"Question": "yo'nalmoq", "RightAnswer": "route", "options": ["persuade","overseas","occupation"]},
{"Question": "xarobalar", "RightAnswer": "ruins", "options": ["route","persuade","overseas"]},
{"Question": "olim", "RightAnswer": "scholar", "options": ["ruins","route","persuade"]},
{"Question": "muhim", "RightAnswer": "significant", "options": ["scholar","ruins","route"]},
{"Question": "vulqon", "RightAnswer": "volcano", "options": ["significant","scholar","ruins"]}],	
"level 38" : [
    {"Question": "keng", "RightAnswer": "broad", "options": ["volcano","significant","scholar"]},
{"Question": "buta", "RightAnswer": "bush", "options": ["broad","volcano","significant"]},
{"Question": "qobiliyatli", "RightAnswer": "capable", "options": ["bush","broad","volcano"]},
{"Question": "mug'ombirlik qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "cheat", "options": ["capable","bush","broad"]},
{"Question": "fikrni jamlamoq", "RightAnswer": "concentrate", "options": ["cheat","capable","bush"]},
{"Question": "xulosa qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "conclude", "options": ["concentrate","cheat","capable"]},
{"Question": "o'ziga ishongan", "RightAnswer": "confident", "options": ["conclude","concentrate","cheat"]},
{"Question": "sezilarli", "RightAnswer": "considerable", "options": ["confident","conclude","concentrate"]},
{"Question": "yetkazmoq", "RightAnswer": "convey", "options": ["considerable","confident","conclude"]},
{"Question": "aniq", "RightAnswer": "definite", "options": ["convey","considerable","confident"]},
{"Question": "zavq", "RightAnswer": "delight", "options": ["definite","convey","considerable"]},
{"Question": "manzil", "RightAnswer": "destination", "options": ["delight","definite","convey"]},
{"Question": "aytib turmoq", "RightAnswer": "dictate", "options": ["destination","delight","definite"]},
{"Question": "chet qirra", "RightAnswer": "edge", "options": ["dictate","destination","delight"]},
{"Question": "yo'l", "RightAnswer": "path", "options": ["edge","dictate","destination"]},
{"Question": "suyanmoq", "RightAnswer": "resort", "options": ["path","edge","dictate"]},
{"Question": "soya", "RightAnswer": "shadow", "options": ["resort","path","edge"]},
{"Question": "muvaffaqiyatga erishmoq", "RightAnswer": "succeed", "options": ["shadow","resort","path"]},
{"Question": "gumon qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "suspect", "options": ["succeed","shadow","resort"]},
{"Question": "vodiy", "RightAnswer": "valley", "options": ["suspect","succeed","shadow"]}],	
"level 39" : [
    {"Question": "hurmat qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "admire", "options": ["valley","suspect","succeed"]},
{"Question": "yordam", "RightAnswer": "aid", "options": ["admire","valley","suspect"]},
{"Question": "urinish", "RightAnswer": "attempt", "options": ["aid","admire","valley"]},
{"Question": "hokimiyat", "RightAnswer": "authority", "options": ["attempt","aid","admire"]},
{"Question": "poytaxt", "RightAnswer": "capital", "options": ["authority","attempt","aid"]},
{"Question": "hamkorlik qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "cooperate", "options": ["capital","authority","attempt"]},
{"Question": "himoya qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "defend", "options": ["cooperate","capital","authority"]},
{"Question": "vayrongarchilik", "RightAnswer": "destruction", "options": ["defend","cooperate","capital"]},
{"Question": "tartibsizlik", "RightAnswer": "disorder", "options": ["destruction","defend","cooperate"]},
{"Question": "bo'linish", "RightAnswer": "division", "options": ["disorder","destruction","defend"]},
{"Question": "imkon bermoq", "RightAnswer": "enable", "options": ["division","disorder","destruction"]},
{"Question": "ko'nglini qoldirmoq", "RightAnswer": "frustrate", "options": ["enable","division","disorder"]},
{"Question": "boshqarmoq", "RightAnswer": "govern", "options": ["frustrate","enable","division"]},
{"Question": "mo'l", "RightAnswer": "plenty", "options": ["govern","frustrate","enable"]},
{"Question": "xalos qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "relieve", "options": ["plenty","govern","frustrate"]},
{"Question": "obro'", "RightAnswer": "reputation", "options": ["relieve","plenty","govern"]},
{"Question": "qirollik", "RightAnswer": "royal", "options": ["reputation","relieve","plenty"]},
{"Question": "qul", "RightAnswer": "slave", "options": ["royal","reputation","relieve"]},
{"Question": "kurash", "RightAnswer": "struggle", "options": ["slave","royal","reputation"]},
{"Question": "ahmoqona", "RightAnswer": "stupid", "options": ["struggle","slave","royal"]}],	
"level 40" : [
    {"Question": "fuqaro", "RightAnswer": "citizen", "options": ["stupid","struggle","slave"]},
{"Question": "kengash", "RightAnswer": "council", "options": ["citizen","stupid","struggle"]},
{"Question": "e'lon qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "declare", "options": ["council","citizen","stupid"]},
{"Question": "ulkan", "RightAnswer": "enormous", "options": ["declare","council","citizen"]},
{"Question": "noodatiy", "RightAnswer": "extraordinary", "options": ["enormous","declare","council"]},
{"Question": "tuman", "RightAnswer": "fog", "options": ["extraordinary","enormous","declare"]},
{"Question": "dafn marosimi", "RightAnswer": "funeral", "options": ["fog","extraordinary","enormous"]},
{"Question": "ulkan", "RightAnswer": "giant", "options": ["funeral","fog","extraordinary"]},
{"Question": "taassurot", "RightAnswer": "impression", "options": ["giant","funeral","fog"]},
{"Question": "daromadlar", "RightAnswer": "income", "options": ["impression","giant","funeral"]},
{"Question": "telba", "RightAnswer": "mad", "options": ["income","impression","giant"]},
{"Question": "kerak", "RightAnswer": "ought", "options": ["mad","income","impression"]},
{"Question": "qarshilik ko'rsatmoq", "RightAnswer": "resist", "options": ["ought","mad","income"]},
{"Question": "oshkor qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "reveal", "options": ["resist","ought","mad"]},
{"Question": "qutilmoq", "RightAnswer": "rid", "options": ["reveal","resist","ought"]},
{"Question": "qilich", "RightAnswer": "sword", "options": ["rid","reveal","resist"]},
{"Question": "hikoya", "RightAnswer": "tale", "options": ["sword","rid","reveal"]},
{"Question": "tuzoq", "RightAnswer": "trap", "options": ["tale","sword","rid"]},
{"Question": "sud", "RightAnswer": "trial", "options": ["trap","tale","sword"]},
{"Question": "zo'ravon", "RightAnswer": "violent", "options": ["trial","trap","tale"]}],	
"level 41" : [
    {"Question": "ruxsat", "RightAnswer": "admission", "options": ["violent","trial","trap"]},
{"Question": "astronomiya", "RightAnswer": "astronomy", "options": ["admission","violent","trial"]},
{"Question": "ayblamoq", "RightAnswer": "blame", "options": ["astronomy","admission","violent"]},
{"Question": "kimyo", "RightAnswer": "chemistry", "options": ["blame","astronomy","admission"]},
{"Question": "qaramasdan", "RightAnswer": "despite", "options": ["chemistry","blame","astronomy"]},
{"Question": "dinozavr", "RightAnswer": "dinosaur", "options": ["despite","chemistry","blame"]},
{"Question": "ko'rgazma", "RightAnswer": "exhibit", "options": ["dinosaur","despite","chemistry"]},
{"Question": "shuhrat", "RightAnswer": "fame", "options": ["exhibit","dinosaur","despite"]},
{"Question": "ob-havo ma'lumoti", "RightAnswer": "forecast", "options": ["fame","exhibit","dinosaur"]},
{"Question": "daho", "RightAnswer": "genius", "options": ["forecast","fame","exhibit"]},
{"Question": "muloyim", "RightAnswer": "gentle", "options": ["genius","forecast","fame"]},
{"Question": "geografiya", "RightAnswer": "geography", "options": ["gentle","genius","forecast"]},
{"Question": "aralashmoq", "RightAnswer": "interfere", "options": ["geography","gentle","genius"]},
{"Question": "engil", "RightAnswer": "lightly", "options": ["interfere","geography","gentle"]},
{"Question": "asosiy direktor", "RightAnswer": "principal", "options": ["lightly","interfere","geography"]},
{"Question": "qator", "RightAnswer": "row", "options": ["principal","lightly","interfere"]},
{"Question": "tokcha", "RightAnswer": "shelf", "options": ["row","principal","lightly"]},
{"Question": "ataylab", "RightAnswer": "spite", "options": ["shelf","row","principal"]},
{"Question": "ajoyib", "RightAnswer": "super", "options": ["spite","shelf","row"]},
{"Question": "nam", "RightAnswer": "wet", "options": ["super","spite","shelf"]}],	
"level 42" : [
    {"Question": "ozor yetkazmoq", "RightAnswer": "abuse", "options": ["wet","super","spite"]},
{"Question": "qurbi yetmoq", "RightAnswer": "afford", "options": ["abuse","wet","super"]},
{"Question": "pishirmoq", "RightAnswer": "bake", "options": ["afford","abuse","wet"]},
{"Question": "loviya", "RightAnswer": "bean", "options": ["bake","afford","abuse"]},
{"Question": "sham", "RightAnswer": "candle", "options": ["bean","bake","afford"]},
{"Question": "o'zgartirmoq", "RightAnswer": "convert", "options": ["candle","bean","bake"]},
{"Question": "qarz", "RightAnswer": "debt", "options": ["convert","candle","bean"]},
{"Question": "kamaymoq", "RightAnswer": "decrease", "options": ["debt","convert","candle"]},
{"Question": "xato", "RightAnswer": "fault", "options": ["decrease","debt","convert"]},
{"Question": "jamg'arma", "RightAnswer": "fund", "options": ["fault","decrease","debt"]},
{"Question": "saxiy", "RightAnswer": "generous", "options": ["fund","fault","decrease"]},
{"Question": "ingredient", "RightAnswer": "ingredient", "options": ["generous","fund","fault"]},
{"Question": "turib olmoq", "RightAnswer": "insist", "options": ["ingredient","generous","fund"]},
{"Question": "tartibsizlik", "RightAnswer": "mess", "options": ["insist","ingredient","generous"]},
{"Question": "metall", "RightAnswer": "metal", "options": ["mess","insist","ingredient"]},
{"Question": "kuzatmoq", "RightAnswer": "monitor", "options": ["metal","mess","insist"]},
{"Question": "qarshilik ko'rsatmoq", "RightAnswer": "oppose", "options": ["monitor","metal","mess"]},
{"Question": "sust", "RightAnswer": "passive", "options": ["oppose","monitor","metal"]},
{"Question": "miqdor", "RightAnswer": "quantity", "options": ["passive","oppose","monitor"]},
{"Question": "sudga bermoq", "RightAnswer": "sue", "options": ["quantity","passive","oppose"]}],	
"level 43" : [
    {"Question": "tashvish", "RightAnswer": "anxiety", "options": ["sue","quantity","passive"]},
{"Question": "armiya", "RightAnswer": "army", "options": ["anxiety","sue","quantity"]},
{"Question": "milliard", "RightAnswer": "billion", "options": ["army","anxiety","sue"]},
{"Question": "o'ymoq", "RightAnswer": "carve", "options": ["billion","army","anxiety"]},
{"Question": "maslahatlashmoq", "RightAnswer": "consult", "options": ["carve","billion","army"]},
{"Question": "favqulodda holat", "RightAnswer": "emergency", "options": ["consult","carve","billion"]},
{"Question": "boylik omad", "RightAnswer": "fortune", "options": ["emergency","consult","carve"]},
{"Question": "kafolat bermoq", "RightAnswer": "guarantee", "options": ["fortune","emergency","consult"]},
{"Question": "yurmoq", "RightAnswer": "hike", "options": ["guarantee","fortune","emergency"]},
{"Question": "boshlang'ich", "RightAnswer": "initial", "options": ["hike","guarantee","fortune"]},
{"Question": "qizg'in kuchli", "RightAnswer": "intense", "options": ["initial","hike","guarantee"]},
{"Question": "qarz berish", "RightAnswer": "lend", "options": ["intense","initial","hike"]},
{"Question": "cho'qqi", "RightAnswer": "peak", "options": ["lend","intense","initial"]},
{"Question": "ehtimoliy", "RightAnswer": "potential", "options": ["peak","lend","intense"]},
{"Question": "g'urur", "RightAnswer": "pride", "options": ["potential","peak","lend"]},
{"Question": "dalil", "RightAnswer": "proof", "options": ["pride","potential","peak"]},
{"Question": "chiqish", "RightAnswer": "quit", "options": ["proof","pride","potential"]},
{"Question": "aylantirmoq", "RightAnswer": "spin", "options": ["quit","proof","pride"]},
{"Question": "kichik", "RightAnswer": "tiny", "options": ["spin","quit","proof"]},
{"Question": "o'qituvchi", "RightAnswer": "tutor", "options": ["tiny","spin","quit"]}],	
"level 44" : [
    {"Question": "aniq", "RightAnswer": "apparent", "options": ["tutor","tiny","spin"]},
{"Question": "ko'r", "RightAnswer": "blind", "options": ["apparent","tutor","tiny"]},
{"Question": "hisoblmoq", "RightAnswer": "calculate", "options": ["blind","apparent","tutor"]},
{"Question": "suhbat", "RightAnswer": "chat", "options": ["calculate","blind","apparent"]},
{"Question": "ahd qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "commit", "options": ["chat","calculate","blind"]},
{"Question": "tuzmoq", "RightAnswer": "compose", "options": ["commit","chat","calculate"]},
{"Question": "yotoqxona", "RightAnswer": "dormitory", "options": ["compose","commit","chat"]},
{"Question": "holdan toymoq", "RightAnswer": "exhaust", "options": ["dormitory","compose","commit"]},
{"Question": "issiqxona", "RightAnswer": "greenhouse", "options": ["exhaust","dormitory","compose"]},
{"Question": "e'tibor bermaslik", "RightAnswer": "ignore", "options": ["greenhouse","exhaust","dormitory"]},
{"Question": "aniq", "RightAnswer": "obvious", "options": ["ignore","greenhouse","exhaust"]},
{"Question": "fizika", "RightAnswer": "physics", "options": ["obvious","ignore","greenhouse"]},
{"Question": "qism", "RightAnswer": "portion", "options": ["physics","obvious","ignore"]},
{"Question": "Eslatmoq", "RightAnswer": "remind", "options": ["portion","physics","obvious"]},
{"Question": "kotib", "RightAnswer": "secretary", "options": ["remind","portion","physics"]},
{"Question": "jiddiy", "RightAnswer": "severe", "options": ["secretary","remind","portion"]},
{"Question": "iste'dod", "RightAnswer": "talent", "options": ["severe","secretary","remind"]},
{"Question": "maqola", "RightAnswer": "thesis", "options": ["talent","severe","secretary"]},
{"Question": "forma", "RightAnswer": "uniform", "options": ["thesis","talent","severe"]},
{"Question": "ko'rish", "RightAnswer": "vision", "options": ["uniform","thesis","talent"]}],	
"level 45" : [
    {"Question": "shimib olmoq", "RightAnswer": "absorb", "options": ["vision","uniform","thesis"]},
{"Question": "xo'jayin", "RightAnswer": "boss", "options": ["absorb","vision","uniform"]},
{"Question": "Qo'mita", "RightAnswer": "committee", "options": ["boss","absorb","vision"]},
{"Question": "shartnoma", "RightAnswer": "contract", "options": ["committee","boss","absorb"]},
{"Question": "jamoa", "RightAnswer": "crew", "options": ["contract","committee","boss"]},
{"Question": "bag'ishlamoq", "RightAnswer": "devote", "options": ["crew","contract","committee"]},
{"Question": "qazimoq", "RightAnswer": "dig", "options": ["devote","crew","contract"]},
{"Question": "Ovqatlanmoq", "RightAnswer": "dine", "options": ["dig","devote","crew"]},
{"Question": "ehson qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "donate", "options": ["dine","dig","devote"]},
{"Question": "ikki karra", "RightAnswer": "double", "options": ["donate","dine","dig"]},
{"Question": "ko'tarmoq", "RightAnswer": "elevate", "options": ["double","donate","dine"]},
{"Question": "lazzat", "RightAnswer": "flavor", "options": ["elevate","double","donate"]},
{"Question": "asos", "RightAnswer": "foundation", "options": ["flavor","elevate","double"]},
{"Question": "avlod", "RightAnswer": "generation", "options": ["foundation","flavor","elevate"]},
{"Question": "dastak", "RightAnswer": "handle", "options": ["generation","foundation","flavor"]},
{"Question": "qatlam", "RightAnswer": "layer", "options": ["handle","generation","foundation"]},
{"Question": "loy", "RightAnswer": "mud", "options": ["layer","handle","generation"]},
{"Question": "silliq", "RightAnswer": "smooth", "options": ["mud","layer","handle"]},
{"Question": "tuproq", "RightAnswer": "soil", "options": ["smooth","mud","layer"]},
{"Question": "noyob, o'zgacha", "RightAnswer": "unique", "options": ["soil","smooth","mud"]}],	
"level 46" : [
    {"Question": "xujra", "RightAnswer": "chamber", "options": ["unique","soil","smooth"]},
{"Question": "inkor qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "deny", "options": ["chamber","unique","soil"]},
{"Question": "hujjat", "RightAnswer": "document", "options": ["deny","chamber","unique"]},
{"Question": "urg'u bermoq", "RightAnswer": "emphasize", "options": ["document","deny","chamber"]},
{"Question": "isitma", "RightAnswer": "fever", "options": ["emphasize","document","deny"]},
{"Question": "gripp", "RightAnswer": "flu", "options": ["fever","emphasize","document"]},
{"Question": "muzlatmoq", "RightAnswer": "freeze", "options": ["flu","fever","emphasize"]},
{"Question": "imo-ishora", "RightAnswer": "gesture", "options": ["freeze","flu","fever"]},
{"Question": "gapni bo'lmoq", "RightAnswer": "interrupt", "options": ["gesture","freeze","flu"]},
{"Question": "oxirgi", "RightAnswer": "last", "options": ["interrupt","gesture","freeze"]},
{"Question": "o'xshashlik", "RightAnswer": "likeness", "options": ["last","interrupt","gesture"]},
{"Question": "bundan tashqari", "RightAnswer": "moreover", "options": ["likeness","last","interrupt"]},
{"Question": "nazar", "RightAnswer": "perspective", "options": ["moreover","likeness","last"]},
{"Question": "oqilona", "RightAnswer": "rational", "options": ["perspective","moreover","likeness"]},
{"Question": "tiklanmoq", "RightAnswer": "recover", "options": ["rational","perspective","moreover"]},
{"Question": "tayanmoq", "RightAnswer": "rely", "options": ["recover","rational","perspective"]},
{"Question": "zarba", "RightAnswer": "shock", "options": ["rely","recover","rational"]},
{"Question": "uyatchang", "RightAnswer": "shy", "options": ["shock","rely","recover"]},
{"Question": "tikilmoq", "RightAnswer": "stare", "options": ["shy","shock","rely"]},
{"Question": "shunday qilib", "RightAnswer": "thus", "options": ["stare","shy","shock"]}],	
"level 47" : [
    {"Question": "maqsad", "RightAnswer": "aim", "options": ["thus","stare","shy"]},
{"Question": "ulamoq", "RightAnswer": "attach", "options": ["aim","thus","stare"]},
{"Question": "garov bog'lamoq", "RightAnswer": "bet", "options": ["attach","aim","thus"]},
{"Question": "arava", "RightAnswer": "carriage", "options": ["bet","attach","aim"]},
{"Question": "mumtoz", "RightAnswer": "classic", "options": ["carriage","bet","attach"]},
{"Question": "borib kelmoq", "RightAnswer": "commute", "options": ["classic","carriage","bet"]},
{"Question": "tasdiqlamoq", "RightAnswer": "confirm", "options": ["commute","classic","carriage"]},
{"Question": "tanqid qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "criticize", "options": ["confirm","commute","classic"]},
{"Question": "farq qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "differ", "options": ["criticize","confirm","commute"]},
{"Question": "xarajatlar", "RightAnswer": "expense", "options": ["differ","criticize","confirm"]},
{"Question": "rasmiy", "RightAnswer": "formal", "options": ["expense","differ","criticize"]},
{"Question": "balandlik", "RightAnswer": "height", "options": ["formal","expense","differ"]},
{"Question": "ixtiro qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "invent", "options": ["height","formal","expense"]},
{"Question": "kichik", "RightAnswer": "junior", "options": ["invent","height","formal"]},
{"Question": "mehnat", "RightAnswer": "labor", "options": ["junior","invent","height"]},
{"Question": "mexanik", "RightAnswer": "mechanic", "options": ["labor","junior","invent"]},
{"Question": "asosiy", "RightAnswer": "prime", "options": ["mechanic","labor","junior"]},
{"Question": "o'zgarish", "RightAnswer": "shift", "options": ["prime","mechanic","labor"]},
{"Question": "belgi", "RightAnswer": "signal", "options": ["shift","prime","mechanic"]},
{"Question": "samimiy", "RightAnswer": "sincere", "options": ["signal","shift","prime"]}],	
"level 48" : [
    {"Question": "qobiliyat", "RightAnswer": "ability", "options": ["sincere","signal","shift"]},
{"Question": "qishloq xo'jaligi", "RightAnswer": "agriculture", "options": ["ability","sincere","signal"]},
{"Question": "multfilm", "RightAnswer": "cartoon", "options": ["agriculture","ability","sincere"]},
{"Question": "shift", "RightAnswer": "ceiling", "options": ["cartoon","agriculture","ability"]},
{"Question": "ishontirmoq", "RightAnswer": "convince", "options": ["ceiling","cartoon","agriculture"]},
{"Question": "qiziquvchan", "RightAnswer": "curious", "options": ["convince","ceiling","cartoon"]},
{"Question": "kechiktirmoq", "RightAnswer": "delay", "options": ["curious","convince","ceiling"]},
{"Question": "kundalik", "RightAnswer": "diary", "options": ["delay","curious","convince"]},
{"Question": "element", "RightAnswer": "element", "options": ["diary","delay","curious"]},
{"Question": "e'tiqod", "RightAnswer": "faith", "options": ["element","diary","delay"]},
{"Question": "don", "RightAnswer": "grain", "options": ["faith","element","diary"]},
{"Question": "salomlashmoq", "RightAnswer": "greet", "options": ["grain","faith","element"]},
{"Question": "tekshirmoq", "RightAnswer": "investigate", "options": ["greet","grain","faith"]},
{"Question": "quvonch", "RightAnswer": "joy", "options": ["investigate","greet","grain"]},
{"Question": "yorliq", "RightAnswer": "label", "options": ["joy","investigate","greet"]},
{"Question": "rohib", "RightAnswer": "monk", "options": ["label","joy","investigate"]},
{"Question": "g'alati", "RightAnswer": "odd", "options": ["monk","label","joy"]},
{"Question": "to'xtatib turmoq", "RightAnswer": "pause", "options": ["odd","monk","label"]},
{"Question": "ruhoniy", "RightAnswer": "priest", "options": ["pause","odd","monk"]},
{"Question": "kasb", "RightAnswer": "profession", "options": ["priest","pause","odd"]}],	
"level 49" : [
    {"Question": "qabul qilmoq, boqib olmoq", "RightAnswer": "adopt", "options": ["profession","priest","pause"]},
{"Question": "yalinmoq", "RightAnswer": "beg", "options": ["adopt","profession","priest"]},
{"Question": "ortida", "RightAnswer": "beyond", "options": ["beg","adopt","profession"]},
{"Question": "kostyum", "RightAnswer": "costume", "options": ["beyond","beg","adopt"]},
{"Question": "takidlamoq", "RightAnswer": "exclaim", "options": ["costume","beyond","beg"]},
{"Question": "uzaytirmoq", "RightAnswer": "extend", "options": ["exclaim","costume","beyond"]},
{"Question": "ahmoq", "RightAnswer": "fool", "options": ["extend","exclaim","costume"]},
{"Question": "taqiqlamoq", "RightAnswer": "forbid", "options": ["fool","extend","exclaim"]},
{"Question": "tasvirlab bermoq", "RightAnswer": "illustrate", "options": ["forbid","fool","extend"]},
{"Question": "haqiqatdan ham", "RightAnswer": "indeed", "options": ["illustrate","forbid","fool"]},
{"Question": "tushuntirmoq", "RightAnswer": "interpret", "options": ["indeed","illustrate","forbid"]},
{"Question": "muloyimlik bilan", "RightAnswer": "kindly", "options": ["interpret","indeed","illustrate"]},
{"Question": "maqsad", "RightAnswer": "motive", "options": ["kindly","interpret","indeed"]},
{"Question": "uy", "RightAnswer": "nest", "options": ["motive","kindly","interpret"]},
{"Question": "kelib chiqishi", "RightAnswer": "origin", "options": ["nest","motive","kindly"]},
{"Question": "qabulxona", "RightAnswer": "reception", "options": ["origin","nest","motive"]},
{"Question": "rad etmoq", "RightAnswer": "reject", "options": ["reception","origin","nest"]},
{"Question": "sukunat", "RightAnswer": "silence", "options": ["reject","reception","origin"]},
{"Question": "soy", "RightAnswer": "stream", "options": ["silence","reject","reception"]},
{"Question": "ovoz", "RightAnswer": "tone", "options": ["stream","silence","reject"]}],	
"level 50" : [
    {"Question": "bajarmoq", "RightAnswer": "accomplish", "options": ["tone","stream","silence"]},
{"Question": "tasdiqlamoq", "RightAnswer": "approve", "options": ["accomplish","tone","stream"]},
{"Question": "taxminiy", "RightAnswer": "approximate", "options": ["approve","accomplish","tone"]},
{"Question": "to'siq", "RightAnswer": "barrier", "options": ["approximate","approve","accomplish"]},
{"Question": "aniqlamoq", "RightAnswer": "detect", "options": ["barrier","approximate","approve"]},
{"Question": "vazifa", "RightAnswer": "duty", "options": ["detect","barrier","approximate"]},
{"Question": "boshlang'ich", "RightAnswer": "elementary", "options": ["duty","detect","barrier"]},
{"Question": "muvaffaqiyatsizlik", "RightAnswer": "failure", "options": ["elementary","duty","detect"]},
{"Question": "bosqichma-bosqich", "RightAnswer": "gradual", "options": ["failure","elementary","duty"]},
{"Question": "ko'chib keluvchi", "RightAnswer": "immigrant", "options": ["gradual","failure","elementary"]},
{"Question": "kiritmoq", "RightAnswer": "insert", "options": ["immigrant","gradual","failure"]},
{"Question": "tezda", "RightAnswer": "instant", "options": ["insert","immigrant","gradual"]},
{"Question": "qashshoqlik", "RightAnswer": "poverty", "options": ["instant","insert","immigrant"]},
{"Question": "mug'ombirlik qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "pretend", "options": ["poverty","instant","insert"]},
{"Question": "daraja", "RightAnswer": "rank", "options": ["pretend","poverty","instant"]},
{"Question": "tanish", "RightAnswer": "recognition", "options": ["rank","pretend","poverty"]},
{"Question": "muzlatmoq", "RightAnswer": "refrigerate", "options": ["recognition","rank","pretend"]},
{"Question": "ijaraga olmoq", "RightAnswer": "rent", "options": ["refrigerate","recognition","rank"]},
{"Question": "nafaqaga chiqmoq", "RightAnswer": "retire", "options": ["rent","refrigerate","recognition"]},
{"Question": "statistika, raqamlar", "RightAnswer": "statistic", "options": ["retire","rent","refrigerate"]}],	
"level 51" : [
    {"Question": "astronavt", "RightAnswer": "astronaut", "options": ["statistic","retire","rent"]},
{"Question": "uyg'oq", "RightAnswer": "awake", "options": ["astronaut","statistic","retire"]},
{"Question": "jasorat", "RightAnswer": "courage", "options": ["awake","astronaut","statistic"]},
{"Question": "suzmoq", "RightAnswer": "float", "options": ["courage","awake","astronaut"]},
{"Question": "taqdim etmoq", "RightAnswer": "grant", "options": ["float","courage","awake"]},
{"Question": "tortish kuchi", "RightAnswer": "gravity", "options": ["grant","float","courage"]},
{"Question": "qimmatbaho tosh", "RightAnswer": "jewel", "options": ["gravity","grant","float"]},
{"Question": "konchi", "RightAnswer": "miner", "options": ["jewel","gravity","grant"]},
{"Question": "mineral", "RightAnswer": "mineral", "options": ["miner","jewel","gravity"]},
{"Question": "ishtirok etmoq", "RightAnswer": "participate", "options": ["mineral","miner","jewel"]},
{"Question": "ruxsat", "RightAnswer": "permission", "options": ["participate","mineral","miner"]},
{"Question": "quymoq", "RightAnswer": "pour", "options": ["permission","participate","mineral"]},
{"Question": "mavjudlik", "RightAnswer": "presence", "options": ["pour","permission","participate"]},
{"Question": "xom", "RightAnswer": "raw", "options": ["presence","pour","permission"]},
{"Question": "sun'iy yo'ldosh", "RightAnswer": "satellite", "options": ["raw","presence","pour"]},
{"Question": "ko'lam", "RightAnswer": "scale", "options": ["satellite","raw","presence"]},
{"Question": "o'tkazib yuborish", "RightAnswer": "skip", "options": ["scale","satellite","raw"]},
{"Question": "cho'zmoq", "RightAnswer": "stretch", "options": ["skip","scale","satellite"]},
{"Question": "teleskop", "RightAnswer": "telescope", "options": ["stretch","skip","scale"]},
{"Question": "yer osti", "RightAnswer": "underground", "options": ["telescope","stretch","skip"]}],	
"level 52" : [
    {"Question": "ogohlantiruvchi ovoz", "RightAnswer": "alarm", "options": ["underground","telescope","stretch"]},
{"Question": "alohida, ayro", "RightAnswer": "apart", "options": ["alarm","underground","telescope"]},
{"Question": "hibsga olmoq", "RightAnswer": "arrest", "options": ["apart","alarm","underground"]},
{"Question": "mukofot", "RightAnswer": "award", "options": ["arrest","apart","alarm"]},
{"Question": "zot", "RightAnswer": "breed", "options": ["award","arrest","apart"]},
{"Question": "paqir", "RightAnswer": "bucket", "options": ["breed","award","arrest"]},
{"Question": "tanlov", "RightAnswer": "contest", "options": ["bucket","breed","award"]},
{"Question": "aybdor deb topmoq", "RightAnswer": "convict", "options": ["contest","bucket","breed"]},
{"Question": "garaj", "RightAnswer": "garage", "options": ["convict","contest","bucket"]},
{"Question": "jurnalist", "RightAnswer": "journalist", "options": ["garage","convict","contest"]},
{"Question": "it bolasi", "RightAnswer": "pup", "options": ["journalist","garage","convict"]},
{"Question": "mos kelmoq", "RightAnswer": "qualify", "options": ["pup","journalist","garage"]},
{"Question": "ta'mirlamoq", "RightAnswer": "repair", "options": ["qualify","pup","journalist"]},
{"Question": "davom ettirmoq", "RightAnswer": "resume", "options": ["repair","qualify","pup"]},
{"Question": "tunab ketmoq", "RightAnswer": "rob", "options": ["resume","repair","qualify"]},
{"Question": "toyib ketmoq", "RightAnswer": "slip", "options": ["rob","resume","repair"]},
{"Question": "nimagadir", "RightAnswer": "somewhat", "options": ["slip","rob","resume"]},
{"Question": "barqaror", "RightAnswer": "stable", "options": ["somewhat","slip","rob"]},
{"Question": "to'qima, salfetka", "RightAnswer": "tissue", "options": ["stable","somewhat","slip"]},
{"Question": "hovli", "RightAnswer": "yard", "options": ["tissue","stable","somewhat"]}],	
"level 53" : [
    {"Question": "o'xshash", "RightAnswer": "alike", "options": ["yard","tissue","stable"]},
{"Question": "jig'iga tegmoq", "RightAnswer": "annoy", "options": ["alike","yard","tissue"]},
{"Question": "arxitektura", "RightAnswer": "architecture", "options": ["annoy","alike","yard"]},
{"Question": "sun'iy", "RightAnswer": "artificial", "options": ["architecture","annoy","alike"]},
{"Question": "zanjir", "RightAnswer": "chain", "options": ["artificial","architecture","annoy"]},
{"Question": "farqli", "RightAnswer": "distinct", "options": ["chain","artificial","architecture"]},
{"Question": "ajratmoq", "RightAnswer": "distinguish", "options": ["distinct","chain","artificial"]},
{"Question": "chang", "RightAnswer": "dust", "options": ["distinguish","distinct","chain"]},
{"Question": "hayajon", "RightAnswer": "excitement", "options": ["dust","distinguish","distinct"]},
{"Question": "tuzalmoq", "RightAnswer": "heal", "options": ["excitement","dust","distinguish"]},
{"Question": "meros qilib olmoq", "RightAnswer": "inherit", "options": ["heal","excitement","dust"]},
{"Question": "ahloq, odob", "RightAnswer": "manner", "options": ["inherit","heal","excitement"]},
{"Question": "kuchaymoq", "RightAnswer": "mount", "options": ["manner","inherit","heal"]},
{"Question": "tom", "RightAnswer": "roof", "options": ["mount","manner","inherit"]},
{"Question": "kamchilik", "RightAnswer": "shortage", "options": ["roof","mount","manner"]},
{"Question": "qattiq", "RightAnswer": "solid", "options": ["shortage","roof","mount"]},
{"Question": "g'aram", "RightAnswer": "stock", "options": ["solid","shortage","roof"]},
{"Question": "modda", "RightAnswer": "substance", "options": ["stock","solid","shortage"]},
{"Question": "maqbara", "RightAnswer": "tomb", "options": ["substance","stock","solid"]},
{"Question": "yara", "RightAnswer": "wound", "options": ["tomb","substance","stock"]}],	
"level 54" : [
    {"Question": "vanna", "RightAnswer": "bath", "options": ["wound","tomb","substance"]},
{"Question": "bukmoq", "RightAnswer": "bend", "options": ["bath","wound","tomb"]},
{"Question": "chaynamoq", "RightAnswer": "chew", "options": ["bend","bath","wound"]},
{"Question": "nogiron", "RightAnswer": "disabled", "options": ["chew","bend","bath"]},
{"Question": "ajoyib", "RightAnswer": "fantastic", "options": ["disabled","chew","bend"]},
{"Question": "to'qima", "RightAnswer": "fiction", "options": ["fantastic","disabled","chew"]},
{"Question": "bayroq", "RightAnswer": "flag", "options": ["fiction","fantastic","disabled"]},
{"Question": "tekshirmoq", "RightAnswer": "inspect", "options": ["flag","fiction","fantastic"]},
{"Question": "jurnal", "RightAnswer": "journal", "options": ["inspect","flag","fiction"]},
{"Question": "suyuqlik", "RightAnswer": "liquid", "options": ["journal","inspect","flag"]},
{"Question": "ajoyibot", "RightAnswer": "marvel", "options": ["liquid","journal","inspect"]},
{"Question": "ozuqa moddalari", "RightAnswer": "nutrient", "options": ["marvel","liquid","journal"]},
{"Question": "yengib o'tmoq", "RightAnswer": "overcome", "options": ["nutrient","marvel","liquid"]},
{"Question": "eslatmoq", "RightAnswer": "recall", "options": ["overcome","nutrient","marvel"]},
{"Question": "afsuslanmoq", "RightAnswer": "regret", "options": ["recall","overcome","nutrient"]},
{"Question": "ruh", "RightAnswer": "soul", "options": ["regret","recall","overcome"]},
{"Question": "yetarli", "RightAnswer": "sufficient", "options": ["soul","regret","recall"]},
{"Question": "jarrohlik", "RightAnswer": "surgery", "options": ["sufficient","soul","regret"]},
{"Question": "qiyin", "RightAnswer": "tough", "options": ["surgery","sufficient","soul"]},
{"Question": "quvur", "RightAnswer": "tube", "options": ["tough","surgery","sufficient"]}],	
"level 55" : [
    {"Question": "tan olmoq", "RightAnswer": "admit", "options": ["tube","tough","surgery"]},
{"Question": "quti", "RightAnswer": "bin", "options": ["admit","tube","tough"]},
{"Question": "kosa", "RightAnswer": "bowl", "options": ["bin","admit","tube"]},
{"Question": "hujra", "RightAnswer": "cabin", "options": ["bowl","bin","admit"]},
{"Question": "naqd pul", "RightAnswer": "cash", "options": ["cabin","bowl","bin"]},
{"Question": "jinoyatchi", "RightAnswer": "criminal", "options": ["cash","cabin","bowl"]},
{"Question": "o'nlab", "RightAnswer": "dozen", "options": ["criminal","cash","cabin"]},
{"Question": "kattaroq", "RightAnswer": "elder", "options": ["dozen","criminal","cash"]},
{"Question": "yuzga oid", "RightAnswer": "facial", "options": ["elder","dozen","criminal"]},
{"Question": "to'siq", "RightAnswer": "fence", "options": ["facial","elder","dozen"]},
{"Question": "ilhomlantirmoq", "RightAnswer": "inspire", "options": ["fence","facial","elder"]},
{"Question": "biroz", "RightAnswer": "mere", "options": ["inspire","fence","facial"]},
{"Question": "pokiza", "RightAnswer": "neat", "options": ["mere","inspire","fence"]},
{"Question": "vaziyat", "RightAnswer": "occasion", "options": ["neat","mere","inspire"]},
{"Question": "jazo", "RightAnswer": "penalty", "options": ["occasion","neat","mere"]},
{"Question": "qo'pol", "RightAnswer": "rude", "options": ["penalty","occasion","neat"]},
{"Question": "joylashmoq", "RightAnswer": "settle", "options": ["rude","penalty","occasion"]},
{"Question": "transport vositasi", "RightAnswer": "vehicle", "options": ["settle","rude","penalty"]},
{"Question": "hamyon", "RightAnswer": "wallet", "options": ["vehicle","settle","rude"]},
{"Question": "baqirmoq", "RightAnswer": "yell", "options": ["wallet","vehicle","settle"]}],	
"level 56" : [
    {"Question": "ayblamoq", "RightAnswer": "accuse", "options": ["yell","wallet","vehicle"]},
{"Question": "sozlamoq", "RightAnswer": "adjust", "options": ["accuse","yell","wallet"]},
{"Question": "qiziqtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "amuse", "options": ["adjust","accuse","yell"]},
{"Question": "marjon", "RightAnswer": "coral", "options": ["amuse","adjust","accuse"]},
{"Question": "paxta", "RightAnswer": "cotton", "options": ["coral","amuse","adjust"]},
{"Question": "to'qnashmoq", "RightAnswer": "crash", "options": ["cotton","coral","amuse"]},
{"Question": "paluba", "RightAnswer": "deck", "options": ["crash","cotton","coral"]},
{"Question": "jalb qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "engage", "options": ["deck","crash","cotton"]},
{"Question": "qattiq, firma", "RightAnswer": "firm", "options": ["engage","deck","crash"]},
{"Question": "yoqilg'i", "RightAnswer": "fuel", "options": ["firm","engage","deck"]},
{"Question": "katta", "RightAnswer": "grand", "options": ["fuel","firm","engage"]},
{"Question": "bo'ron", "RightAnswer": "hurricane", "options": ["grand","fuel","firm"]},
{"Question": "yo'qotish", "RightAnswer": "loss", "options": ["hurricane","grand","fuel"]},
{"Question": "tekis", "RightAnswer": "plain", "options": ["loss","hurricane","grand"]},
{"Question": "qoya", "RightAnswer": "reef", "options": ["plain","loss","hurricane"]},
{"Question": "yopish", "RightAnswer": "shut", "options": ["reef","plain","loss"]},
{"Question": "qat'iy", "RightAnswer": "strict", "options": ["shut","reef","plain"]},
{"Question": "to'lqinda uchmoq", "RightAnswer": "surf", "options": ["strict","shut","reef"]},
{"Question": "vazifa", "RightAnswer": "task", "options": ["surf","strict","shut"]},
{"Question": "zona, hudud", "RightAnswer": "zone", "options": ["task","surf","strict"]}],	
"level 57" : [
    {"Question": "kechirim so'rash", "RightAnswer": "apology", "options": ["zone","task","surf"]},
{"Question": "botir", "RightAnswer": "bold", "options": ["apology","zone","task"]},
{"Question": "tutmoq", "RightAnswer": "capture", "options": ["bold","apology","zone"]},
{"Question": "asosiy", "RightAnswer": "cardinal", "options": ["capture","bold","apology"]},
{"Question": "gersog", "RightAnswer": "duke", "options": ["cardinal","capture","bold"]},
{"Question": "ta'sir ostida bo'lmoq", "RightAnswer": "expose", "options": ["duke","cardinal","capture"]},
{"Question": "aybdor", "RightAnswer": "guilty", "options": ["expose","duke","cardinal"]},
{"Question": "ijaraga olmoq", "RightAnswer": "hire", "options": ["guilty","expose","duke"]},
{"Question": "begunoh", "RightAnswer": "innocent", "options": ["hire","guilty","expose"]},
{"Question": "qamoqxona", "RightAnswer": "jail", "options": ["innocent","hire","guilty"]},
{"Question": "vazir", "RightAnswer": "minister", "options": ["jail","innocent","hire"]},
{"Question": "oddiy", "RightAnswer": "ordinary", "options": ["minister","jail","innocent"]},
{"Question": "doimiy", "RightAnswer": "permanent", "options": ["ordinary","minister","jail"]},
{"Question": "himoya qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "preserve", "options": ["permanent","ordinary","minister"]},
{"Question": "talaffuz qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "pronounce", "options": ["preserve","permanent","ordinary"]},
{"Question": "aks etmoq", "RightAnswer": "resemble", "options": ["pronounce","preserve","permanent"]},
{"Question": "belgi", "RightAnswer": "symptom", "options": ["resemble","pronounce","preserve"]},
{"Question": "tamaki", "RightAnswer": "tobacco", "options": ["symptom","resemble","pronounce"]},
{"Question": "egizak", "RightAnswer": "twin", "options": ["tobacco","symptom","resemble"]},
{"Question": "jodugar", "RightAnswer": "witch", "options": ["twin","tobacco","symptom"]}],	
"level 58" : [
    {"Question": "hamroh bo'lmoq", "RightAnswer": "accompany", "options": ["witch","twin","tobacco"]},
{"Question": "yalang'och", "RightAnswer": "bare", "options": ["accompany","witch","twin"]},
{"Question": "shox", "RightAnswer": "branch", "options": ["bare","accompany","witch"]},
{"Question": "nafas olish", "RightAnswer": "breath", "options": ["branch","bare","accompany"]},
{"Question": "ko'prik", "RightAnswer": "bridge", "options": ["breath","branch","bare"]},
{"Question": "uloqtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "cast", "options": ["bridge","breath","branch"]},
{"Question": "jazm qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "dare", "options": ["cast","bridge","breath"]},
{"Question": "elektron", "RightAnswer": "electronic", "options": ["dare","cast","bridge"]},
{"Question": "kichik mehmonxona", "RightAnswer": "inn", "options": ["electronic","dare","cast"]},
{"Question": "to'r", "RightAnswer": "net", "options": ["inn","electronic","dare"]},
{"Question": "falsafa", "RightAnswer": "philosophy", "options": ["net","inn","electronic"]},
{"Question": "qozon", "RightAnswer": "pot", "options": ["philosophy","net","inn"]},
{"Question": "urug'", "RightAnswer": "seed", "options": ["pot","philosophy","net"]},
{"Question": "o'tkir", "RightAnswer": "sharp", "options": ["seed","pot","philosophy"]},
{"Question": "tur", "RightAnswer": "sort", "options": ["sharp","seed","pot"]},
{"Question": "ayirmoq", "RightAnswer": "subtract", "options": ["sort","sharp","seed"]},
{"Question": "qattiq", "RightAnswer": "tight", "options": ["subtract","sort","sharp"]},
{"Question": "virtual", "RightAnswer": "virtual", "options": ["tight","subtract","sort"]},
{"Question": "o'lchamoq", "RightAnswer": "weigh", "options": ["virtual","tight","subtract"]},
{"Question": "pichirlamoq", "RightAnswer": "whisper", "options": ["weigh","virtual","tight"]}],	
"level 59" : [
    {"Question": "mavhum", "RightAnswer": "abstract", "options": ["whisper","weigh","virtual"]},
{"Question": "yillik", "RightAnswer": "annual", "options": ["abstract","whisper","weigh"]},
{"Question": "sopol", "RightAnswer": "clay", "options": ["annual","abstract","whisper"]},
{"Question": "mato", "RightAnswer": "cloth", "options": ["clay","annual","abstract"]},
{"Question": "parda", "RightAnswer": "curtain", "options": ["cloth","clay","annual"]},
{"Question": "loyiq", "RightAnswer": "deserve", "options": ["curtain","cloth","clay"]},
{"Question": "pat", "RightAnswer": "feather", "options": ["deserve","curtain","cloth"]},
{"Question": "unumdor", "RightAnswer": "fertile", "options": ["feather","deserve","curtain"]},
{"Question": "suv toshqini", "RightAnswer": "flood", "options": ["fertile","feather","deserve"]},
{"Question": "mebel", "RightAnswer": "furniture", "options": ["flood","fertile","feather"]},
{"Question": "qabr", "RightAnswer": "grave", "options": ["furniture","flood","fertile"]},
{"Question": "ideal", "RightAnswer": "ideal", "options": ["grave","furniture","flood"]},
{"Question": "idrok", "RightAnswer": "intelligence", "options": ["ideal","grave","furniture"]},
{"Question": "shu kunlarda", "RightAnswer": "nowadays", "options": ["intelligence","ideal","grave"]},
{"Question": "olmoq", "RightAnswer": "obtain", "options": ["nowadays","intelligence","ideal"]},
{"Question": "diniy", "RightAnswer": "religious", "options": ["obtain","nowadays","intelligence"]},
{"Question": "ishqiy", "RightAnswer": "romantic", "options": ["religious","obtain","nowadays"]},
{"Question": "qobiq", "RightAnswer": "shell", "options": ["romantic","religious","obtain"]},
{"Question": "qirg'oq", "RightAnswer": "shore", "options": ["shell","romantic","religious"]},
{"Question": "g'ildirak", "RightAnswer": "wheel", "options": ["shore","shell","romantic"]}],	
"level 60" : [
    {"Question": "o'ziga tortmoq", "RightAnswer": "appeal", "options": ["wheel","shore","shell"]},
{"Question": "faraz qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "assume", "options": ["appeal","wheel","shore"]},
{"Question": "qarz olmoq", "RightAnswer": "borrow", "options": ["assume","appeal","wheel"]},
{"Question": "mijoz", "RightAnswer": "client", "options": ["borrow","assume","appeal"]},
{"Question": "shahar markazi", "RightAnswer": "downtown", "options": ["client","borrow","assume"]},
{"Question": "zerikarli", "RightAnswer": "dull", "options": ["downtown","client","borrow"]},
{"Question": "uyatga qildirmoq", "RightAnswer": "embarrass", "options": ["dull","downtown","client"]},
{"Question": "haq, to'lov", "RightAnswer": "fare", "options": ["embarrass","dull","downtown"]},
{"Question": "sobiq", "RightAnswer": "former", "options": ["fare","embarrass","dull"]},
{"Question": "formula", "RightAnswer": "formula", "options": ["former","fare","embarrass"]},
{"Question": "tashkil qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "found", "options": ["formula","former","fare"]},
{"Question": "sarmoya tikmoq", "RightAnswer": "invest", "options": ["found","formula","former"]},
{"Question": "qarz", "RightAnswer": "loan", "options": ["invest","found","formula"]},
{"Question": "amaliy", "RightAnswer": "practical", "options": ["loan","invest","found"]},
{"Question": "chorak", "RightAnswer": "quarter", "options": ["practical","loan","invest"]},
{"Question": "ish haqi", "RightAnswer": "salary", "options": ["quarter","practical","loan"]},
{"Question": "stipendiya", "RightAnswer": "scholarship", "options": ["salary","quarter","practical"]},
{"Question": "vaqtinchalik", "RightAnswer": "temporary", "options": ["scholarship","salary","quarter"]},
{"Question": "xazina", "RightAnswer": "treasure", "options": ["temporary","scholarship","salary"]},
{"Question": "da'vat qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "urge", "options": ["treasure","temporary","scholarship"]}],	
"level 61" : [
    {"Question": "yuzaga kelmoq", "RightAnswer": "arise", "options": ["urge","treasure","temporary"]},
{"Question": "ko'mak beruvchi", "RightAnswer": "benefactor", "options": ["arise","urge","treasure"]},
{"Question": "temirchi", "RightAnswer": "blacksmith", "options": ["benefactor","arise","urge"]},
{"Question": "ochiqqo'l", "RightAnswer": "charitable", "options": ["blacksmith","benefactor","arise"]},
{"Question": "mo'ri", "RightAnswer": "chimney", "options": ["charitable","blacksmith","benefactor"]},
{"Question": "qoplamoq", "RightAnswer": "compensate", "options": ["chimney","charitable","blacksmith"]},
{"Question": "duch kelmoq", "RightAnswer": "encounter", "options": ["compensate","chimney","charitable"]},
{"Question": "oshib ketmoq", "RightAnswer": "exceed", "options": ["encounter","compensate","chimney"]},
{"Question": "shakllantirmoq", "RightAnswer": "forge", "options": ["exceed","encounter","compensate"]},
{"Question": "kamtarin", "RightAnswer": "humble", "options": ["forge","exceed","encounter"]},
{"Question": "temir", "RightAnswer": "iron", "options": ["humble","forge","exceed"]},
{"Question": "narvon", "RightAnswer": "ladder", "options": ["iron","humble","forge"]},
{"Question": "kamtarin", "RightAnswer": "modest", "options": ["ladder","iron","humble"]},
{"Question": "ishg'ol qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "occupy", "options": ["modest","ladder","iron"]},
{"Question": "chaqa", "RightAnswer": "penny", "options": ["occupy","modest","ladder"]},
{"Question": "voizlik qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "preach", "options": ["penny","occupy","modest"]},
{"Question": "yashnamoq", "RightAnswer": "prosper", "options": ["preach","penny","occupy"]},
{"Question": "viloyat", "RightAnswer": "province", "options": ["prosper","preach","penny"]},
{"Question": "mamnuniyat", "RightAnswer": "satisfaction", "options": ["province","prosper","preach"]},
{"Question": "davom ettirmoq", "RightAnswer": "sustain", "options": ["satisfaction","province","prosper"]}],	
"level 62" : [
    {"Question": "ega bo'lmoq", "RightAnswer": "acquire", "options": ["sustain","satisfaction","province"]},
{"Question": "noqulay", "RightAnswer": "awkward", "options": ["acquire","sustain","satisfaction"]},
{"Question": "enaga", "RightAnswer": "caretaker", "options": ["awkward","acquire","sustain"]},
{"Question": "aldamoq", "RightAnswer": "deceive", "options": ["caretaker","awkward","acquire"]},
{"Question": "tushkunlikka solmoq", "RightAnswer": "discourage", "options": ["deceive","caretaker","awkward"]},
{"Question": "soxta", "RightAnswer": "fake", "options": ["discourage","deceive","caretaker"]},
{"Question": "nafrat", "RightAnswer": "hatred", "options": ["fake","discourage","deceive"]},
{"Question": "kulba", "RightAnswer": "hut", "options": ["hatred","fake","discourage"]},
{"Question": "past", "RightAnswer": "inferior", "options": ["hut","hatred","fake"]},
{"Question": "kulba", "RightAnswer": "lodge", "options": ["inferior","hut","hatred"]},
{"Question": "beparvolik qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "neglect", "options": ["lodge","inferior","hut"]},
{"Question": "yangi kelgan", "RightAnswer": "newcomer", "options": ["neglect","lodge","inferior"]},
{"Question": "jinoyat", "RightAnswer": "offense", "options": ["newcomer","neglect","lodge"]},
{"Question": "e'tiborsizlik", "RightAnswer": "overlook", "options": ["offense","newcomer","neglect"]},
{"Question": "qaytarish", "RightAnswer": "repay", "options": ["overlook","offense","newcomer"]},
{"Question": "kulgili", "RightAnswer": "ridiculous", "options": ["repay","overlook","offense"]},
{"Question": "qoniqarli", "RightAnswer": "satisfactory", "options": ["ridiculous","repay","overlook"]},
{"Question": "cho'pon", "RightAnswer": "shepherd", "options": ["satisfactory","ridiculous","repay"]},
{"Question": "oshiqmoq", "RightAnswer": "venture", "options": ["shepherd","satisfactory","ridiculous"]},
{"Question": "bug'doy", "RightAnswer": "wheat", "options": ["venture","shepherd","satisfactory"]}],	
"level 63" : [
    {"Question": "tor ko'cha", "RightAnswer": "alley", "options": ["wheat","venture","shepherd"]},
{"Question": "bolta", "RightAnswer": "ax", "options": ["alley","wheat","venture"]},
{"Question": "dasta, shingil", "RightAnswer": "bunch", "options": ["ax","alley","wheat"]},
{"Question": "majburyat", "RightAnswer": "chore", "options": ["bunch","ax","alley"]},
{"Question": "yaxshi", "RightAnswer": "decent", "options": ["chore","bunch","ax"]},
{"Question": "sharmandalik", "RightAnswer": "disgrace", "options": ["decent","chore","bunch"]},
{"Question": "tirsak", "RightAnswer": "elbow", "options": ["disgrace","decent","chore"]},
{"Question": "minnatdor", "RightAnswer": "grateful", "options": ["elbow","disgrace","decent"]},
{"Question": "jaxlini chiqarmoq", "RightAnswer": "irritate", "options": ["grateful","elbow","disgrace"]},
{"Question": "bola", "RightAnswer": "kid", "options": ["irritate","grateful","elbow"]},
{"Question": "bo'sh, mustahkam emas", "RightAnswer": "loose", "options": ["kid","irritate","grateful"]},
{"Question": "xafa qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "offend", "options": ["loose","kid","irritate"]},
{"Question": "kechki paytda", "RightAnswer": "overnight", "options": ["offend","loose","kid"]},
{"Question": "davom etmoq", "RightAnswer": "persist", "options": ["overnight","offend","loose"]},
{"Question": "qarag'ay", "RightAnswer": "pine", "options": ["persist","overnight","offend"]},
{"Question": "chandiq", "RightAnswer": "scar", "options": ["pine","persist","overnight"]},
{"Question": "hissiyot", "RightAnswer": "sensation", "options": ["scar","pine","persist"]},
{"Question": "chana", "RightAnswer": "sled", "options": ["sensation","scar","pine"]},
{"Question": "masxara qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "tease", "options": ["sled","sensation","scar"]},
{"Question": "shaydo bo'lmoq", "RightAnswer": "valentine", "options": ["tease","sled","sensation"]}],	
"level 64" : [
    {"Question": "gullamoq", "RightAnswer": "bloom", "options": ["valentine","tease","sled"]},
{"Question": "ixcham", "RightAnswer": "compact", "options": ["bloom","valentine","tease"]},
{"Question": "jingala", "RightAnswer": "curl", "options": ["compact","bloom","valentine"]},
{"Question": "parchalanish", "RightAnswer": "decay", "options": ["curl","compact","bloom"]},
{"Question": "shirinlik", "RightAnswer": "dessert", "options": ["decay","curl","compact"]},
{"Question": "botirmoq", "RightAnswer": "dip", "options": ["dessert","decay","curl"]},
{"Question": "uzoq", "RightAnswer": "distant", "options": ["dip","dessert","decay"]},
{"Question": "tutilmoq", "RightAnswer": "eclipse", "options": ["distant","dip","dessert"]},
{"Question": "farishta", "RightAnswer": "fairy", "options": ["eclipse","distant","dip"]},
{"Question": "viqor", "RightAnswer": "grace", "options": ["fairy","eclipse","distant"]},
{"Question": "dam olmoq", "RightAnswer": "leisure", "options": ["grace","fairy","eclipse"]},
{"Question": "insoniyat", "RightAnswer": "mankind", "options": ["leisure","grace","fairy"]},
{"Question": "ehtiros", "RightAnswer": "passion", "options": ["mankind","leisure","grace"]},
{"Question": "yostiq", "RightAnswer": "pillow", "options": ["passion","mankind","leisure"]},
{"Question": "zarba", "RightAnswer": "pulse", "options": ["pillow","passion","mankind"]},
{"Question": "yangilash", "RightAnswer": "refresh", "options": ["pulse","pillow","passion"]},
{"Question": "aksirmoq", "RightAnswer": "sneeze", "options": ["refresh","pulse","pillow"]},
{"Question": "ziravorlar", "RightAnswer": "spice", "options": ["sneeze","refresh","pulse"]},
{"Question": "hushtak", "RightAnswer": "whistle", "options": ["spice","sneeze","refresh"]},
{"Question": "jun", "RightAnswer": "wool", "options": ["whistle","spice","sneeze"]}],	
"level 65" : [
    {"Question": "tanishmoq", "RightAnswer": "acquaint", "options": ["wool","whistle","spice"]},
{"Question": "qabriston", "RightAnswer": "cemetery", "options": ["acquaint","wool","whistle"]},
{"Question": "la'natlamoq", "RightAnswer": "curse", "options": ["cemetery","acquaint","wool"]},
{"Question": "niqob", "RightAnswer": "disguise", "options": ["curse","cemetery","acquaint"]},
{"Question": "noodatiy", "RightAnswer": "fancy", "options": ["disguise","curse","cemetery"]},
{"Question": "chiroq", "RightAnswer": "flashlight", "options": ["fancy","disguise","curse"]},
{"Question": "qalpoq", "RightAnswer": "hood", "options": ["flashlight","fancy","disguise"]},
{"Question": "yashovchi", "RightAnswer": "inhabitant", "options": ["hood","flashlight","fancy"]},
{"Question": "oziqlantirish", "RightAnswer": "nourish", "options": ["inhabitant","hood","flashlight"]},
{"Question": "qaroqchi", "RightAnswer": "pirate", "options": ["nourish","inhabitant","hood"]},
{"Question": "nashr", "RightAnswer": "publication", "options": ["pirate","nourish","inhabitant"]},
{"Question": "topishmoq", "RightAnswer": "riddle", "options": ["publication","pirate","nourish"]},
{"Question": "chirimoq", "RightAnswer": "rot", "options": ["riddle","publication","pirate"]},
{"Question": "qo'rqitmoq", "RightAnswer": "scare", "options": ["rot","riddle","publication"]},
{"Question": "qisqa vaqt ichida", "RightAnswer": "shortly", "options": ["scare","rot","riddle"]},
{"Question": "skelet", "RightAnswer": "skeleton", "options": ["shortly","scare","rot"]},
{"Question": "buzilmoq", "RightAnswer": "spoil", "options": ["skeleton","shortly","scare"]},
{"Question": "och qolmoq", "RightAnswer": "starve", "options": ["spoil","skeleton","shortly"]},
{"Question": "qiziqish", "RightAnswer": "thrill", "options": ["starve","spoil","skeleton"]},
{"Question": "yomon", "RightAnswer": "wicked", "options": ["thrill","starve","spoil"]}],	
"level 66" : [
    {"Question": "ogohlantirmoq", "RightAnswer": "alert", "options": ["wicked","thrill","starve"]},
{"Question": "eshittirish", "RightAnswer": "broadcast", "options": ["alert","wicked","thrill"]},
{"Question": "xabarnoma", "RightAnswer": "bulletin", "options": ["broadcast","alert","wicked"]},
{"Question": "do'ng, bo'rtgan joy", "RightAnswer": "bump", "options": ["bulletin","broadcast","alert"]},
{"Question": "bo'laklamoq", "RightAnswer": "chop", "options": ["bump","bulletin","broadcast"]},
{"Question": "shkaf", "RightAnswer": "closet", "options": ["chop","bump","bulletin"]},
{"Question": "yupatmoq", "RightAnswer": "console", "options": ["closet","chop","bump"]},
{"Question": "tuman", "RightAnswer": "district", "options": ["console","closet","chop"]},
{"Question": "tortma", "RightAnswer": "drawer", "options": ["district","console","closet"]},
{"Question": "chidamoq", "RightAnswer": "endure", "options": ["drawer","district","console"]},
{"Question": "qatl qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "execute", "options": ["endure","drawer","district"]},
{"Question": "mahkam tutmoq", "RightAnswer": "grasp", "options": ["execute","endure","drawer"]},
{"Question": "orqa", "RightAnswer": "rear", "options": ["grasp","execute","endure"]},
{"Question": "senator", "RightAnswer": "senator", "options": ["rear","grasp","execute"]},
{"Question": "bosh suyagi", "RightAnswer": "skull", "options": ["senator","rear","grasp"]},
{"Question": "aralashtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "stir", "options": ["skull","senator","rear"]},
{"Question": "bosmoq", "RightAnswer": "tap", "options": ["stir","skull","senator"]},
{"Question": "ulkan", "RightAnswer": "tremendous", "options": ["tap","stir","skull"]},
{"Question": "ostida", "RightAnswer": "underneath", "options": ["tremendous","tap","stir"]},
{"Question": "qurt", "RightAnswer": "worm", "options": ["underneath","tremendous","tap"]}],	
"level 67" : [
    {"Question": "tark etmoq", "RightAnswer": "abandon", "options": ["worm","underneath","tremendous"]},
{"Question": "shijoatli", "RightAnswer": "ambitious", "options": ["abandon","worm","underneath"]},
{"Question": "vovullamoq", "RightAnswer": "bark", "options": ["ambitious","abandon","worm"]},
{"Question": "qo'ltiq", "RightAnswer": "bay", "options": ["bark","ambitious","abandon"]},
{"Question": "aqilli", "RightAnswer": "brilliant", "options": ["bay","bark","ambitious"]},
{"Question": "jag'", "RightAnswer": "chin", "options": ["brilliant","bay","bark"]},
{"Question": "shikoyat", "RightAnswer": "complaint", "options": ["chin","brilliant","bay"]},
{"Question": "kar", "RightAnswer": "deaf", "options": ["complaint","chin","brilliant"]},
{"Question": "g'ayratli", "RightAnswer": "enthusiastic", "options": ["deaf","complaint","chin"]},
{"Question": "ekspeditsiya", "RightAnswer": "expedition", "options": ["enthusiastic","deaf","complaint"]},
{"Question": "ufq", "RightAnswer": "horizon", "options": ["expedition","enthusiastic","deaf"]},
{"Question": "sodiq", "RightAnswer": "loyal", "options": ["horizon","expedition","enthusiastic"]},
{"Question": "shahar hokimi", "RightAnswer": "mayor", "options": ["loyal","horizon","expedition"]},
{"Question": "o'zaro", "RightAnswer": "mutual", "options": ["mayor","loyal","horizon"]},
{"Question": "semiz", "RightAnswer": "overweight", "options": ["mutual","mayor","loyal"]},
{"Question": "boshpana", "RightAnswer": "refuge", "options": ["overweight","mutual","mayor"]},
{"Question": "tiklash", "RightAnswer": "restore", "options": ["refuge","overweight","mutual"]},
{"Question": "ishqalamoq", "RightAnswer": "rub", "options": ["restore","refuge","overweight"]},
{"Question": "hislar", "RightAnswer": "senses", "options": ["rub","restore","refuge"]},
{"Question": "veterinar", "RightAnswer": "veterinarian", "options": ["senses","rub","restore"]}],	
"level 68" : [
    {"Question": "yilligi", "RightAnswer": "anniversary", "options": ["veterinarian","senses","rub"]},
{"Question": "arifmetik", "RightAnswer": "arithmetic", "options": ["anniversary","veterinarian","senses"]},
{"Question": "uyatli", "RightAnswer": "ashamed", "options": ["arithmetic","anniversary","veterinarian"]},
{"Question": "portlash", "RightAnswer": "burst", "options": ["ashamed","arithmetic","anniversary"]},
{"Question": "duradgor", "RightAnswer": "carpenter", "options": ["burst","ashamed","arithmetic"]},
{"Question": "ko'mir", "RightAnswer": "coal", "options": ["carpenter","burst","ashamed"]},
{"Question": "divan", "RightAnswer": "couch", "options": ["coal","carpenter","burst"]},
{"Question": "tomchilamoq", "RightAnswer": "drip", "options": ["couch","coal","carpenter"]},
{"Question": "bashang", "RightAnswer": "elegant", "options": ["drip","couch","coal"]},
{"Question": "mato", "RightAnswer": "fabric", "options": ["elegant","drip","couch"]},
{"Question": "tog'li hududlar", "RightAnswer": "highlands", "options": ["fabric","elegant","drip"]},
{"Question": "fil suyagi", "RightAnswer": "ivory", "options": ["highlands","fabric","elegant"]},
{"Question": "tegirmon", "RightAnswer": "mill", "options": ["ivory","highlands","fabric"]},
{"Question": "igna", "RightAnswer": "needle", "options": ["mill","ivory","highlands"]},
{"Question": "jilo bermoq", "RightAnswer": "polish", "options": ["needle","mill","ivory"]},
{"Question": "tikmoq", "RightAnswer": "sew", "options": ["polish","needle","mill"]},
{"Question": "omborxona", "RightAnswer": "shed", "options": ["sew","polish","needle"]},
{"Question": "ip", "RightAnswer": "thread", "options": ["shed","sew","polish"]},
{"Question": "tartibga solmoq", "RightAnswer": "trim", "options": ["thread","shed","sew"]},
{"Question": "yuqoriga", "RightAnswer": "upwards", "options": ["trim","thread","shed"]}],	
"level 69" : [
    {"Question": "ozor bermoq", "RightAnswer": "ail", "options": ["upwards","trim","thread"]},
{"Question": "ittifoqchi", "RightAnswer": "ally", "options": ["ail","upwards","trim"]},
{"Question": "maqtanmoq", "RightAnswer": "boast", "options": ["ally","ail","upwards"]},
{"Question": "dukkilamoq", "RightAnswer": "bounce", "options": ["boast","ally","ail"]},
{"Question": "bezori", "RightAnswer": "bully", "options": ["bounce","boast","ally"]},
{"Question": "karbongidrat", "RightAnswer": "carbohydrate", "options": ["bully","bounce","boast"]},
{"Question": "emaklamoq", "RightAnswer": "crawl", "options": ["carbohydrate","bully","bounce"]},
{"Question": "mag'lubiyat", "RightAnswer": "defeat", "options": ["crawl","carbohydrate","bully"]},
{"Question": "terish", "RightAnswer": "dial", "options": ["defeat","crawl","carbohydrate"]},
{"Question": "dominant", "RightAnswer": "dominant", "options": ["dial","defeat","crawl"]},
{"Question": "rahmdillik", "RightAnswer": "mercy", "options": ["dominant","dial","defeat"]},
{"Question": "bosh qimirlatmoq", "RightAnswer": "nod", "options": ["mercy","dominant","dial"]},
{"Question": "raqib", "RightAnswer": "opponent", "options": ["nod","mercy","dominant"]},
{"Question": "janjallashmoq", "RightAnswer": "rival", "options": ["opponent","nod","mercy"]},
{"Question": "raqib", "RightAnswer": "sore", "options": ["rival","opponent","nod"]},
{"Question": "og'riq", "RightAnswer": "sting", "options": ["sore","rival","opponent"]},
{"Question": "nish, chaqmoq", "RightAnswer": "strain", "options": ["sting","sore","rival"]},
{"Question": "tirishmoq", "RightAnswer": "torture", "options": ["strain","sting","sore"]},
{"Question": "qiynoq", "RightAnswer": "wrestle", "options": ["torture","strain","sting"]},
{"Question": "kurashmoq", "RightAnswer": "quarrel", "options": ["wrestle","torture","strain"]}],	
"level 70" : [
    {"Question": "yo'qlik", "RightAnswer": "absence", "options": ["quarrel","wrestle","torture"]},
{"Question": "ovoz chiqarib", "RightAnswer": "aloud", "options": ["absence","quarrel","wrestle"]},
{"Question": "kal", "RightAnswer": "bald", "options": ["aloud","absence","quarrel"]},
{"Question": "ko'rpa", "RightAnswer": "blanket", "options": ["bald","aloud","absence"]},
{"Question": "o'rmalamoq", "RightAnswer": "creep", "options": ["blanket","bald","aloud"]},
{"Question": "ajrashmoq", "RightAnswer": "divorce", "options": ["creep","blanket","bald"]},
{"Question": "taqlid qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "imitate", "options": ["divorce","creep","blanket"]},
{"Question": "chaqaloq", "RightAnswer": "infant", "options": ["imitate","divorce","creep"]},
{"Question": "o'g'irlash", "RightAnswer": "kidnap", "options": ["infant","imitate","divorce"]},
{"Question": "mizg'ish", "RightAnswer": "nap", "options": ["kidnap","infant","imitate"]},
{"Question": "hech qayerda", "RightAnswer": "nowhere", "options": ["nap","kidnap","infant"]},
{"Question": "ohista urmoq", "RightAnswer": "pat", "options": ["nowhere","nap","kidnap"]},
{"Question": "yengillik", "RightAnswer": "relief", "options": ["pat","nowhere","nap"]},
{"Question": "nusxa yasamoq", "RightAnswer": "reproduce", "options": ["relief","pat","nowhere"]},
{"Question": "qofiya", "RightAnswer": "rhyme", "options": ["reproduce","relief","pat"]},
{"Question": "so'rmoq", "RightAnswer": "suck", "options": ["rhyme","reproduce","relief"]},
{"Question": "shoshilinch", "RightAnswer": "urgent", "options": ["suck","rhyme","reproduce"]},
{"Question": "yo'qolmoq", "RightAnswer": "vanish", "options": ["urgent","suck","rhyme"]},
{"Question": "aravacha", "RightAnswer": "wagon", "options": ["vanish","urgent","suck"]},
{"Question": "ajin", "RightAnswer": "wrinkle", "options": ["wagon","vanish","urgent"]}],	
"level 71" : [
    {"Question": "noodatiy", "RightAnswer": "abnormal", "options": ["wrinkle","wagon","vanish"]},
{"Question": "bambuk", "RightAnswer": "bamboo", "options": ["abnormal","wrinkle","wagon"]},
{"Question": "gullamoq", "RightAnswer": "blossom", "options": ["bamboo","abnormal","wrinkle"]},
{"Question": "kompas", "RightAnswer": "compass", "options": ["blossom","bamboo","abnormal"]},
{"Question": "lahja", "RightAnswer": "dialect", "options": ["compass","blossom","bamboo"]},
{"Question": "yolg'onchi", "RightAnswer": "dishonest", "options": ["dialect","compass","blossom"]},
{"Question": "mitti", "RightAnswer": "dwarf", "options": ["dishonest","dialect","compass"]},
{"Question": "ekosistema", "RightAnswer": "ecosystem", "options": ["dwarf","dishonest","dialect"]},
{"Question": "ayanchli", "RightAnswer": "fatal", "options": ["ecosystem","dwarf","dishonest"]},
{"Question": "sabrsiz", "RightAnswer": "impatient", "options": ["fatal","ecosystem","dwarf"]},
{"Question": "yaproq", "RightAnswer": "leaf", "options": ["impatient","fatal","ecosystem"]},
{"Question": "qo'lyozmasi", "RightAnswer": "manuscript", "options": ["leaf","impatient","fatal"]},
{"Question": "yaylov", "RightAnswer": "marsh", "options": ["manuscript","leaf","impatient"]},
{"Question": "sabr-toqat", "RightAnswer": "patience", "options": ["marsh","manuscript","leaf"]},
{"Question": "atir", "RightAnswer": "perfume", "options": ["patience","marsh","manuscript"]},
{"Question": "hovuz", "RightAnswer": "pond", "options": ["perfume","patience","marsh"]},
{"Question": "maqol", "RightAnswer": "proverb", "options": ["pond","perfume","patience"]},
{"Question": "ta'qib qilish", "RightAnswer": "pursuit", "options": ["proverb","pond","perfume"]},
{"Question": "takrorlamoq qaytarmoq", "RightAnswer": "recite", "options": ["pursuit","proverb","pond"]},
{"Question": "biyobon", "RightAnswer": "wilderness", "options": ["recite","pursuit","proverb"]}],	
"level 72" : [
    {"Question": "oldindan bilmoq", "RightAnswer": "anticipate", "options": ["wilderness","recite","pursuit"]},
{"Question": "bochka", "RightAnswer": "barrel", "options": ["anticipate","wilderness","recite"]},
{"Question": "nur", "RightAnswer": "beam", "options": ["barrel","anticipate","wilderness"]},
{"Question": "oddiy", "RightAnswer": "casual", "options": ["beam","barrel","anticipate"]},
{"Question": "ehtiyotkorlik", "RightAnswer": "caution", "options": ["casual","beam","barrel"]},
{"Question": "teskari", "RightAnswer": "contrary", "options": ["caution","casual","beam"]},
{"Question": "qasddan atay", "RightAnswer": "deliberate", "options": ["contrary","caution","casual"]},
{"Question": "suyuqlikda erimoq", "RightAnswer": "dissolve", "options": ["deliberate","contrary","caution"]},
{"Question": "portlamoq", "RightAnswer": "explode", "options": ["dissolve","deliberate","contrary"]},
{"Question": "bog'lamoq", "RightAnswer": "fasten", "options": ["explode","dissolve","deliberate"]},
{"Question": "mikrob", "RightAnswer": "germ", "options": ["fasten","explode","dissolve"]},
{"Question": "to'plam", "RightAnswer": "kit", "options": ["germ","fasten","explode"]},
{"Question": "tutun", "RightAnswer": "puff", "options": ["kit","germ","fasten"]},
{"Question": "latta", "RightAnswer": "rag", "options": ["puff","kit","germ"]},
{"Question": "sochmoq", "RightAnswer": "scatter", "options": ["rag","puff","kit"]},
{"Question": "hid", "RightAnswer": "scent", "options": ["scatter","rag","puff"]},
{"Question": "po'lat", "RightAnswer": "steel", "options": ["scent","scatter","rag"]},
{"Question": "tezkor", "RightAnswer": "swift", "options": ["steel","scent","scatter"]},
{"Question": "otmoq tashlamoq", "RightAnswer": "toss", "options": ["swift","steel","scent"]},
{"Question": "g'alaba", "RightAnswer": "triumph", "options": ["toss","swift","steel"]}],	
"level 73" : [
    {"Question": "bortda", "RightAnswer": "aboard", "options": ["triumph","toss","swift"]},
{"Question": "achchiq", "RightAnswer": "bitter", "options": ["aboard","triumph","toss"]},
{"Question": "o'q", "RightAnswer": "bullet", "options": ["bitter","aboard","triumph"]},
{"Question": "shayton", "RightAnswer": "devil", "options": ["bullet","bitter","aboard"]},
{"Question": "siljimoq", "RightAnswer": "drift", "options": ["devil","bullet","bitter"]},
{"Question": "majburlash", "RightAnswer": "enforce", "options": ["drift","devil","bullet"]},
{"Question": "fontan", "RightAnswer": "fountain", "options": ["enforce","drift","devil"]},
{"Question": "bandargoh", "RightAnswer": "harbor", "options": ["fountain","enforce","drift"]},
{"Question": "yashamoq", "RightAnswer": "inhabit", "options": ["harbor","fountain","enforce"]},
{"Question": "qadam tashlamoq", "RightAnswer": "march", "options": ["inhabit","harbor","fountain"]},
{"Question": "millioner", "RightAnswer": "millionaire", "options": ["march","inhabit","harbor"]},
{"Question": "port", "RightAnswer": "port", "options": ["millionaire","march","inhabit"]},
{"Question": "sherif", "RightAnswer": "sheriff", "options": ["port","millionaire","march"]},
{"Question": "cho'chimoq", "RightAnswer": "startle", "options": ["sheriff","port","millionaire"]},
{"Question": "terlamoq", "RightAnswer": "sweat", "options": ["startle","sheriff","port"]},
{"Question": "tepki", "RightAnswer": "trigger", "options": ["sweat","startle","sheriff"]},
{"Question": "birlashtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "unify", "options": ["trigger","sweat","startle"]},
{"Question": "kema", "RightAnswer": "vessel", "options": ["unify","trigger","sweat"]},
{"Question": "sayohat", "RightAnswer": "voyage", "options": ["vessel","unify","trigger"]},
{"Question": "ibodat qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "worship", "options": ["voyage","vessel","unify"]}],	
"level 74" : [
    {"Question": "shogird", "RightAnswer": "apprentice", "options": ["worship","voyage","vessel"]},
{"Question": "ishontirmoq", "RightAnswer": "assure", "options": ["apprentice","worship","voyage"]},
{"Question": "bint", "RightAnswer": "bandage", "options": ["assure","apprentice","worship"]},
{"Question": "qonamoq", "RightAnswer": "bleed", "options": ["bandage","assure","apprentice"]},
{"Question": "bog'lanmoq", "RightAnswer": "bond", "options": ["bleed","bandage","assure"]},
{"Question": "oshpaz", "RightAnswer": "chef", "options": ["bond","bleed","bandage"]},
{"Question": "toj", "RightAnswer": "crown", "options": ["chef","bond","bleed"]},
{"Question": "ketmoq", "RightAnswer": "departure", "options": ["crown","chef","bond"]},
{"Question": "mehnatsevar", "RightAnswer": "diligent", "options": ["departure","crown","chef"]},
{"Question": "imperator", "RightAnswer": "emperor", "options": ["diligent","departure","crown"]},
{"Question": "tola", "RightAnswer": "fiber", "options": ["emperor","diligent","departure"]},
{"Question": "dahshatli", "RightAnswer": "horrible", "options": ["fiber","emperor","diligent"]},
{"Question": "qo'pol", "RightAnswer": "impolite", "options": ["horrible","fiber","emperor"]},
{"Question": "tizzalamoq", "RightAnswer": "kneel", "options": ["impolite","horrible","fiber"]},
{"Question": "hashamat", "RightAnswer": "luxury", "options": ["kneel","impolite","horrible"]},
{"Question": "katta", "RightAnswer": "massive", "options": ["luxury","kneel","impolite"]},
{"Question": "vahima", "RightAnswer": "panic", "options": ["massive","luxury","kneel"]},
{"Question": "ustuvorlik", "RightAnswer": "priority", "options": ["panic","massive","luxury"]},
{"Question": "xalat", "RightAnswer": "robe", "options": ["priority","panic","massive"]},
{"Question": "tanbeh bermoq", "RightAnswer": "scold", "options": ["robe","priority","panic"]}],	
"level 75" : [
    {"Question": "munosabat", "RightAnswer": "affair", "options": ["scold","robe","priority"]},
{"Question": "yig'ilish", "RightAnswer": "assembly", "options": ["affair","scold","robe"]},
{"Question": "yorlaqamoq", "RightAnswer": "bless", "options": ["assembly","affair","scold"]},
{"Question": "don", "RightAnswer": "cereal", "options": ["bless","assembly","affair"]},
{"Question": "quvnoq", "RightAnswer": "cheerful", "options": ["cereal","bless","assembly"]},
{"Question": "diametr", "RightAnswer": "diameter", "options": ["cheerful","cereal","bless"]},
{"Question": "majburiy ishlatmoq", "RightAnswer": "exploit", "options": ["diameter","cheerful","cereal"]},
{"Question": "ochlik", "RightAnswer": "famine", "options": ["exploit","diameter","cheerful"]},
{"Question": "hosil", "RightAnswer": "harvest", "options": ["famine","exploit","diameter"]},
{"Question": "xushchaqchaq", "RightAnswer": "merry", "options": ["harvest","famine","exploit"]},
{"Question": "yong'oq", "RightAnswer": "nut", "options": ["merry","harvest","famine"]},
{"Question": "afv etish", "RightAnswer": "pardon", "options": ["nut","merry","harvest"]},
{"Question": "Fir'avn", "RightAnswer": "pharaoh", "options": ["pardon","nut","merry"]},
{"Question": "pishgan", "RightAnswer": "ripe", "options": ["pharaoh","pardon","nut"]},
{"Question": "qovurilgan", "RightAnswer": "roast", "options": ["ripe","pharaoh","pardon"]},
{"Question": "muntazam", "RightAnswer": "routine", "options": ["roast","ripe","pharaoh"]},
{"Question": "sxema", "RightAnswer": "scheme", "options": ["routine","roast","ripe"]},
{"Question": "nozik", "RightAnswer": "slim", "options": ["scheme","routine","roast"]},
{"Question": "pechka", "RightAnswer": "stove", "options": ["slim","scheme","routine"]},
{"Question": "o'g'irlik", "RightAnswer": "theft", "options": ["stove","slim","scheme"]}],	
"level 76" : [
    {"Question": "o'smir", "RightAnswer": "adolescent", "options": ["theft","stove","slim"]},
{"Question": "qobiliyat", "RightAnswer": "aptitude", "options": ["adolescent","theft","stove"]},
{"Question": "iltifot", "RightAnswer": "compliment", "options": ["aptitude","adolescent","theft"]},
{"Question": "to'siq qo'yish", "RightAnswer": "hinder", "options": ["compliment","aptitude","adolescent"]},
{"Question": "jurnalistika", "RightAnswer": "journalism", "options": ["hinder","compliment","aptitude"]},
{"Question": "hakamlar hay'ati", "RightAnswer": "jury", "options": ["journalism","hinder","compliment"]},
{"Question": "adolat", "RightAnswer": "justice", "options": ["jury","journalism","hinder"]},
{"Question": "ozodlik", "RightAnswer": "liberty", "options": ["justice","jury","journalism"]},
{"Question": "adabiy", "RightAnswer": "literary", "options": ["liberty","justice","jury"]},
{"Question": "dori darmon", "RightAnswer": "pharmacy", "options": ["literary","liberty","justice"]},
{"Question": "hapdori", "RightAnswer": "pill", "options": ["pharmacy","literary","liberty"]},
{"Question": "taxmin qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "presume", "options": ["pill","pharmacy","literary"]},
{"Question": "maxfiylik", "RightAnswer": "privacy", "options": ["presume","pill","pharmacy"]},
{"Question": "jazo", "RightAnswer": "punishment", "options": ["privacy","presume","pill"]},
{"Question": "aqlli", "RightAnswer": "sensible", "options": ["punishment","privacy","presume"]},
{"Question": "tilim", "RightAnswer": "slice", "options": ["sensible","punishment","privacy"]},
{"Question": "qayg'u", "RightAnswer": "sorrow", "options": ["slice","sensible","punishment"]},
{"Question": "somon", "RightAnswer": "straw", "options": ["sorrow","slice","sensible"]},
{"Question": "shishmoq", "RightAnswer": "swell", "options": ["straw","sorrow","slice"]},
{"Question": "toza", "RightAnswer": "tidy", "options": ["swell","straw","sorrow"]}],	
"level 77" : [
    {"Question": "muhabbat", "RightAnswer": "affection", "options": ["tidy","swell","straw"]},
{"Question": "agentlik", "RightAnswer": "agency", "options": ["affection","tidy","swell"]},
{"Question": "kul", "RightAnswer": "ash", "options": ["agency","affection","tidy"]},
{"Question": "saqlamoq", "RightAnswer": "confine", "options": ["ash","agency","affection"]},
{"Question": "olib tashlamoq", "RightAnswer": "dismiss", "options": ["confine","ash","agency"]},
{"Question": "otilmoq", "RightAnswer": "erupt", "options": ["dismiss","confine","ash"]},
{"Question": "taqdir", "RightAnswer": "fate", "options": ["erupt","dismiss","confine"]},
{"Question": "lava", "RightAnswer": "lava", "options": ["fate","erupt","dismiss"]},
{"Question": "bechora", "RightAnswer": "miserable", "options": ["lava","fate","erupt"]},
{"Question": "boshqarmoq", "RightAnswer": "navigate", "options": ["miserable","lava","fate"]},
{"Question": "kelib chiqmoq", "RightAnswer": "originate", "options": ["navigate","miserable","lava"]},
{"Question": "qoldiq", "RightAnswer": "remainder", "options": ["originate","navigate","miserable"]},
{"Question": "topib kelmoq", "RightAnswer": "retrieve", "options": ["remainder","originate","navigate"]},
{"Question": "sayoz", "RightAnswer": "shallow", "options": ["retrieve","remainder","originate"]},
{"Question": "qiyalik", "RightAnswer": "slope", "options": ["shallow","retrieve","remainder"]},
{"Question": "kenglik", "RightAnswer": "span", "options": ["slope","shallow","retrieve"]},
{"Question": "insu-jins,", "RightAnswer": "superstition", "options": ["span","slope","shallow"]},
{"Question": "hamdartlik, achinish", "RightAnswer": "sympathy", "options": ["superstition","span","slope"]},
{"Question": "tebranmoq", "RightAnswer": "vibrate", "options": ["sympathy","superstition","span"]},
{"Question": "sang'imoq", "RightAnswer": "wander", "options": ["vibrate","sympathy","superstition"]}],	
"level 78" : [
    {"Question": "zirh", "RightAnswer": "armor", "options": ["wander","vibrate","sympathy"]},
{"Question": "portlamoq (ko'rinish)", "RightAnswer": "blaze", "options": ["armor","wander","vibrate"]},
{"Question": "portlamoq (ovoz)", "RightAnswer": "boom", "options": ["blaze","armor","wander"]},
{"Question": "qoya", "RightAnswer": "cliff", "options": ["boom","blaze","armor"]},
{"Question": "alanga", "RightAnswer": "flame", "options": ["cliff","boom","blaze"]},
{"Question": "mustaqillik", "RightAnswer": "independence", "options": ["flame","cliff","boom"]},
{"Question": "bosqin", "RightAnswer": "invasion", "options": ["independence","flame","cliff"]},
{"Question": "ritsar", "RightAnswer": "knight", "options": ["invasion","independence","flame"]},
{"Question": "chaqmoq", "RightAnswer": "lightning", "options": ["knight","invasion","independence"]},
{"Question": "isyonchi", "RightAnswer": "rebel", "options": ["lightning","knight","invasion"]},
{"Question": "chekinmoq", "RightAnswer": "retreat", "options": ["rebel","lightning","knight"]},
{"Question": "inqilob", "RightAnswer": "revolution", "options": ["retreat","rebel","lightning"]},
{"Question": "nayza", "RightAnswer": "spear", "options": ["revolution","retreat","rebel"]},
{"Question": "tik", "RightAnswer": "steep", "options": ["spear","revolution","retreat"]},
{"Question": "cho'qqi", "RightAnswer": "summit", "options": ["steep","spear","revolution"]},
{"Question": "momaqaldiroq", "RightAnswer": "thunder", "options": ["summit","steep","spear"]},
{"Question": "askarlar", "RightAnswer": "troops", "options": ["thunder","summit","steep"]},
{"Question": "jangchi", "RightAnswer": "warrior", "options": ["troops","thunder","summit"]},
{"Question": "olib tashlamoq", "RightAnswer": "withdraw", "options": ["warrior","troops","thunder"]},
{"Question": "yo'l bermoq", "RightAnswer": "yield", "options": ["withdraw","warrior","troops"]}],	
"level 79" : [
    {"Question": "o'rindiq", "RightAnswer": "bench", "options": ["yield","withdraw","warrior"]},
{"Question": "qarshi turmoq", "RightAnswer": "confront", "options": ["bench","yield","withdraw"]},
{"Question": "moychechak", "RightAnswer": "daisy", "options": ["confront","bench","yield"]},
{"Question": "kelishmovchilik", "RightAnswer": "dispute", "options": ["daisy","confront","bench"]},
{"Question": "dahshat", "RightAnswer": "horror", "options": ["dispute","daisy","confront"]},
{"Question": "hodisa", "RightAnswer": "incident", "options": ["horror","dispute","daisy"]},
{"Question": "tuman", "RightAnswer": "mist", "options": ["incident","horror","dispute"]},
{"Question": "ob'ekt", "RightAnswer": "object", "options": ["mist","incident","horror"]},
{"Question": "yetim", "RightAnswer": "orphan", "options": ["object","mist","incident"]},
{"Question": "reja", "RightAnswer": "plot", "options": ["orphan","object","mist"]},
{"Question": "homilador", "RightAnswer": "pregnant", "options": ["plot","orphan","object"]},
{"Question": "g'azab", "RightAnswer": "rage", "options": ["pregnant","plot","orphan"]},
{"Question": "intiqom", "RightAnswer": "revenge", "options": ["rage","pregnant","plot"]},
{"Question": "sharmandalik", "RightAnswer": "shame", "options": ["revenge","rage","pregnant"]},
{"Question": "xo'rsinmoq", "RightAnswer": "sigh", "options": ["shame","revenge","rage"]},
{"Question": "sezdirmasdan yurmoq", "RightAnswer": "sneak", "options": ["sigh","shame","revenge"]},
{"Question": "ortiqcha", "RightAnswer": "spare", "options": ["sneak","sigh","shame"]},
{"Question": "tana", "RightAnswer": "stem", "options": ["spare","sneak","sigh"]},
{"Question": "kechki ovqat", "RightAnswer": "supper", "options": ["stem","spare","sneak"]},
{"Question": "yumshoq", "RightAnswer": "tender", "options": ["supper","stem","spare"]}],	
"level 80" : [
    {"Question": "ostida", "RightAnswer": "beneath", "options": ["tender","supper","stem"]},
{"Question": "ayiq bolasi", "RightAnswer": "cub", "options": ["beneath","tender","supper"]},
{"Question": "tong", "RightAnswer": "dawn", "options": ["cub","beneath","tender"]},
{"Question": "qoniqmagan", "RightAnswer": "dissatisfied", "options": ["dawn","cub","beneath"]},
{"Question": "yengillik", "RightAnswer": "ease", "options": ["dissatisfied","dawn","cub"]},
{"Question": "aniq", "RightAnswer": "evident", "options": ["ease","dissatisfied","dawn"]},
{"Question": "do'l", "RightAnswer": "hail", "options": ["evident","ease","dissatisfied"]},
{"Question": "uvullamoq", "RightAnswer": "howl", "options": ["hail","evident","ease"]},
{"Question": "sakrash", "RightAnswer": "leap", "options": ["howl","hail","evident"]},
{"Question": "ajoyib", "RightAnswer": "magnificent", "options": ["leap","howl","hail"]},
{"Question": "majburiyat", "RightAnswer": "necessity", "options": ["magnificent","leap","howl"]},
{"Question": "natija", "RightAnswer": "outcome", "options": ["necessity","magnificent","leap"]},
{"Question": "uyum", "RightAnswer": "pile", "options": ["outcome","necessity","magnificent"]},
{"Question": "aqilli", "RightAnswer": "profound", "options": ["pile","outcome","necessity"]},
{"Question": "changallamoq", "RightAnswer": "seize", "options": ["profound","pile","outcome"]},
{"Question": "siqmoq", "RightAnswer": "squeeze", "options": ["seize","profound","pile"]},
{"Question": "oliy", "RightAnswer": "supreme", "options": ["squeeze","seize","profound"]},
{"Question": "ajoyib", "RightAnswer": "terrific", "options": ["supreme","squeeze","seize"]},
{"Question": "fazilat", "RightAnswer": "trait", "options": ["terrific","supreme","squeeze"]},
{"Question": "hayotiy", "RightAnswer": "vital", "options": ["trait","terrific","supreme"]}],	
"level 81" : [
    {"Question": "odatlanib qolgan", "RightAnswer": "accustomed", "options": ["vital","trait","terrific"]},
{"Question": "tasdiqlamoq", "RightAnswer": "affirm", "options": ["accustomed","vital","trait"]},
{"Question": "hayratda qolgan", "RightAnswer": "astonished", "options": ["affirm","accustomed","vital"]},
{"Question": "gumburlatmoq", "RightAnswer": "bang", "options": ["astonished","affirm","accustomed"]},
{"Question": "qabila", "RightAnswer": "clan", "options": ["bang","astonished","affirm"]},
{"Question": "kuchsiz yorug'lik", "RightAnswer": "dim", "options": ["clan","bang","astonished"]},
{"Question": "diqqat", "RightAnswer": "emphasis", "options": ["dim","clan","bang"]},
{"Question": "matal", "RightAnswer": "fable", "options": ["emphasis","dim","clan"]},
{"Question": "bayram", "RightAnswer": "feast", "options": ["fable","emphasis","dim"]},
{"Question": "yorug'lik", "RightAnswer": "glow", "options": ["feast","fable","emphasis"]},
{"Question": "ichi bo'sh", "RightAnswer": "hollow", "options": ["glow","feast","fable"]},
{"Question": "insti", "RightAnswer": "instinct", "options": ["hollow","glow","feast"]},
{"Question": "qo'shma", "RightAnswer": "joint", "options": ["instinct","hollow","glow"]},
{"Question": "oqish", "RightAnswer": "leak", "options": ["joint","instinct","hollow"]},
{"Question": "shifokor", "RightAnswer": "physician", "options": ["leak","joint","instinct"]},
{"Question": "qurbon qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "sacrifice", "options": ["physician","leak","joint"]},
{"Question": "qattiq", "RightAnswer": "stiff", "options": ["sacrifice","physician","leak"]},
{"Question": "paypaslamoq", "RightAnswer": "stroke", "options": ["stiff","sacrifice","physician"]},
{"Question": "fojiali", "RightAnswer": "tragic", "options": ["stroke","stiff","sacrifice"]},
{"Question": "sozlash", "RightAnswer": "tune", "options": ["tragic","stroke","stiff"]}],	
"level 82" : [
    {"Question": "joylashtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "accommodate", "options": ["tune","tragic","stroke"]},
{"Question": "sirk", "RightAnswer": "circus", "options": ["accommodate","tune","tragic"]},
{"Question": "baravar bo'moq", "RightAnswer": "coincide", "options": ["circus","accommodate","tune"]},
{"Question": "haq to'lamoq", "RightAnswer": "commission", "options": ["coincide","circus","accommodate"]},
{"Question": "doza", "RightAnswer": "dose", "options": ["commission","coincide","circus"]},
{"Question": "bo'yoq", "RightAnswer": "dye", "options": ["dose","commission","coincide"]},
{"Question": "ko'lam", "RightAnswer": "extent", "options": ["dye","dose","commission"]},
{"Question": "jins", "RightAnswer": "gender", "options": ["extent","dye","dose"]},
{"Question": "sarlavha", "RightAnswer": "headline", "options": ["gender","extent","dye"]},
{"Question": "norasmiy", "RightAnswer": "informal", "options": ["headline","gender","extent"]},
{"Question": "so'ramoq", "RightAnswer": "inquire", "options": ["informal","headline","gender"]},
{"Question": "xabarchi", "RightAnswer": "messenger", "options": ["inquire","informal","headline"]},
{"Question": "kuzatmoq", "RightAnswer": "peer", "options": ["messenger","inquire","informal"]},
{"Question": "portret", "RightAnswer": "portrait", "options": ["peer","messenger","inquire"]},
{"Question": "pozitsiya", "RightAnswer": "pose", "options": ["portrait","peer","messenger"]},
{"Question": "rancho", "RightAnswer": "ranch", "options": ["pose","portrait","peer"]},
{"Question": "boshqarmoq", "RightAnswer": "steer", "options": ["ranch","pose","portrait"]},
{"Question": "yo'l-yo'l chiziq", "RightAnswer": "stripe", "options": ["steer","ranch","pose"]},
{"Question": "qo'lga o'rgatilgan", "RightAnswer": "tame", "options": ["stripe","steer","ranch"]},
{"Question": "undamoq", "RightAnswer": "tempt", "options": ["tame","stripe","steer"]}],	
"level 83" : [
    {"Question": "Aborigin", "RightAnswer": "aborigine", "options": ["tempt","tame","stripe"]},
{"Question": "taqiqlamoq", "RightAnswer": "ban", "options": ["aborigine","tempt","tame"]},
{"Question": "ehtiyotkor", "RightAnswer": "cautious", "options": ["ban","aborigine","tempt"]},
{"Question": "tan olmoq", "RightAnswer": "confess", "options": ["cautious","ban","aborigine"]},
{"Question": "yozgi uy", "RightAnswer": "cottage", "options": ["confess","cautious","ban"]},
{"Question": "kunduzi", "RightAnswer": "daytime", "options": ["cottage","confess","cautious"]},
{"Question": "istalgan", "RightAnswer": "desperate", "options": ["daytime","cottage","confess"]},
{"Question": "rangi o'chmoq", "RightAnswer": "fade", "options": ["desperate","daytime","cottage"]},
{"Question": "shafqatsiz", "RightAnswer": "fierce", "options": ["fade","desperate","daytime"]},
{"Question": "qimor", "RightAnswer": "gamble", "options": ["fierce","fade","desperate"]},
{"Question": "maysazor", "RightAnswer": "lawn", "options": ["gamble","fierce","fade"]},
{"Question": "o'roq", "RightAnswer": "mow", "options": ["lawn","gamble","fierce"]},
{"Question": "noqonuniy", "RightAnswer": "outlaw", "options": ["mow","lawn","gamble"]},
{"Question": "istiqbol", "RightAnswer": "prospect", "options": ["outlaw","mow","lawn"]},
{"Question": "sumka", "RightAnswer": "purse", "options": ["prospect","outlaw","mow"]},
{"Question": "tayoq", "RightAnswer": "rod", "options": ["purse","prospect","outlaw"]},
{"Question": "kamdan-kam hollarda", "RightAnswer": "seldom", "options": ["rod","purse","prospect"]},
{"Question": "soqol olmoq", "RightAnswer": "shave", "options": ["seldom","rod","purse"]},
{"Question": "qo'rqqan", "RightAnswer": "terrified", "options": ["shave","seldom","rod"]},
{"Question": "sehrgar", "RightAnswer": "wizard", "options": ["terrified","shave","seldom"]}],	
"level 84" : [
    {"Question": "lampochka", "RightAnswer": "baggage", "options": ["wizard","terrified","shave"]},
{"Question": "to'plam", "RightAnswer": "bulb", "options": ["baggage","wizard","terrified"]},
{"Question": "qoramol", "RightAnswer": "bundle", "options": ["bulb","baggage","wizard"]},
{"Question": "qochmoq", "RightAnswer": "cattle", "options": ["bundle","bulb","baggage"]},
{"Question": "o'tlamoq", "RightAnswer": "flee", "options": ["cattle","bundle","bulb"]},
{"Question": "ochko'zlik", "RightAnswer": "graze", "options": ["flee","cattle","bundle"]},
{"Question": "poda", "RightAnswer": "greed", "options": ["graze","flee","cattle"]},
{"Question": "boshlamoq", "RightAnswer": "herd", "options": ["greed","graze","flee"]},
{"Question": "yo'l", "RightAnswer": "initiate", "options": ["herd","greed","graze"]},
{"Question": "yuk", "RightAnswer": "lane", "options": ["initiate","herd","greed"]},
{"Question": "asab", "RightAnswer": "nerve", "options": ["lane","initiate","herd"]},
{"Question": "optimist", "RightAnswer": "optimist", "options": ["nerve","lane","initiate"]},
{"Question": "parad", "RightAnswer": "parade", "options": ["optimist","nerve","lane"]},
{"Question": "tosh yotqizmoq", "RightAnswer": "pave", "options": ["parade","optimist","nerve"]},
{"Question": "hayoliy", "RightAnswer": "phantom", "options": ["pave","parade","optimist"]},
{"Question": "portativ", "RightAnswer": "portable", "options": ["phantom","pave","parade"]},
{"Question": "afisha", "RightAnswer": "poster", "options": ["portable","phantom","pave"]},
{"Question": "tirnamoq", "RightAnswer": "scratch", "options": ["poster","portable","phantom"]},
{"Question": "simfoniya", "RightAnswer": "symphony", "options": ["scratch","poster","portable"]},
{"Question": "beva ayol", "RightAnswer": "widow", "options": ["symphony","scratch","poster"]}],	
"level 85" : [
    {"Question": "tarqatmoq", "RightAnswer": "alter", "options": ["widow","symphony","scratch"]},
{"Question": "natijada", "RightAnswer": "aside", "options": ["alter","widow","symphony"]},
{"Question": "ko'chirmoq", "RightAnswer": "autumn", "options": ["aside","alter","widow"]},
{"Question": "cho'kmoq", "RightAnswer": "blend", "options": ["autumn","aside","alter"]},
{"Question": "sulola", "RightAnswer": "collapse", "options": ["blend","autumn","aside"]},
{"Question": "qism", "RightAnswer": "crush", "options": ["collapse","blend","autumn"]},
{"Question": "yaxlmalak", "RightAnswer": "curve", "options": ["crush","collapse","blend"]},
{"Question": "illuziya", "RightAnswer": "disgusting", "options": ["curve","crush","collapse"]},
{"Question": "ishg'ol qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "drain", "options": ["disgusting","curve","crush"]},
{"Question": "leytenant", "RightAnswer": "embrace", "options": ["drain","disgusting","curve"]},
{"Question": "dengizdagi", "RightAnswer": "envy", "options": ["embrace","drain","disgusting"]},
{"Question": "qadr-qimmati", "RightAnswer": "fireworks", "options": ["envy","embrace","drain"]},
{"Question": "flot", "RightAnswer": "flour", "options": ["fireworks","envy","embrace"]},
{"Question": "qutbli", "RightAnswer": "fuse", "options": ["flour","fireworks","envy"]},
{"Question": "nur", "RightAnswer": "ginger", "options": ["fuse","flour","fireworks"]},
{"Question": "iste'foga chiqmoq", "RightAnswer": "jealous", "options": ["ginger","fuse","flour"]},
{"Question": "o'z joniga qasd qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "paste", "options": ["jealous","ginger","fuse"]},
{"Question": "qaltirash", "RightAnswer": "receipt", "options": ["paste","jealous","ginger"]},
{"Question": "asosiy", "RightAnswer": "wipe", "options": ["receipt","paste","jealous"]},
{"Question": "orqali", "RightAnswer": "wire", "options": ["wipe","receipt","paste"]}],	
"level 86" : [
    {"Question": "o'zgartirmoq", "RightAnswer": "acknowledge", "options": ["wire","wipe","receipt"]},
{"Question": "chetda", "RightAnswer": "ambassador", "options": ["acknowledge","wire","wipe"]},
{"Question": "kuz", "RightAnswer": "blonde", "options": ["ambassador","acknowledge","wire"]},
{"Question": "aralashtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "conquer", "options": ["blonde","ambassador","acknowledge"]},
{"Question": "qulamoq", "RightAnswer": "drag", "options": ["conquer","blonde","ambassador"]},
{"Question": "ezmoq", "RightAnswer": "exaggerate", "options": ["drag","conquer","blonde"]},
{"Question": "yoy", "RightAnswer": "heritage", "options": ["exaggerate","drag","conquer"]},
{"Question": "jirkanchli", "RightAnswer": "insult", "options": ["heritage","exaggerate","drag"]},
{"Question": "oqova", "RightAnswer": "meanwhile", "options": ["insult","heritage","exaggerate"]},
{"Question": "quchoqlamoq", "RightAnswer": "necklace", "options": ["meanwhile","insult","heritage"]},
{"Question": "hasad qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "noble", "options": ["necklace","meanwhile","insult"]},
{"Question": "mushak", "RightAnswer": "precious", "options": ["noble","necklace","meanwhile"]},
{"Question": "un", "RightAnswer": "prejudice", "options": ["precious","noble","necklace"]},
{"Question": "yonadigan arqon", "RightAnswer": "rumor", "options": ["prejudice","precious","noble"]},
{"Question": "zanjabil", "RightAnswer": "sin", "options": ["rumor","prejudice","precious"]},
{"Question": "hasadchi", "RightAnswer": "spectacle", "options": ["sin","rumor","prejudice"]},
{"Question": "pasta, surtmoq", "RightAnswer": "stack", "options": ["spectacle","sin","rumor"]},
{"Question": "chek", "RightAnswer": "suspicious", "options": ["stack","spectacle","sin"]},
{"Question": "artmoq", "RightAnswer": "tin", "options": ["suspicious","stack","spectacle"]},
{"Question": "sim", "RightAnswer": "vase", "options": ["tin","suspicious","stack"]}],	
"level 87" : [
    {"Question": "e'tirof etmoq", "RightAnswer": "circulate", "options": ["vase","tin","suspicious"]},
{"Question": "elchi", "RightAnswer": "consequent", "options": ["circulate","vase","tin"]},
{"Question": "mallasoch", "RightAnswer": "derive", "options": ["consequent","circulate","vase"]},
{"Question": "ishg'ol qilish", "RightAnswer": "drown", "options": ["derive","consequent","circulate"]},
{"Question": "tortmoq", "RightAnswer": "dynasty", "options": ["drown","derive","consequent"]},
{"Question": "oshirib ko'rsatmoq", "RightAnswer": "fraction", "options": ["dynasty","drown","derive"]},
{"Question": "meros", "RightAnswer": "frost", "options": ["fraction","dynasty","drown"]},
{"Question": "haqorat qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "illusion", "options": ["frost","fraction","dynasty"]},
{"Question": "paytida", "RightAnswer": "invade", "options": ["illusion","frost","fraction"]},
{"Question": "marjon", "RightAnswer": "lieutenant", "options": ["invade","illusion","frost"]},
{"Question": "oliyjanob", "RightAnswer": "marine", "options": ["lieutenant","invade","illusion"]},
{"Question": "qimmatbaho", "RightAnswer": "merit", "options": ["marine","lieutenant","invade"]},
{"Question": "noto'g'ri tushuncha", "RightAnswer": "navy", "options": ["merit","marine","lieutenant"]},
{"Question": "mish-mish", "RightAnswer": "polar", "options": ["navy","merit","marine"]},
{"Question": "gunoh", "RightAnswer": "ray", "options": ["polar","navy","merit"]},
{"Question": "manzara", "RightAnswer": "resign", "options": ["ray","polar","navy"]},
{"Question": "g'aram", "RightAnswer": "suicide", "options": ["resign","ray","polar"]},
{"Question": "shubhali", "RightAnswer": "tremble", "options": ["suicide","resign","ray"]},
{"Question": "qalay", "RightAnswer": "underlying", "options": ["tremble","suicide","resign"]},
{"Question": "vaza", "RightAnswer": "via", "options": ["underlying","tremble","suicide"]}],	
"level 88" : [
    {"Question": "og'riq", "RightAnswer": "ache", "options": ["via","underlying","tremble"]},
{"Question": "arktik", "RightAnswer": "arctic", "options": ["ache","via","underlying"]},
{"Question": "kanal", "RightAnswer": "canal", "options": ["arctic","ache","via"]},
{"Question": "kimyogar", "RightAnswer": "chemist", "options": ["canal","arctic","ache"]},
{"Question": "salqinlamoq", "RightAnswer": "chill", "options": ["chemist","canal","arctic"]},
{"Question": "Kongress", "RightAnswer": "congress", "options": ["chill","chemist","canal"]},
{"Question": "sut mahsulotlari", "RightAnswer": "dairy", "options": ["congress","chill","chemist"]},
{"Question": "tushmoq", "RightAnswer": "descend", "options": ["dairy","congress","chill"]},
{"Question": "baqqol", "RightAnswer": "grocer", "options": ["descend","dairy","congress"]},
{"Question": "ikkilanmoq", "RightAnswer": "hesitate", "options": ["grocer","descend","dairy"]},
{"Question": "muassasa", "RightAnswer": "institution", "options": ["hesitate","grocer","descend"]},
{"Question": "yugurmoq", "RightAnswer": "jog", "options": ["institution","hesitate","grocer"]},
{"Question": "savdogar", "RightAnswer": "merchant", "options": ["jog","institution","hesitate"]},
{"Question": "bosmoq turtmoq", "RightAnswer": "poke", "options": ["merchant","jog","institution"]},
{"Question": "kechiktirmoq", "RightAnswer": "postpone", "options": ["poke","merchant","jog"]},
{"Question": "sepmoq", "RightAnswer": "splash", "options": ["postpone","poke","merchant"]},
{"Question": "o'jar", "RightAnswer": "stubborn", "options": ["splash","postpone","poke"]},
{"Question": "shahar cheti", "RightAnswer": "suburb", "options": ["stubborn","splash","postpone"]},
{"Question": "to'lqin", "RightAnswer": "tide", "options": ["suburb","stubborn","splash"]},
{"Question": "fojia", "RightAnswer": "tragedy", "options": ["tide","suburb","stubborn"]}],	
"level 89" : [
    {"Question": "bomba", "RightAnswer": "bomb", "options": ["tragedy","tide","suburb"]},
{"Question": "sertifikat", "RightAnswer": "certificate", "options": ["bomb","tragedy","tide"]},
{"Question": "vaziyat", "RightAnswer": "circumstance", "options": ["certificate","bomb","tragedy"]},
{"Question": "tobut", "RightAnswer": "coffin", "options": ["circumstance","certificate","bomb"]},
{"Question": "uddalamoq", "RightAnswer": "cope", "options": ["coffin","circumstance","certificate"]},
{"Question": "tanqid", "RightAnswer": "criticism", "options": ["cope","coffin","circumstance"]},
{"Question": "vayron qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "devastate", "options": ["criticism","cope","coffin"]},
{"Question": "qovoq o'ymoq", "RightAnswer": "frown", "options": ["devastate","criticism","cope"]},
{"Question": "qaramoq", "RightAnswer": "gaze", "options": ["frown","devastate","criticism"]},
{"Question": "qarash", "RightAnswer": "glance", "options": ["gaze","frown","devastate"]},
{"Question": "qayg'u", "RightAnswer": "grief", "options": ["glance","gaze","frown"]},
{"Question": "kuyov", "RightAnswer": "groom", "options": ["grief","glance","gaze"]},
{"Question": "litsenziya", "RightAnswer": "license", "options": ["groom","grief","glance"]},
{"Question": "mikroskop", "RightAnswer": "microscope", "options": ["license","groom","grief"]},
{"Question": "yadroviy", "RightAnswer": "nuclear", "options": ["microscope","license","groom"]},
{"Question": "ko'rsatmoq", "RightAnswer": "portray", "options": ["nuclear","microscope","license"]},
{"Question": "aylantirmoq", "RightAnswer": "rotate", "options": ["portray","nuclear","microscope"]},
{"Question": "estalik", "RightAnswer": "souvenir", "options": ["rotate","portray","nuclear"]},
{"Question": "batiskaf", "RightAnswer": "submarine", "options": ["souvenir","rotate","portray"]},
{"Question": "iz", "RightAnswer": "trace", "options": ["submarine","souvenir","rotate"]}],	
"level 90" : [
    {"Question": "qurilma", "RightAnswer": "appliance", "options": ["trace","submarine","souvenir"]},
{"Question": "havza", "RightAnswer": "basin", "options": ["appliance","trace","submarine"]},
{"Question": "supurgi", "RightAnswer": "broom", "options": ["basin","appliance","trace"]},
{"Question": "kapalak qurti", "RightAnswer": "caterpillar", "options": ["broom","basin","appliance"]},
{"Question": "Javon", "RightAnswer": "cupboard", "options": ["caterpillar","broom","basin"]},
{"Question": "nozik", "RightAnswer": "delicate", "options": ["cupboard","caterpillar","broom"]},
{"Question": "paydo bo'lmoq", "RightAnswer": "emerge", "options": ["delicate","cupboard","caterpillar"]},
{"Question": "falajlik", "RightAnswer": "handicap", "options": ["emerge","delicate","cupboard"]},
{"Question": "ilmoq", "RightAnswer": "hook", "options": ["handicap","emerge","delicate"]},
{"Question": "sakramoq", "RightAnswer": "hop", "options": ["hook","handicap","emerge"]},
{"Question": "kir kiyim", "RightAnswer": "laundry", "options": ["hop","hook","handicap"]},
{"Question": "ta'qib qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "pursue", "options": ["laundry","hop","hook"]},
{"Question": "istamay", "RightAnswer": "reluctant", "options": ["pursue","laundry","hop"]},
{"Question": "yeng", "RightAnswer": "sleeve", "options": ["reluctant","pursue","laundry"]},
{"Question": "umurtqa", "RightAnswer": "spine", "options": ["sleeve","reluctant","pursue"]},
{"Question": "dog'", "RightAnswer": "stain", "options": ["spine","sleeve","reluctant"]},
{"Question": "plyonka", "RightAnswer": "strip", "options": ["stain","spine","sleeve"]},
{"Question": "ont ichmoq", "RightAnswer": "swear", "options": ["strip","stain","spine"]},
{"Question": "belanchak", "RightAnswer": "swing", "options": ["swear","strip","stain"]},
{"Question": "foydalanmoq", "RightAnswer": "utilize", "options": ["swing","swear","strip"]}],	
"level 91" : [
    {"Question": "xushbo'y hid", "RightAnswer": "aroma", "options": ["utilize","swing","swear"]},
{"Question": "ichimliklar", "RightAnswer": "beverage", "options": ["aroma","utilize","swing"]},
{"Question": "to'plam", "RightAnswer": "cluster", "options": ["beverage","aroma","utilize"]},
{"Question": "qo'shmoq", "RightAnswer": "combine", "options": ["cluster","beverage","aroma"]},
{"Question": "zichlangan", "RightAnswer": "condensed", "options": ["combine","cluster","beverage"]},
{"Question": "zamonaviy", "RightAnswer": "contemporary", "options": ["condensed","combine","cluster"]},
{"Question": "yetishtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "cultivate", "options": ["contemporary","condensed","combine"]},
{"Question": "ilohiy", "RightAnswer": "divine", "options": ["cultivate","contemporary","condensed"]},
{"Question": "nam", "RightAnswer": "humid", "options": ["divine","cultivate","contemporary"]},
{"Question": "hid", "RightAnswer": "odor", "options": ["humid","divine","cultivate"]},
{"Question": "tag'nay", "RightAnswer": "palate", "options": ["odor","humid","divine"]},
{"Question": "jannat", "RightAnswer": "paradise", "options": ["palate","odor","humid"]},
{"Question": "dala maydoni", "RightAnswer": "plantation", "options": ["paradise","palate","odor"]},
{"Question": "tez", "RightAnswer": "rapid", "options": ["plantation","paradise","palate"]},
{"Question": "tezlik", "RightAnswer": "rate", "options": ["rapid","plantation","paradise"]},
{"Question": "tinchlantiruvchi", "RightAnswer": "soothing", "options": ["rate","rapid","plantation"]},
{"Question": "sezilmas", "RightAnswer": "subtle", "options": ["soothing","rate","rapid"]},
{"Question": "yuza shakli", "RightAnswer": "texture", "options": ["subtle","soothing","rate"]},
{"Question": "zaxarli", "RightAnswer": "toxic", "options": ["texture","subtle","soothing"]},
{"Question": "farq qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "vary", "options": ["toxic","texture","subtle"]}],	
"level 92" : [
    {"Question": "baxtsiz xodisa", "RightAnswer": "accident", "options": ["vary","toxic","texture"]},
{"Question": "admiral", "RightAnswer": "admiral", "options": ["accident","vary","toxic"]},
{"Question": "yoy", "RightAnswer": "arc", "options": ["admiral","accident","vary"]},
{"Question": "fe'l", "RightAnswer": "character", "options": ["arc","admiral","accident"]},
{"Question": "vijdon", "RightAnswer": "conscience", "options": ["character","arc","admiral"]},
{"Question": "olovli", "RightAnswer": "fiery", "options": ["conscience","character","arc"]},
{"Question": "go'sht", "RightAnswer": "flesh", "options": ["fiery","conscience","character"]},
{"Question": "mandarin", "RightAnswer": "grapefruit", "options": ["flesh","fiery","conscience"]},
{"Question": "pichan", "RightAnswer": "hay", "options": ["grapefruit","flesh","fiery"]},
{"Question": "dahshatga tushgan", "RightAnswer": "horrified", "options": ["hay","grapefruit","flesh"]},
{"Question": "kerosin", "RightAnswer": "kerosene", "options": ["horrified","hay","grapefruit"]},
{"Question": "halqa", "RightAnswer": "loop", "options": ["kerosene","horrified","hay"]},
{"Question": "eshkak", "RightAnswer": "paddle", "options": ["loop","kerosene","horrified"]},
{"Question": "sol", "RightAnswer": "raft", "options": ["paddle","loop","kerosene"]},
{"Question": "nordon", "RightAnswer": "sour", "options": ["raft","paddle","loop"]},
{"Question": "qoziq", "RightAnswer": "stake", "options": ["sour","raft","paddle"]},
{"Question": "xizmatchi", "RightAnswer": "steward", "options": ["stake","sour","raft"]},
{"Question": "ip", "RightAnswer": "string", "options": ["steward","stake","sour"]},
{"Question": "tikan", "RightAnswer": "thorn", "options": ["string","steward","stake"]},
{"Question": "vayron qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "wreck", "options": ["thorn","string","steward"]}],	
"level 93" : [
    {"Question": "tanbeh bermoq", "RightAnswer": "admonish", "options": ["wreck","thorn","string"]},
{"Question": "eshitiladigan", "RightAnswer": "audible", "options": ["admonish","wreck","thorn"]},
{"Question": "ajoyib", "RightAnswer": "awesome", "options": ["audible","admonish","wreck"]},
{"Question": "ehtiyot bo'lmoq", "RightAnswer": "beware", "options": ["awesome","audible","admonish"]},
{"Question": "maqtanmoq", "RightAnswer": "brag", "options": ["beware","awesome","audible"]},
{"Question": "xushi joyida", "RightAnswer": "conscious", "options": ["brag","beware","awesome"]},
{"Question": "qarshi bo'lmoq", "RightAnswer": "disagree", "options": ["conscious","brag","beware"]},
{"Question": "aks sado", "RightAnswer": "echo", "options": ["disagree","conscious","brag"]},
{"Question": "so'ngi", "RightAnswer": "eventual", "options": ["echo","disagree","conscious"]},
{"Question": "ishora", "RightAnswer": "hint", "options": ["eventual","echo","disagree"]},
{"Question": "ahmoq", "RightAnswer": "idiot", "options": ["hint","eventual","echo"]},
{"Question": "ulkan", "RightAnswer": "immense", "options": ["idiot","hint","eventual"]},
{"Question": "bilvosita", "RightAnswer": "indirect", "options": ["immense","idiot","hint"]},
{"Question": "tanlov", "RightAnswer": "option", "options": ["indirect","immense","idiot"]},
{"Question": "ko'ngilochar mashg'ulot", "RightAnswer": "pastime", "options": ["option","indirect","immense"]},
{"Question": "mukammal", "RightAnswer": "perfect", "options": ["pastime","option","indirect"]},
{"Question": "aniqlamoq", "RightAnswer": "pinpoint", "options": ["perfect","pastime","option"]},
{"Question": "o'zgartirmoq", "RightAnswer": "switch", "options": ["pinpoint","perfect","pastime"]},
{"Question": "batafsil to'liq", "RightAnswer": "thorough", "options": ["switch","pinpoint","perfect"]},
{"Question": "azob bermoq", "RightAnswer": "torment", "options": ["thorough","switch","pinpoint"]}],	
"level 94" : [
    {"Question": "tumshuq", "RightAnswer": "beak", "options": ["torment","thorough","switch"]},
{"Question": "ho'l", "RightAnswer": "damp", "options": ["beak","torment","thorough"]},
{"Question": "ma'qullamaslik", "RightAnswer": "disapprove", "options": ["damp","beak","torment"]},
{"Question": "dan tashqari", "RightAnswer": "except", "options": ["disapprove","damp","beak"]},
{"Question": "parvoz", "RightAnswer": "flight", "options": ["except","disapprove","damp"]},
{"Question": "xush ko'rmoq", "RightAnswer": "fond", "options": ["flight","except","disapprove"]},
{"Question": "axloqsiz", "RightAnswer": "immoral", "options": ["fond","flight","except"]},
{"Question": "pechak", "RightAnswer": "ivy", "options": ["immoral","fond","flight"]},
{"Question": "oh tortmoq", "RightAnswer": "moan", "options": ["ivy","immoral","fond"]},
{"Question": "bexabar", "RightAnswer": "oblivious", "options": ["moan","ivy","immoral"]},
{"Question": "halok bo'lmoq", "RightAnswer": "perish", "options": ["oblivious","moan","ivy"]},
{"Question": "chuqur", "RightAnswer": "pit", "options": ["perish","oblivious","moan"]},
{"Question": "chet, gardish", "RightAnswer": "rim", "options": ["pit","perish","oblivious"]},
{"Question": "in", "RightAnswer": "roost", "options": ["rim","pit","perish"]},
{"Question": "sirpanchiq", "RightAnswer": "slippery", "options": ["roost","rim","pit"]},
{"Question": "baland ko'tarilmoq", "RightAnswer": "soar", "options": ["slippery","roost","rim"]},
{"Question": "ahamiyatsiz", "RightAnswer": "trivial", "options": ["soar","slippery","roost"]},
{"Question": "odatiy", "RightAnswer": "typical", "options": ["trivial","soar","slippery"]},
{"Question": "o'ta darajada", "RightAnswer": "utterly", "options": ["typical","trivial","soar"]},
{"Question": "yig'lamoq", "RightAnswer": "weep", "options": ["utterly","typical","trivial"]}],	
"level 95" : [
    {"Question": "bir muddat", "RightAnswer": "awhile", "options": ["weep","utterly","typical"]},
{"Question": "kiber-maydon", "RightAnswer": "cyberspace", "options": ["awhile","weep","utterly"]},
{"Question": "tuzatish kiritmoq", "RightAnswer": "edit", "options": ["cyberspace","awhile","weep"]},
{"Question": "insho", "RightAnswer": "essay", "options": ["edit","cyberspace","awhile"]},
{"Question": "baholamoq", "RightAnswer": "evaluate", "options": ["essay","edit","cyberspace"]},
{"Question": "xushdan ketish", "RightAnswer": "faint", "options": ["evaluate","essay","edit"]},
{"Question": "global", "RightAnswer": "global", "options": ["faint","evaluate","essay"]},
{"Question": "sport zali", "RightAnswer": "gymnasium", "options": ["global","faint","evaluate"]},
{"Question": "belgilab qo'ymoq", "RightAnswer": "highlight", "options": ["gymnasium","global","faint"]},
{"Question": "e'tiborsiz", "RightAnswer": "ignorant", "options": ["highlight","gymnasium","global"]},
{"Question": "jadval", "RightAnswer": "index", "options": ["ignorant","highlight","gymnasium"]},
{"Question": "ma'ruza", "RightAnswer": "lecture", "options": ["index","ignorant","highlight"]},
{"Question": "ahloqiy", "RightAnswer": "moral", "options": ["lecture","index","ignorant"]},
{"Question": "ishlamoq", "RightAnswer": "operate", "options": ["moral","lecture","index"]},
{"Question": "xususiy", "RightAnswer": "private", "options": ["operate","moral","lecture"]},
{"Question": "yaqinda", "RightAnswer": "recent", "options": ["private","operate","moral"]},
{"Question": "qaror", "RightAnswer": "resolution", "options": ["recent","private","operate"]},
{"Question": "semestr", "RightAnswer": "semester", "options": ["resolution","recent","private"]},
{"Question": "yozma", "RightAnswer": "typewritten", "options": ["semester","resolution","recent"]},
{"Question": "g'alati", "RightAnswer": "weird", "options": ["typewritten","semester","resolution"]}],	
"level 96" : [
    {"Question": "mutlaq", "RightAnswer": "absolute", "options": ["weird","typewritten","semester"]},
{"Question": "afsuski", "RightAnswer": "alas", "options": ["absolute","weird","typewritten"]},
{"Question": "diqqatli", "RightAnswer": "attentive", "options": ["alas","absolute","weird"]},
{"Question": "yopinchiq", "RightAnswer": "cape", "options": ["attentive","alas","absolute"]},
{"Question": "tasavvur qilish", "RightAnswer": "envision", "options": ["cape","attentive","alas"]},
{"Question": "teng ravishda", "RightAnswer": "evenly", "options": ["envision","cape","attentive"]},
{"Question": "xalq", "RightAnswer": "folk", "options": ["evenly","envision","cape"]},
{"Question": "erimoq", "RightAnswer": "melt", "options": ["folk","evenly","envision"]},
{"Question": "parcha yer", "RightAnswer": "patch", "options": ["melt","folk","evenly"]},
{"Question": "zavq", "RightAnswer": "pleasure", "options": ["patch","melt","folk"]},
{"Question": "paq (tovush)", "RightAnswer": "pop", "options": ["pleasure","patch","melt"]},
{"Question": "puding", "RightAnswer": "pudding", "options": ["pop","pleasure","patch"]},
{"Question": "panjara qismi", "RightAnswer": "rail", "options": ["pudding","pop","pleasure"]},
{"Question": "retsept", "RightAnswer": "recipe", "options": ["rail","pudding","pop"]},
{"Question": "rol", "RightAnswer": "role", "options": ["recipe","rail","pudding"]},
{"Question": "kichraymoq", "RightAnswer": "shrink", "options": ["role","recipe","rail"]},
{"Question": "namlamoq", "RightAnswer": "soak", "options": ["shrink","role","recipe"]},
{"Question": "uchqun", "RightAnswer": "spark", "options": ["soak","shrink","role"]},
{"Question": "ruh", "RightAnswer": "spirit", "options": ["spark","soak","shrink"]},
{"Question": "kostyum", "RightAnswer": "suit", "options": ["spirit","spark","soak"]}],	
"level 97" : [
    {"Question": "hisob raqam", "RightAnswer": "account", "options": ["suit","spirit","spark"]},
{"Question": "me'mor", "RightAnswer": "architect", "options": ["account","suit","spirit"]},
{"Question": "yashirmoq", "RightAnswer": "conceal", "options": ["architect","account","suit"]},
{"Question": "jinoyat", "RightAnswer": "crime", "options": ["conceal","architect","account"]},
{"Question": "guvohnoma", "RightAnswer": "deed", "options": ["crime","conceal","architect"]},
{"Question": "minnatdorchilik", "RightAnswer": "gratitude", "options": ["deed","crime","conceal"]},
{"Question": "yashash joyi", "RightAnswer": "habitat", "options": ["gratitude","deed","crime"]},
{"Question": "aralashmoq", "RightAnswer": "intervene", "options": ["habitat","gratitude","deed"]},
{"Question": "belgi", "RightAnswer": "landmark", "options": ["intervene","habitat","gratitude"]},
{"Question": "qonuniy", "RightAnswer": "legal", "options": ["landmark","intervene","habitat"]},
{"Question": "unutilmas", "RightAnswer": "memorable", "options": ["legal","landmark","intervene"]},
{"Question": "majbur qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "oblige", "options": ["memorable","legal","landmark"]},
{"Question": "jinoyat", "RightAnswer": "offense", "options": ["oblige","memorable","legal"]},
{"Question": "e'lon qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "proclaim", "options": ["offense","oblige","memorable"]},
{"Question": "namoyish", "RightAnswer": "rally", "options": ["proclaim","offense","oblige"]},
{"Question": "hal qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "resolve", "options": ["rally","proclaim","offense"]},
{"Question": "manba", "RightAnswer": "resource", "options": ["resolve","rally","proclaim"]},
{"Question": "hukm", "RightAnswer": "sentence", "options": ["resource","resolve","rally"]},
{"Question": "ko'ngilli", "RightAnswer": "volunteer", "options": ["sentence","resource","resolve"]},
{"Question": "guvoh", "RightAnswer": "witness", "options": ["volunteer","sentence","resource"]}],	
"level 98" : [
    {"Question": "kirish imkoniyati", "RightAnswer": "access", "options": ["witness","volunteer","sentence"]},
{"Question": "fe'l-atvor", "RightAnswer": "conduct", "options": ["access","witness","volunteer"]},
{"Question": "doimiy", "RightAnswer": "constant", "options": ["conduct","access","witness"]},
{"Question": "yoriq", "RightAnswer": "crack", "options": ["constant","conduct","access"]},
{"Question": "qurilma", "RightAnswer": "device", "options": ["crack","constant","conduct"]},
{"Question": "o'ramoq", "RightAnswer": "enclose", "options": ["device","crack","constant"]},
{"Question": "mahkam tutmoq", "RightAnswer": "grip", "options": ["enclose","device","crack"]},
{"Question": "to'xtamoq", "RightAnswer": "halt", "options": ["grip","enclose","device"]},
{"Question": "yaqinlashib kelayotgan", "RightAnswer": "impending", "options": ["halt","grip","enclose"]},
{"Question": "ta'sir o'tkazmoq", "RightAnswer": "influence", "options": ["impending","halt","grip"]},
{"Question": "qonun", "RightAnswer": "law", "options": ["influence","impending","halt"]},
{"Question": "holat", "RightAnswer": "mode", "options": ["law","influence","impending"]},
{"Question": "terlamoq", "RightAnswer": "perspire", "options": ["mode","law","influence"]},
{"Question": "o'zgartirmoq", "RightAnswer": "replace", "options": ["perspire","mode","law"]},
{"Question": "sindirmoq", "RightAnswer": "snap", "options": ["replace","perspire","mode"]},
{"Question": "ayyor", "RightAnswer": "sly", "options": ["snap","replace","perspire"]},
{"Question": "moyil", "RightAnswer": "tend", "options": ["sly","snap","replace"]},
{"Question": "ishonchli", "RightAnswer": "valid", "options": ["tend","sly","snap"]},
{"Question": "versiya", "RightAnswer": "version", "options": ["valid","tend","sly"]},
{"Question": "umuman", "RightAnswer": "whatsoever", "options": ["version","valid","tend"]}],	
"level 99" : [
    {"Question": "yonida", "RightAnswer": "alongside", "options": ["whatsoever","version","valid"]},
{"Question": "ishtaha", "RightAnswer": "appetite", "options": ["alongside","whatsoever","version"]},
{"Question": "yordam bermoq", "RightAnswer": "assist", "options": ["appetite","alongside","whatsoever"]},
{"Question": "yengil shamol", "RightAnswer": "breeze", "options": ["assist","appetite","alongside"]},
{"Question": "qarshilik qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "defy", "options": ["breeze","assist","appetite"]},
{"Question": "ko'rsatmoq", "RightAnswer": "display", "options": ["defy","breeze","assist"]},
{"Question": "samarali", "RightAnswer": "efficient", "options": ["display","defy","breeze"]},
{"Question": "zaif", "RightAnswer": "feeble", "options": ["efficient","display","defy"]},
{"Question": "kechirmoq", "RightAnswer": "forgive", "options": ["feeble","efficient","display"]},
{"Question": "jo'shqin", "RightAnswer": "lively", "options": ["forgive","feeble","efficient"]},
{"Question": "ulug'vor", "RightAnswer": "majestic", "options": ["lively","forgive","feeble"]},
{"Question": "ham emas", "RightAnswer": "nor", "options": ["majestic","lively","forgive"]},
{"Question": "g'azablangan", "RightAnswer": "outraged", "options": ["nor","majestic","lively"]},
{"Question": "noumid", "RightAnswer": "pessimistic", "options": ["outraged","nor","majestic"]},
{"Question": "mish-mish", "RightAnswer": "rumor", "options": ["pessimistic","outraged","nor"]},
{"Question": "tarsaki tushirmoq", "RightAnswer": "slap", "options": ["rumor","pessimistic","outraged"]},
{"Question": "sindirmoq", "RightAnswer": "smash", "options": ["slap","rumor","pessimistic"]},
{"Question": "mavzu", "RightAnswer": "subject", "options": ["smash","slap","rumor"]},
{"Question": "ish haqi", "RightAnswer": "wage", "options": ["subject","smash","slap"]},
{"Question": "holbuki", "RightAnswer": "whereas", "options": ["wage","subject","smash"]}],	
"level 100" : [
    {"Question": "jonli", "RightAnswer": "animate", "options": ["whereas","wage","subject"]},
{"Question": "tasniflash", "RightAnswer": "classify", "options": ["animate","whereas","wage"]},
{"Question": "tan olmoq", "RightAnswer": "concede", "options": ["classify","animate","whereas"]},
{"Question": "tushuncha", "RightAnswer": "concept", "options": ["concede","classify","animate"]},
{"Question": "qurmoq", "RightAnswer": "construct", "options": ["concept","concede","classify"]},
{"Question": "o'n yil", "RightAnswer": "decade", "options": ["construct","concept","concede"]},
{"Question": "jadval", "RightAnswer": "diagram", "options": ["decade","construct","concept"]},
{"Question": "kema", "RightAnswer": "ferry", "options": ["diagram","decade","construct"]},
{"Question": "foydali", "RightAnswer": "handy", "options": ["ferry","diagram","decade"]},
{"Question": "ajratib qo'ymoq", "RightAnswer": "isolate", "options": ["handy","ferry","diagram"]},
{"Question": "intizorlik", "RightAnswer": "longing", "options": ["isolate","handy","ferry"]},
{"Question": "ko'p", "RightAnswer": "numerous", "options": ["longing","isolate","handy"]},
{"Question": "zarracha", "RightAnswer": "particle", "options": ["numerous","longing","isolate"]},
{"Question": "o'tinch", "RightAnswer": "plea", "options": ["particle","numerous","longing"]},
{"Question": "o'zini tiymoq", "RightAnswer": "refrain", "options": ["plea","particle","numerous"]},
{"Question": "ko'rib chiqmoq", "RightAnswer": "review", "options": ["refrain","plea","particle"]},
{"Question": "murakkab", "RightAnswer": "sophisticated", "options": ["review","refrain","plea"]},
{"Question": "taslim bo'lmoq", "RightAnswer": "surrender", "options": ["sophisticated","review","refrain"]},
{"Question": "tik", "RightAnswer": "upright", "options": ["surrender","sophisticated","review"]},
{"Question": "kerakli", "RightAnswer": "worthwhile", "options": ["upright","surrender","sophisticated"]}],	
"level 101" : [
    {"Question": "ittifoq", "RightAnswer": "alliance", "options": ["worthwhile","upright","surrender"]},
{"Question": "olqmoq", "RightAnswer": "applause", "options": ["alliance","worthwhile","upright"]},
{"Question": "qurollangan", "RightAnswer": "armed", "options": ["applause","alliance","worthwhile"]},
{"Question": "ustuvor", "RightAnswer": "authoritative", "options": ["armed","applause","alliance"]},
{"Question": "marosim", "RightAnswer": "ceremony", "options": ["authoritative","armed","applause"]},
{"Question": "madaniyat", "RightAnswer": "culture", "options": ["ceremony","authoritative","armed"]},
{"Question": "mudofaa", "RightAnswer": "defense", "options": ["culture","ceremony","authoritative"]},
{"Question": "kichik qism", "RightAnswer": "detail", "options": ["defense","culture","ceremony"]},
{"Question": "turli xil", "RightAnswer": "diverse", "options": ["detail","defense","culture"]},
{"Question": "sehrlamoq", "RightAnswer": "enchant", "options": ["diverse","detail","defense"]},
{"Question": "jihozlamoq", "RightAnswer": "equip", "options": ["enchant","diverse","detail"]},
{"Question": "istisno", "RightAnswer": "exception", "options": ["equip","enchant","diverse"]},
{"Question": "uslub", "RightAnswer": "genre", "options": ["exception","equip","enchant"]},
{"Question": "ta'sir", "RightAnswer": "impact", "options": ["genre","exception","equip"]},
{"Question": "o'ziga jalb qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "lure", "options": ["impact","genre","exception"]},
{"Question": "to'siq", "RightAnswer": "obstacle", "options": ["lure","impact","genre"]},
{"Question": "boshpana", "RightAnswer": "shelter", "options": ["obstacle","lure","impact"]},
{"Question": "tartibga solmoq", "RightAnswer": "sort", "options": ["shelter","obstacle","lure"]},
{"Question": "ta'minlamoq", "RightAnswer": "supply", "options": ["sort","shelter","obstacle"]},
{"Question": "o'ziga bino qo'ygan", "RightAnswer": "vain", "options": ["supply","sort","shelter"]}],	
"level 102" : [
    {"Question": "muqobil", "RightAnswer": "alternative", "options": ["vain","supply","sort"]},
{"Question": "ko'cha", "RightAnswer": "avenue", "options": ["alternative","vain","supply"]},
{"Question": "qorin", "RightAnswer": "belly", "options": ["avenue","alternative","vain"]},
{"Question": "urinish", "RightAnswer": "bid", "options": ["belly","avenue","alternative"]},
{"Question": "puflamoq", "RightAnswer": "blow", "options": ["bid","belly","avenue"]},
{"Question": "nizo", "RightAnswer": "conflict", "options": ["blow","bid","belly"]},
{"Question": "qit'a", "RightAnswer": "continent", "options": ["conflict","blow","bid"]},
{"Question": "oqim, hozirgi", "RightAnswer": "current", "options": ["continent","conflict","blow"]},
{"Question": "hurmatsizlik", "RightAnswer": "disrespect", "options": ["current","continent","conflict"]},
{"Question": "g'ayrat", "RightAnswer": "enthusiasm", "options": ["disrespect","current","continent"]},
{"Question": "qattiqqo'l", "RightAnswer": "harsh", "options": ["enthusiasm","disrespect","current"]},
{"Question": "suyanmoq", "RightAnswer": "lean", "options": ["harsh","enthusiasm","disrespect"]},
{"Question": "mobainida", "RightAnswer": "meantime", "options": ["lean","harsh","enthusiasm"]},
{"Question": "nayrang", "RightAnswer": "mischief", "options": ["meantime","lean","harsh"]},
{"Question": "mushak", "RightAnswer": "muscle", "options": ["mischief","meantime","lean"]},
{"Question": "qutqarmoq", "RightAnswer": "rescue", "options": ["muscle","mischief","meantime"]},
{"Question": "ketma-ketlik", "RightAnswer": "succession", "options": ["rescue","muscle","mischief"]},
{"Question": "yer", "RightAnswer": "terrain", "options": ["succession","rescue","muscle"]},
{"Question": "qo'rqoq", "RightAnswer": "timid", "options": ["terrain","succession","rescue"]},
{"Question": "zo'ravonlik", "RightAnswer": "violence", "options": ["timid","terrain","succession"]}],	
"level 103" : [
    {"Question": "ta'sir qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "affect", "options": ["violence","timid","terrain"]},
{"Question": "dastxat", "RightAnswer": "autograph", "options": ["affect","violence","timid"]},
{"Question": "tomchi", "RightAnswer": "bead", "options": ["autograph","affect","violence"]},
{"Question": "damlamoq", "RightAnswer": "brew", "options": ["bead","autograph","affect"]},
{"Question": "e'tiborni tortmoq", "RightAnswer": "charm", "options": ["brew","bead","autograph"]},
{"Question": "taqdir", "RightAnswer": "destiny", "options": ["charm","brew","bead"]},
{"Question": "signal", "RightAnswer": "horn", "options": ["destiny","charm","brew"]},
{"Question": "tez asabiylashadigan", "RightAnswer": "irritable", "options": ["horn","destiny","charm"]},
{"Question": "ortda qolmoq", "RightAnswer": "lag", "options": ["irritable","horn","destiny"]},
{"Question": "kuchaytirmoq", "RightAnswer": "maximize", "options": ["lag","irritable","horn"]},
{"Question": "yomon tush", "RightAnswer": "nightmare", "options": ["maximize","lag","irritable"]},
{"Question": "ozuqaga boy", "RightAnswer": "nutritious", "options": ["nightmare","maximize","lag"]},
{"Question": "oqsil", "RightAnswer": "protein", "options": ["nutritious","nightmare","maximize"]},
{"Question": "imzo", "RightAnswer": "signature", "options": ["protein","nutritious","nightmare"]},
{"Question": "narsa", "RightAnswer": "stuff", "options": ["signature","protein","nutritious"]},
{"Question": "ong osti", "RightAnswer": "subconscious", "options": ["stuff","signature","protein"]},
{"Question": "yuk mashinasi", "RightAnswer": "van", "options": ["subconscious","stuff","signature"]},
{"Question": "ogohlantirmoq", "RightAnswer": "warn", "options": ["van","subconscious","stuff"]},
{"Question": "mashq", "RightAnswer": "workout", "options": ["warn","van","subconscious"]},
{"Question": "tez yurmoq", "RightAnswer": "zoom", "options": ["workout","warn","van"]}],	
"level 104" : [
    {"Question": "g'isht", "RightAnswer": "brick", "options": ["zoom","workout","warn"]},
{"Question": "to'kilib qolmoq", "RightAnswer": "crumble", "options": ["brick","zoom","workout"]},
{"Question": "xamir", "RightAnswer": "dough", "options": ["crumble","brick","zoom"]},
{"Question": "ifodalamoq", "RightAnswer": "express", "options": ["dough","crumble","brick"]},
{"Question": "musht", "RightAnswer": "fist", "options": ["express","dough","crumble"]},
{"Question": "moslashuvchan", "RightAnswer": "flexible", "options": ["fist","express","dough"]},
{"Question": "qizarmoq", "RightAnswer": "flush", "options": ["flexible","fist","express"]},
{"Question": "shikastlamoq", "RightAnswer": "injure", "options": ["flush","flexible","fist"]},
{"Question": "bo'lak", "RightAnswer": "lump", "options": ["injure","flush","flexible"]},
{"Question": "aralashma", "RightAnswer": "mixture", "options": ["lump","injure","flush"]},
{"Question": "yarashmoq", "RightAnswer": "reconcile", "options": ["mixture","lump","injure"]},
{"Question": "vayron qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "ruin", "options": ["reconcile","mixture","lump"]},
{"Question": "sindirmoq", "RightAnswer": "shatter", "options": ["ruin","reconcile","mixture"]},
{"Question": "tashqi deraza", "RightAnswer": "shutter", "options": ["shatter","ruin","reconcile"]},
{"Question": "elamoq", "RightAnswer": "sift", "options": ["shutter","shatter","ruin"]},
{"Question": "biroz", "RightAnswer": "slight", "options": ["sift","shutter","shatter"]},
{"Question": "chaqnamoq", "RightAnswer": "sparkle", "options": ["slight","sift","shutter"]},
{"Question": "sepmoq", "RightAnswer": "sprinkle", "options": ["sparkle","slight","sift"]},
{"Question": "qotgan", "RightAnswer": "stale", "options": ["sprinkle","sparkle","slight"]},
{"Question": "gapirmoq", "RightAnswer": "utter", "options": ["stale","sprinkle","sparkle"]}],	
"level 105" : [
    {"Question": "bo'lsa-da", "RightAnswer": "although", "options": ["utter","stale","sprinkle"]},
{"Question": "qo'ymoq", "RightAnswer": "apply", "options": ["although","utter","stale"]},
{"Question": "kutmoq", "RightAnswer": "await", "options": ["apply","although","utter"]},
{"Question": "sevimli", "RightAnswer": "beloved", "options": ["await","apply","although"]},
{"Question": "dafn qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "bury", "options": ["beloved","await","apply"]},
{"Question": "iqlim", "RightAnswer": "climate", "options": ["bury","beloved","await"]},
{"Question": "shikoyat qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "complain", "options": ["climate","bury","beloved"]},
{"Question": "adashtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "confuse", "options": ["complain","climate","bury"]},
{"Question": "kutilmoq", "RightAnswer": "due", "options": ["confuse","complain","climate"]},
{"Question": "butun", "RightAnswer": "entire", "options": ["due","confuse","complain"]},
{"Question": "tashkil etmoq", "RightAnswer": "establish", "options": ["entire","due","confuse"]},
{"Question": "isitgich", "RightAnswer": "furnace", "options": ["establish","entire","due"]},
{"Question": "arqon", "RightAnswer": "leash", "options": ["furnace","establish","entire"]},
{"Question": "ulg'aymoq", "RightAnswer": "mature", "options": ["leash","furnace","establish"]},
{"Question": "o'lchamoq", "RightAnswer": "measure", "options": ["mature","leash","furnace"]},
{"Question": "o'rtada", "RightAnswer": "midst", "options": ["measure","mature","leash"]},
{"Question": "baxtsizlik", "RightAnswer": "misery", "options": ["midst","measure","mature"]},
{"Question": "oldin", "RightAnswer": "prior", "options": ["misery","midst","measure"]},
{"Question": "tadqiqot", "RightAnswer": "research", "options": ["prior","misery","midst"]},
{"Question": "turli", "RightAnswer": "variety", "options": ["research","prior","misery"]}],	
"level 106" : [
    {"Question": "batamom", "RightAnswer": "altogether", "options": ["variety","research","prior"]},
{"Question": "birlashmoq", "RightAnswer": "bind", "options": ["altogether","variety","research"]},
{"Question": "ko'karish lat", "RightAnswer": "bruise", "options": ["bind","altogether","variety"]},
{"Question": "odat", "RightAnswer": "custom", "options": ["bruise","bind","altogether"]},
{"Question": "itoatsiz", "RightAnswer": "disobedient", "options": ["custom","bruise","bind"]},
{"Question": "oldindan ko'rmoq", "RightAnswer": "foresee", "options": ["disobedient","custom","bruise"]},
{"Question": "qaramoq", "RightAnswer": "glimpse", "options": ["foresee","disobedient","custom"]},
{"Question": "halqa", "RightAnswer": "hoop", "options": ["glimpse","foresee","disobedient"]},
{"Question": "baxtsizlik", "RightAnswer": "misfortune", "options": ["hoop","glimpse","foresee"]},
{"Question": "salbiy", "RightAnswer": "negative", "options": ["misfortune","hoop","glimpse"]},
{"Question": "boshiga har bir", "RightAnswer": "per", "options": ["negative","misfortune","hoop"]},
{"Question": "yalinib so'ramoq", "RightAnswer": "plead", "options": ["per","negative","misfortune"]},
{"Question": "yirtmoq", "RightAnswer": "rip", "options": ["plead","per","negative"]},
{"Question": "uchun", "RightAnswer": "sake", "options": ["rip","plead","per"]},
{"Question": "qirmoq", "RightAnswer": "scrape", "options": ["sake","rip","plead"]},
{"Question": "manba", "RightAnswer": "source", "options": ["scrape","sake","rip"]},
{"Question": "juda jiddiy", "RightAnswer": "stern", "options": ["source","scrape","sake"]},
{"Question": "tikmoq", "RightAnswer": "stitch", "options": ["stern","source","scrape"]},
{"Question": "do'ppillash", "RightAnswer": "thump", "options": ["stitch","stern","source"]},
{"Question": "asabiylashgan", "RightAnswer": "vehement", "options": ["thump","stitch","stern"]}],	
"level 107" : [
    {"Question": "sivilizatsiya", "RightAnswer": "civilization", "options": ["vehement","thump","stitch"]},
{"Question": "qulay", "RightAnswer": "convenient", "options": ["civilization","vehement","thump"]},
{"Question": "in, o'ra", "RightAnswer": "den", "options": ["convenient","civilization","vehement"]},
{"Question": "shudring", "RightAnswer": "dew", "options": ["den","convenient","civilization"]},
{"Question": "qattiq, og'ir", "RightAnswer": "drastic", "options": ["dew","den","convenient"]},
{"Question": "chiqmoq", "RightAnswer": "exit", "options": ["drastic","dew","den"]},
{"Question": "suruv", "RightAnswer": "flock", "options": ["exit","drastic","dew"]},
{"Question": "qatlamoq", "RightAnswer": "fold", "options": ["flock","exit","drastic"]},
{"Question": "qopqoq", "RightAnswer": "lid", "options": ["fold","flock","exit"]},
{"Question": "cho'lg'amoq", "RightAnswer": "loom", "options": ["lid","fold","flock"]},
{"Question": "qudratli", "RightAnswer": "mighty", "options": ["loom","lid","fold"]},
{"Question": "qo'ziqorin", "RightAnswer": "mushroom", "options": ["mighty","loom","lid"]},
{"Question": "mahalliy", "RightAnswer": "native", "options": ["mushroom","mighty","loom"]},
{"Question": "zahar", "RightAnswer": "poison", "options": ["native","mushroom","mighty"]},
{"Question": "qamish", "RightAnswer": "reed", "options": ["poison","native","mushroom"]},
{"Question": "himoya qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "shield", "options": ["reed","poison","native"]},
{"Question": "bo'ronli", "RightAnswer": "stormy", "options": ["shield","reed","poison"]},
{"Question": "tebranmoq", "RightAnswer": "sway", "options": ["stormy","shield","reed"]},
{"Question": "shahar", "RightAnswer": "urban", "options": ["sway","stormy","shield"]},
{"Question": "suvda yurmoq", "RightAnswer": "wade", "options": ["urban","sway","stormy"]}],	
"level 108" : [
    {"Question": "talaffuz aksent", "RightAnswer": "accent", "options": ["wade","urban","sway"]},
{"Question": "sartarosh", "RightAnswer": "barber", "options": ["accent","wade","urban"]},
{"Question": "yerto'la", "RightAnswer": "basement", "options": ["barber","accent","wade"]},
{"Question": "bo'sh", "RightAnswer": "blank", "options": ["basement","barber","accent"]},
{"Question": "ko'zni yumib ochmoq", "RightAnswer": "blink", "options": ["blank","basement","barber"]},
{"Question": "xor", "RightAnswer": "choir", "options": ["blink","blank","basement"]},
{"Question": "kulgili", "RightAnswer": "comic", "options": ["choir","blink","blank"]},
{"Question": "murakkablashtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "complicate", "options": ["comic","choir","blink"]},
{"Question": "rad etmoq", "RightAnswer": "decline", "options": ["complicate","comic","choir"]},
{"Question": "harakat", "RightAnswer": "errand", "options": ["decline","complicate","comic"]},
{"Question": "qo'lqop", "RightAnswer": "glove", "options": ["errand","decline","complicate"]},
{"Question": "odamovi", "RightAnswer": "hermit", "options": ["glove","errand","decline"]},
{"Question": "adolatli", "RightAnswer": "justly", "options": ["hermit","glove","errand"]},
{"Question": "charm", "RightAnswer": "leather", "options": ["justly","hermit","glove"]},
{"Question": "o'ylab ko'rmoq", "RightAnswer": "ponder", "options": ["leather","justly","hermit"]},
{"Question": "olib qo'ymoq", "RightAnswer": "reserve", "options": ["ponder","leather","justly"]},
{"Question": "ssenariy", "RightAnswer": "script", "options": ["reserve","ponder","leather"]},
{"Question": "qidirmoq", "RightAnswer": "search", "options": ["script","reserve","ponder"]},
{"Question": "qattiq yopmoq", "RightAnswer": "slam", "options": ["search","script","reserve"]},
{"Question": "zina", "RightAnswer": "staircase", "options": ["slam","search","script"]}],	
"level 109" : [
    {"Question": "azoblangan", "RightAnswer": "afflicted", "options": ["staircase","slam","search"]},
{"Question": "yo'lak", "RightAnswer": "aisle", "options": ["afflicted","staircase","slam"]},
{"Question": "atmosfera", "RightAnswer": "atmosphere", "options": ["aisle","afflicted","staircase"]},
{"Question": "muallif", "RightAnswer": "author", "options": ["atmosphere","aisle","afflicted"]},
{"Question": "buzilish", "RightAnswer": "breakdown", "options": ["author","atmosphere","aisle"]},
{"Question": "yuk", "RightAnswer": "cargo", "options": ["breakdown","author","atmosphere"]},
{"Question": "bo'lim", "RightAnswer": "chapter", "options": ["cargo","breakdown","author"]},
{"Question": "ulanmoq", "RightAnswer": "connect", "options": ["chapter","cargo","breakdown"]},
{"Question": "va boshqalar", "RightAnswer": "etc.", "options": ["connect","chapter","cargo"]},
{"Question": "bosmoq", "RightAnswer": "flip", "options": ["etc.","connect","chapter"]},
{"Question": "bo'sh", "RightAnswer": "idle", "options": ["flip","etc.","connect"]},
{"Question": "xabar bermoq", "RightAnswer": "notify", "options": ["idle","flip","etc."]},
{"Question": "no'xat", "RightAnswer": "pea", "options": ["notify","idle","flip"]},
{"Question": "mayiz", "RightAnswer": "raisin", "options": ["pea","notify","idle"]},
{"Question": "saqlamoq", "RightAnswer": "retain", "options": ["raisin","pea","notify"]},
{"Question": "takidlamoq", "RightAnswer": "state", "options": ["retain","raisin","pea"]},
{"Question": "patnis", "RightAnswer": "tray", "options": ["state","retain","raisin"]},
{"Question": "baxtsiz", "RightAnswer": "unfortunate", "options": ["tray","state","retain"]},
{"Question": "rang-barang", "RightAnswer": "vivid", "options": ["unfortunate","tray","state"]},
{"Question": "qayt qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "vomit", "options": ["vivid","unfortunate","tray"]}],	
"level 110" : [
    {"Question": "xiyonat qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "betray", "options": ["vomit","vivid","unfortunate"]},
{"Question": "portlash", "RightAnswer": "blast", "options": ["betray","vomit","vivid"]},
{"Question": "bilaguzuk", "RightAnswer": "bracelet", "options": ["blast","betray","vomit"]},
{"Question": "to'xtamoq", "RightAnswer": "cease", "options": ["bracelet","blast","betray"]},
{"Question": "yo'talmoq", "RightAnswer": "choke", "options": ["cease","bracelet","blast"]},
{"Question": "fuqarolik", "RightAnswer": "civil", "options": ["choke","cease","bracelet"]},
{"Question": "sharhlamoq", "RightAnswer": "comment", "options": ["civil","choke","cease"]},
{"Question": "kesib o'tmoq", "RightAnswer": "cross", "options": ["comment","civil","choke"]},
{"Question": "pachoq", "RightAnswer": "dent", "options": ["cross","comment","civil"]},
{"Question": "ishonchsizlik", "RightAnswer": "distrust", "options": ["dent","cross","comment"]},
{"Question": "qal'a", "RightAnswer": "fort", "options": ["distrust","dent","cross"]},
{"Question": "tashkil qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "found", "options": ["fort","distrust","dent"]},
{"Question": "astar", "RightAnswer": "lining", "options": ["found","fort","distrust"]},
{"Question": "uyum", "RightAnswer": "mass", "options": ["lining","found","fort"]},
{"Question": "ibodat qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "pray", "options": ["mass","lining","found"]},
{"Question": "to'la", "RightAnswer": "rife", "options": ["pray","mass","lining"]},
{"Question": "yagona", "RightAnswer": "sole", "options": ["rife","pray","mass"]},
{"Question": "supurmoq", "RightAnswer": "sweep", "options": ["sole","rife","pray"]},
{"Question": "xiyonat", "RightAnswer": "treachery", "options": ["sweep","sole","rife"]},
{"Question": "joylamoq", "RightAnswer": "tuck", "options": ["treachery","sweep","sole"]}],	
"level 111" : [
    {"Question": "tarbiya", "RightAnswer": "background", "options": ["tuck","treachery","sweep"]},
{"Question": "xo'rak", "RightAnswer": "bait", "options": ["background","tuck","treachery"]},
{"Question": "yozib bormoq", "RightAnswer": "chronicle", "options": ["bait","background","tuck"]},
{"Question": "mis", "RightAnswer": "copper", "options": ["chronicle","bait","background"]},
{"Question": "kasallik", "RightAnswer": "disease", "options": ["copper","chronicle","bait"]},
{"Question": "xalq ijodi", "RightAnswer": "folklore", "options": ["disease","copper","chronicle"]},
{"Question": "yuqtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "infect", "options": ["folklore","disease","copper"]},
{"Question": "qichimoq", "RightAnswer": "itch", "options": ["infect","folklore","disease"]},
{"Question": "adabiyot", "RightAnswer": "literature", "options": ["itch","infect","folklore"]},
{"Question": "ming yillik", "RightAnswer": "millennium", "options": ["literature","itch","infect"]},
{"Question": "afsona", "RightAnswer": "myth", "options": ["millennium","literature","itch"]},
{"Question": "mansabini oshirmoq", "RightAnswer": "promote", "options": ["myth","millennium","literature"]},
{"Question": "bog'lamoq", "RightAnswer": "relate", "options": ["promote","myth","millennium"]},
{"Question": "din", "RightAnswer": "religion", "options": ["relate","promote","myth"]},
{"Question": "miqdor", "RightAnswer": "sum", "options": ["religion","relate","promote"]},
{"Question": "bank ishchisi", "RightAnswer": "teller", "options": ["sum","religion","relate"]},
{"Question": "ishonchli", "RightAnswer": "trustworthy", "options": ["teller","sum","religion"]},
{"Question": "yangilamoq", "RightAnswer": "update", "options": ["trustworthy","teller","sum"]},
{"Question": "tomir", "RightAnswer": "vein", "options": ["update","trustworthy","teller"]},
{"Question": "zahar", "RightAnswer": "venom", "options": ["vein","update","trustworthy"]}],	
"level 112" : [
    {"Question": "xayriya", "RightAnswer": "charity", "options": ["venom","vein","update"]},
{"Question": "tijorat", "RightAnswer": "commerce", "options": ["charity","venom","vein"]},
{"Question": "hukm qilish", "RightAnswer": "condemn", "options": ["commerce","charity","venom"]},
{"Question": "qulay", "RightAnswer": "cozy", "options": ["condemn","commerce","charity"]},
{"Question": "tugatmoq", "RightAnswer": "deplete", "options": ["cozy","condemn","commerce"]},
{"Question": "iqtisodiyot", "RightAnswer": "economy", "options": ["deplete","cozy","condemn"]},
{"Question": "imperiya", "RightAnswer": "empire", "options": ["economy","deplete","cozy"]},
{"Question": "mahsulot", "RightAnswer": "goods", "options": ["empire","economy","deplete"]},
{"Question": "diqqat qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "heed", "options": ["goods","empire","economy"]},
{"Question": "tekinga yurmoq", "RightAnswer": "hitchhike", "options": ["heed","goods","empire"]},
{"Question": "masxara qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "mock", "options": ["hitchhike","heed","goods"]},
{"Question": "betaraf", "RightAnswer": "neutral", "options": ["mock","hitchhike","heed"]},
{"Question": "kamsitmoq", "RightAnswer": "persecute", "options": ["neutral","mock","hitchhike"]},
{"Question": "achinish", "RightAnswer": "pity", "options": ["persecute","neutral","mock"]},
{"Question": "kamaytirmoq", "RightAnswer": "reduce", "options": ["pity","persecute","neutral"]},
{"Question": "xattot", "RightAnswer": "scribe", "options": ["reduce","pity","persecute"]},
{"Question": "jaxl", "RightAnswer": "temper", "options": ["scribe","reduce","pity"]},
{"Question": "taxt", "RightAnswer": "throne", "options": ["temper","scribe","reduce"]},
{"Question": "birlik", "RightAnswer": "unity", "options": ["throne","temper","scribe"]},
{"Question": "g'olib", "RightAnswer": "victor", "options": ["unity","throne","temper"]}],	
"level 113" : [
    {"Question": "aniq", "RightAnswer": "accurate", "options": ["victor","unity","throne"]},
{"Question": "tahlil qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "analyze", "options": ["accurate","victor","unity"]},
{"Question": "asteroid", "RightAnswer": "asteroid", "options": ["analyze","accurate","victor"]},
{"Question": "tortishuv", "RightAnswer": "controversy", "options": ["asteroid","analyze","accurate"]},
{"Question": "rivojlanmoq", "RightAnswer": "evolve", "options": ["controversy","asteroid","analyze"]},
{"Question": "omil", "RightAnswer": "factor", "options": ["evolve","controversy","asteroid"]},
{"Question": "genetik", "RightAnswer": "genetic", "options": ["factor","evolve","controversy"]},
{"Question": "irsiyat", "RightAnswer": "genome", "options": ["genetic","factor","evolve"]},
{"Question": "bir xil", "RightAnswer": "identical", "options": ["genome","genetic","factor"]},
{"Question": "oqil", "RightAnswer": "intellectual", "options": ["identical","genome","genetic"]},
{"Question": "ko'pchilik", "RightAnswer": "majority", "options": ["intellectual","identical","genome"]},
{"Question": "sutemizuvchi", "RightAnswer": "mammal", "options": ["majority","intellectual","identical"]},
{"Question": "ko'paymoq", "RightAnswer": "multiply", "options": ["mammal","majority","intellectual"]},
{"Question": "zurriyod", "RightAnswer": "offspring", "options": ["multiply","mammal","majority"]},
{"Question": "pestisid", "RightAnswer": "pesticide", "options": ["offspring","multiply","mammal"]},
{"Question": "tartibga solmoq", "RightAnswer": "regulate", "options": ["pesticide","offspring","multiply"]},
{"Question": "kuchaytirmoq", "RightAnswer": "reinforce", "options": ["regulate","pesticide","offspring"]},
{"Question": "aziyat chekgan", "RightAnswer": "stricken", "options": ["reinforce","regulate","pesticide"]},
{"Question": "katta", "RightAnswer": "vast", "options": ["stricken","reinforce","regulate"]},
{"Question": "vegetarian", "RightAnswer": "vegetarian", "options": ["vast","stricken","reinforce"]}],	
"level 114" : [
    {"Question": "qadrlamoq", "RightAnswer": "cherish", "options": ["vegetarian","vast","stricken"]},
{"Question": "rahm", "RightAnswer": "compassion", "options": ["cherish","vegetarian","vast"]},
{"Question": "rozilik", "RightAnswer": "consent", "options": ["compassion","cherish","vegetarian"]},
{"Question": "o'zak", "RightAnswer": "core", "options": ["consent","compassion","cherish"]},
{"Question": "ayyor", "RightAnswer": "cunning", "options": ["core","consent","compassion"]},
{"Question": "holsiz", "RightAnswer": "dizzy", "options": ["cunning","core","consent"]},
{"Question": "muvozanat", "RightAnswer": "equilibrium", "options": ["dizzy","cunning","core"]},
{"Question": "shakllantirish", "RightAnswer": "foster", "options": ["equilibrium","dizzy","cunning"]},
{"Question": "ezmoq", "RightAnswer": "grind", "options": ["foster","equilibrium","dizzy"]},
{"Question": "irillamoq", "RightAnswer": "growl", "options": ["grind","foster","equilibrium"]},
{"Question": "o'rtacha", "RightAnswer": "moderation", "options": ["growl","grind","foster"]},
{"Question": "yirtqich", "RightAnswer": "predator", "options": ["moderation","growl","grind"]},
{"Question": "ongli", "RightAnswer": "sane", "options": ["predator","moderation","growl"]},
{"Question": "likopcha", "RightAnswer": "saucer", "options": ["sane","predator","moderation"]},
{"Question": "yulib olmoq", "RightAnswer": "snatch", "options": ["saucer","sane","predator"]},
{"Question": "dovdiramoq", "RightAnswer": "stagger", "options": ["snatch","saucer","sane"]},
{"Question": "qoqilmoq", "RightAnswer": "stumble", "options": ["stagger","snatch","saucer"]},
{"Question": "tashvishda", "RightAnswer": "tense", "options": ["stumble","stagger","snatch"]},
{"Question": "dumalab ketmoq", "RightAnswer": "tumble", "options": ["tense","stumble","stagger"]},
{"Question": "tutib turmoq", "RightAnswer": "withhold", "options": ["tumble","tense","stumble"]}],	
"level 115" : [
    {"Question": "samolyot", "RightAnswer": "aircraft", "options": ["withhold","tumble","tense"]},
{"Question": "mashhur kishi", "RightAnswer": "celebrity", "options": ["aircraft","withhold","tumble"]},
{"Question": "beton", "RightAnswer": "concrete", "options": ["celebrity","aircraft","withhold"]},
{"Question": "hal qiluvchi", "RightAnswer": "decisive", "options": ["concrete","celebrity","aircraft"]},
{"Question": "hurmatli", "RightAnswer": "esteemed", "options": ["decisive","concrete","celebrity"]},
{"Question": "axloqiy", "RightAnswer": "ethical", "options": ["esteemed","decisive","concrete"]},
{"Question": "yo'qolgan", "RightAnswer": "extinct", "options": ["ethical","esteemed","decisive"]},
{"Question": "irodali", "RightAnswer": "hardy", "options": ["extinct","ethical","esteemed"]},
{"Question": "institut", "RightAnswer": "institute", "options": ["hardy","extinct","ethical"]},
{"Question": "rashk", "RightAnswer": "jealousy", "options": ["institute","hardy","extinct"]},
{"Question": "ko'chmoq", "RightAnswer": "migrate", "options": ["jealousy","institute","hardy"]},
{"Question": "tarbiyalamoq", "RightAnswer": "nurture", "options": ["migrate","jealousy","institute"]},
{"Question": "tepadan", "RightAnswer": "overhead", "options": ["nurture","migrate","jealousy"]},
{"Question": "odob-ahloq", "RightAnswer": "principle", "options": ["overhead","nurture","migrate"]},
{"Question": "qishloq", "RightAnswer": "rural", "options": ["principle","overhead","nurture"]},
{"Question": "olis", "RightAnswer": "secluded", "options": ["rural","principle","overhead"]},
{"Question": "tur", "RightAnswer": "species", "options": ["secluded","rural","principle"]},
{"Question": "botqoqlik", "RightAnswer": "swamp", "options": ["species","secluded","rural"]},
{"Question": "kezmoq", "RightAnswer": "traverse", "options": ["swamp","species","secluded"]},
{"Question": "zoologiya", "RightAnswer": "zoology", "options": ["traverse","swamp","species"]}],	
"level 116" : [
    {"Question": "taxmin", "RightAnswer": "assumption", "options": ["zoology","traverse","swamp"]},
{"Question": "arpa", "RightAnswer": "barley", "options": ["assumption","zoology","traverse"]},
{"Question": "maxluq", "RightAnswer": "beast", "options": ["barley","assumption","zoology"]},
{"Question": "polkovnik", "RightAnswer": "colonel", "options": ["beast","barley","assumption"]},
{"Question": "yuqumli", "RightAnswer": "contagious", "options": ["colonel","beast","barley"]},
{"Question": "murda", "RightAnswer": "corpse", "options": ["contagious","colonel","beast"]},
{"Question": "inqiroz", "RightAnswer": "crisis", "options": ["corpse","contagious","colonel"]},
{"Question": "davolamoq", "RightAnswer": "cure", "options": ["crisis","corpse","contagious"]},
{"Question": "qiyshaygan", "RightAnswer": "deformed", "options": ["cure","crisis","corpse"]},
{"Question": "kamsitmoq", "RightAnswer": "discriminate", "options": ["deformed","cure","crisis"]},
{"Question": "elchixona", "RightAnswer": "embassy", "options": ["discriminate","deformed","cure"]},
{"Question": "o'chirmoq", "RightAnswer": "extinguish", "options": ["embassy","discriminate","deformed"]},
{"Question": "tosh", "RightAnswer": "flint", "options": ["extinguish","embassy","discriminate"]},
{"Question": "tazyiq o'tkazmoq", "RightAnswer": "harass", "options": ["flint","extinguish","embassy"]},
{"Question": "qo'shilmoq", "RightAnswer": "integrate", "options": ["harass","flint","extinguish"]},
{"Question": "mitti", "RightAnswer": "miniature", "options": ["integrate","harass","flint"]},
{"Question": "ozuqa", "RightAnswer": "nutrition", "options": ["miniature","integrate","harass"]},
{"Question": "darhol", "RightAnswer": "promptly", "options": ["nutrition","miniature","integrate"]},
{"Question": "usta", "RightAnswer": "technician", "options": ["promptly","nutrition","miniature"]},
{"Question": "tropik mintaqa", "RightAnswer": "tropics", "options": ["technician","promptly","nutrition"]}],	
"level 117" : [
    {"Question": "foydali", "RightAnswer": "beneficial", "options": ["tropics","technician","promptly"]},
{"Question": "tug'ilgan joyi", "RightAnswer": "birthplace", "options": ["beneficial","tropics","technician"]},
{"Question": "sig'im", "RightAnswer": "capacity", "options": ["birthplace","beneficial","tropics"]},
{"Question": "qiyosiy", "RightAnswer": "comparative", "options": ["capacity","birthplace","beneficial"]},
{"Question": "keng qamrovli", "RightAnswer": "comprehensive", "options": ["comparative","capacity","birthplace"]},
{"Question": "saqlab qolmoq", "RightAnswer": "conserve", "options": ["comprehensive","comparative","capacity"]},
{"Question": "muhim", "RightAnswer": "crucial", "options": ["conserve","comprehensive","comparative"]},
{"Question": "yig'iladigan", "RightAnswer": "cumulative", "options": ["crucial","conserve","comprehensive"]},
{"Question": "qo'ymoq", "RightAnswer": "deposit", "options": ["cumulative","crucial","conserve"]},
{"Question": "tarqatmoq", "RightAnswer": "distribute", "options": ["deposit","cumulative","crucial"]},
{"Question": "ekvator", "RightAnswer": "equator", "options": ["distribute","deposit","cumulative"]},
{"Question": "ekzotik", "RightAnswer": "exotic", "options": ["equator","distribute","deposit"]},
{"Question": "federal", "RightAnswer": "federal", "options": ["exotic","equator","distribute"]},
{"Question": "shakllanish", "RightAnswer": "formation", "options": ["federal","exotic","equator"]},
{"Question": "takrorlanish", "RightAnswer": "frequency", "options": ["formation","federal","exotic"]},
{"Question": "maqsad", "RightAnswer": "objective", "options": ["frequency","formation","federal"]},
{"Question": "kislorod", "RightAnswer": "oxygen", "options": ["objective","frequency","formation"]},
{"Question": "tropik o'rmon", "RightAnswer": "rainforest", "options": ["oxygen","objective","frequency"]},
{"Question": "strategiya", "RightAnswer": "strategy", "options": ["rainforest","oxygen","objective"]},
{"Question": "o'rmonli", "RightAnswer": "wooded", "options": ["strategy","rainforest","oxygen"]}],	
"level 118" : [
    {"Question": "yordam", "RightAnswer": "avail", "options": ["wooded","strategy","rainforest"]},
{"Question": "kengaymoq", "RightAnswer": "expand", "options": ["avail","wooded","strategy"]},
{"Question": "belgilamoq", "RightAnswer": "define", "options": ["expand","avail","wooded"]},
{"Question": "qo'rqmoq", "RightAnswer": "dread", "options": ["define","expand","avail"]},
{"Question": "asosiy", "RightAnswer": "fundamental", "options": ["dread","define","expand"]},
{"Question": "dahshatli", "RightAnswer": "horrifying", "options": ["fundamental","dread","define"]},
{"Question": "ishonib bo'lmaydigan", "RightAnswer": "incredulous", "options": ["horrifying","fundamental","dread"]},
{"Question": "ko'p vaqt turmoq", "RightAnswer": "linger", "options": ["incredulous","horrifying","fundamental"]},
{"Question": "organizm", "RightAnswer": "organism", "options": ["linger","incredulous","horrifying"]},
{"Question": "soddalashtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "paraphrase", "options": ["organism","linger","incredulous"]},
{"Question": "vabo", "RightAnswer": "plague", "options": ["paraphrase","organism","linger"]},
{"Question": "hozirgi kunda", "RightAnswer": "presently", "options": ["plague","paraphrase","organism"]},
{"Question": "tasodifiy", "RightAnswer": "random", "options": ["presently","plague","paraphrase"]},
{"Question": "isyon", "RightAnswer": "riot", "options": ["random","presently","plague"]},
{"Question": "qoralamoq", "RightAnswer": "scribble", "options": ["riot","random","presently"]},
{"Question": "ziyoratgoh", "RightAnswer": "shrine", "options": ["scribble","riot","random"]},
{"Question": "yolg'izlik", "RightAnswer": "solitude", "options": ["shrine","scribble","riot"]},
{"Question": "mutlaq", "RightAnswer": "stark", "options": ["solitude","shrine","scribble"]},
{"Question": "chaqirmoq", "RightAnswer": "summon", "options": ["stark","solitude","shrine"]},
{"Question": "yomonlashmoq", "RightAnswer": "worsen", "options": ["summon","stark","solitude"]}],	
"level 119" : [
    {"Question": "avtomobil", "RightAnswer": "automobile", "options": ["worsen","summon","stark"]},
{"Question": "nomzod", "RightAnswer": "candidate", "options": ["automobile","worsen","summon"]},
{"Question": "maxfiy", "RightAnswer": "confidential", "options": ["candidate","automobile","worsen"]},
{"Question": "korporativ", "RightAnswer": "corporate", "options": ["confidential","candidate","automobile"]},
{"Question": "yaxshilamoq", "RightAnswer": "enhance", "options": ["corporate","confidential","candidate"]},
{"Question": "davr", "RightAnswer": "era", "options": ["enhance","corporate","confidential"]},
{"Question": "ko'rsatma", "RightAnswer": "guideline", "options": ["era","enhance","corporate"]},
{"Question": "qo'shmoq", "RightAnswer": "incorporate", "options": ["guideline","era","enhance"]},
{"Question": "aloqa qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "interact", "options": ["incorporate","guideline","era"]},
{"Question": "tanaffus", "RightAnswer": "interval", "options": ["interact","incorporate","guideline"]},
{"Question": "mobil", "RightAnswer": "mobile", "options": ["interval","interact","incorporate"]},
{"Question": "o'zgartirmoq", "RightAnswer": "modify", "options": ["mobile","interval","interact"]},
{"Question": "parallel", "RightAnswer": "parallel", "options": ["modify","mobile","interval"]},
{"Question": "hodisa", "RightAnswer": "phenomenon", "options": ["parallel","modify","mobile"]},
{"Question": "ifloslamoq", "RightAnswer": "pollute", "options": ["phenomenon","parallel","modify"]},
{"Question": "masxara qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "ridicule", "options": ["pollute","phenomenon","parallel"]},
{"Question": "quyosh", "RightAnswer": "solar", "options": ["ridicule","pollute","phenomenon"]},
{"Question": "hudud", "RightAnswer": "territory", "options": ["solar","ridicule","pollute"]},
{"Question": "turnir", "RightAnswer": "tournament", "options": ["territory","solar","ridicule"]},
{"Question": "transport", "RightAnswer": "transportation", "options": ["tournament","territory","solar"]}],	
"level 120" : [
    {"Question": "to'lov", "RightAnswer": "bill", "options": ["transportation","tournament","territory"]},
{"Question": "chegara", "RightAnswer": "boundary", "options": ["bill","transportation","tournament"]},
{"Question": "chalkashlik", "RightAnswer": "chaos", "options": ["boundary","bill","transportation"]},
{"Question": "tartibli", "RightAnswer": "consistent", "options": ["chaos","boundary","bill"]},
{"Question": "to'fon", "RightAnswer": "cyclone", "options": ["consistent","chaos","boundary"]},
{"Question": "umidsiz", "RightAnswer": "doomed", "options": ["cyclone","consistent","chaos"]},
{"Question": "merosxo'r", "RightAnswer": "heir", "options": ["doomed","cyclone","consistent"]},
{"Question": "jang", "RightAnswer": "martial", "options": ["heir","doomed","cyclone"]},
{"Question": "organik", "RightAnswer": "organic", "options": ["martial","heir","doomed"]},
{"Question": "parranda", "RightAnswer": "poultry", "options": ["organic","martial","heir"]},
{"Question": "hovliqmoq", "RightAnswer": "scramble", "options": ["poultry","organic","martial"]},
{"Question": "serjant", "RightAnswer": "sergeant", "options": ["scramble","poultry","organic"]},
{"Question": "haqqoniy", "RightAnswer": "sheer", "options": ["sergeant","scramble","poultry"]},
{"Question": "mulohaza", "RightAnswer": "stance", "options": ["sheer","sergeant","scramble"]},
{"Question": "telegraf", "RightAnswer": "telegraph", "options": ["stance","sheer","sergeant"]},
{"Question": "mato", "RightAnswer": "textile", "options": ["telegraph","stance","sheer"]},
{"Question": "quyun", "RightAnswer": "tornado", "options": ["textile","telegraph","stance"]},
{"Question": "to'fon", "RightAnswer": "typhoon", "options": ["tornado","textile","telegraph"]},
{"Question": "yig'lamoq", "RightAnswer": "wail", "options": ["typhoon","tornado","textile"]},
{"Question": "kiyim jovoni", "RightAnswer": "wardrobe", "options": ["wail","typhoon","tornado"]}],	
"level 121" : [
    {"Question": "taqdim qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "allot", "options": ["wardrobe","wail","typhoon"]},
{"Question": "dahshatga tushmoq", "RightAnswer": "appall", "options": ["allot","wardrobe","wail"]},
{"Question": "quti", "RightAnswer": "cache", "options": ["appall","allot","wardrobe"]},
{"Question": "qulaylik", "RightAnswer": "convenience", "options": ["cache","appall","allot"]},
{"Question": "kamchil", "RightAnswer": "dearth", "options": ["convenience","cache","appall"]},
{"Question": "qasddan", "RightAnswer": "deliberate", "options": ["dearth","convenience","cache"]},
{"Question": "dahshatli", "RightAnswer": "dire", "options": ["deliberate","dearth","convenience"]},
{"Question": "o'tmoq (vaqt)", "RightAnswer": "elapse", "options": ["dire","deliberate","dearth"]},
{"Question": "hamdardlik", "RightAnswer": "empathy", "options": ["elapse","dire","deliberate"]},
{"Question": "xayoliy", "RightAnswer": "fanciful", "options": ["empathy","elapse","dire"]},
{"Question": "xarxasha qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "gripe", "options": ["fanciful","empathy","elapse"]},
{"Question": "qiyin", "RightAnswer": "grueling", "options": ["gripe","fanciful","empathy"]},
{"Question": "zerikarli", "RightAnswer": "mundane", "options": ["grueling","gripe","fanciful"]},
{"Question": "tanlamoq", "RightAnswer": "opt", "options": ["mundane","grueling","gripe"]},
{"Question": "g'azab", "RightAnswer": "outrage", "options": ["opt","mundane","grueling"]},
{"Question": "juda kam", "RightAnswer": "paltry", "options": ["outrage","opt","mundane"]},
{"Question": "tuzatmoq", "RightAnswer": "rectify", "options": ["paltry","outrage","opt"]},
{"Question": "topqir", "RightAnswer": "resourceful", "options": ["rectify","paltry","outrage"]},
{"Question": "ozuqa", "RightAnswer": "sustenance", "options": ["resourceful","rectify","paltry"]},
{"Question": "zerikarli", "RightAnswer": "tedious", "options": ["sustenance","resourceful","rectify"]}],	
"level 122" : [
    {"Question": "abbatlik", "RightAnswer": "abbey", "options": ["tedious","sustenance","resourceful"]},
{"Question": "mo'l-ko'l", "RightAnswer": "abundant", "options": ["abbey","tedious","sustenance"]},
{"Question": "qo'shni", "RightAnswer": "adjoin", "options": ["abundant","abbey","tedious"]},
{"Question": "yetarli", "RightAnswer": "ample", "options": ["adjoin","abundant","abbey"]},
{"Question": "quruq", "RightAnswer": "arid", "options": ["ample","adjoin","abundant"]},
{"Question": "cherkov", "RightAnswer": "cathedral", "options": ["arid","ample","adjoin"]},
{"Question": "mahrum qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "deprive", "options": ["cathedral","arid","ample"]},
{"Question": "qurg'oqchilik", "RightAnswer": "drought", "options": ["deprive","cathedral","arid"]},
{"Question": "loyiq", "RightAnswer": "eligible", "options": ["drought","deprive","cathedral"]},
{"Question": "ro'za", "RightAnswer": "fast", "options": ["eligible","drought","deprive"]},
{"Question": "nolimoq", "RightAnswer": "grumble", "options": ["fast","eligible","drought"]},
{"Question": "ichkari", "RightAnswer": "inland", "options": ["grumble","fast","eligible"]},
{"Question": "namlik", "RightAnswer": "moisture", "options": ["inland","grumble","fast"]},
{"Question": "baribir", "RightAnswer": "nonetheless", "options": ["moisture","inland","grumble"]},
{"Question": "qasam", "RightAnswer": "oath", "options": ["nonetheless","moisture","inland"]},
{"Question": "dasht", "RightAnswer": "prairie", "options": ["oath","nonetheless","moisture"]},
{"Question": "yirtiq", "RightAnswer": "ragged", "options": ["prairie","oath","nonetheless"]},
{"Question": "noqulay", "RightAnswer": "rugged", "options": ["ragged","prairie","oath"]},
{"Question": "kam", "RightAnswer": "scarce", "options": ["rugged","ragged","prairie"]},
{"Question": "taxmin qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "speculate", "options": ["scarce","rugged","ragged"]}],	
"level 123" : [
    {"Question": "mantiqiy", "RightAnswer": "analytic", "options": ["speculate","scarce","rugged"]},
{"Question": "tasdiqlash", "RightAnswer": "assert", "options": ["analytic","speculate","scarce"]},
{"Question": "bo'ydoq", "RightAnswer": "bachelor", "options": ["assert","analytic","speculate"]},
{"Question": "oliy matematika", "RightAnswer": "calculus", "options": ["bachelor","assert","analytic"]},
{"Question": "samoviy", "RightAnswer": "celestial", "options": ["calculus","bachelor","assert"]},
{"Question": "aqliy", "RightAnswer": "cognitive", "options": ["celestial","calculus","bachelor"]},
{"Question": "to'qnashuv", "RightAnswer": "collision", "options": ["cognitive","celestial","calculus"]},
{"Question": "puxta", "RightAnswer": "competent", "options": ["collision","cognitive","celestial"]},
{"Question": "diplom", "RightAnswer": "diploma", "options": ["competent","collision","cognitive"]},
{"Question": "juda yaxshi", "RightAnswer": "excel", "options": ["diploma","competent","collision"]},
{"Question": "geologiya", "RightAnswer": "geology", "options": ["excel","diploma","competent"]},
{"Question": "foydalanmoq", "RightAnswer": "harness", "options": ["geology","excel","diploma"]},
{"Question": "idrok", "RightAnswer": "intellect", "options": ["harness","geology","excel"]},
{"Question": "zehnli", "RightAnswer": "keen", "options": ["intellect","harness","geology"]},
{"Question": "afsona", "RightAnswer": "mythology", "options": ["keen","intellect","harness"]},
{"Question": "fiziologiya", "RightAnswer": "physiology", "options": ["mythology","keen","intellect"]},
{"Question": "radioaktiv", "RightAnswer": "radioactive", "options": ["physiology","mythology","keen"]},
{"Question": "nisbiylik", "RightAnswer": "relativity", "options": ["radioactive","physiology","mythology"]},
{"Question": "sotsiologiya", "RightAnswer": "sociology", "options": ["relativity","radioactive","physiology"]},
{"Question": "nazariy", "RightAnswer": "theoretical", "options": ["sociology","relativity","radioactive"]}],	
"level 124" : [
    {"Question": "ma'mur", "RightAnswer": "administrator", "options": ["theoretical","sociology","relativity"]},
{"Question": "boy", "RightAnswer": "affluent", "options": ["administrator","theoretical","sociology"]},
{"Question": "taftish", "RightAnswer": "audit", "options": ["affluent","administrator","theoretical"]},
{"Question": "avtomatlashtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "automate", "options": ["audit","affluent","administrator"]},
{"Question": "pora bermoq", "RightAnswer": "bribe", "options": ["automate","audit","affluent"]},
{"Question": "poraxo'r", "RightAnswer": "corrupt", "options": ["bribe","automate","audit"]},
{"Question": "yo'q qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "dispose", "options": ["corrupt","bribe","automate"]},
{"Question": "shtabkvartirasi", "RightAnswer": "headquarters", "options": ["dispose","corrupt","bribe"]},
{"Question": "rag'batlantirmoq", "RightAnswer": "incentive", "options": ["headquarters","dispose","corrupt"]},
{"Question": "infratuzilma", "RightAnswer": "infrastructure", "options": ["incentive","headquarters","dispose"]},
{"Question": "qonun chiqarmoq", "RightAnswer": "legislate", "options": ["infrastructure","incentive","headquarters"]},
{"Question": "qonuniy", "RightAnswer": "legitimate", "options": ["legislate","infrastructure","incentive"]},
{"Question": "boshqarmoq", "RightAnswer": "manipulate", "options": ["legitimate","legislate","infrastructure"]},
{"Question": "tovar", "RightAnswer": "merchandise", "options": ["manipulate","legitimate","legislate"]},
{"Question": "chakana savdo", "RightAnswer": "retail", "options": ["merchandise","manipulate","legitimate"]},
{"Question": "daromad", "RightAnswer": "revenue", "options": ["retail","merchandise","manipulate"]},
{"Question": "axlat", "RightAnswer": "rubbish", "options": ["revenue","retail","merchandise"]},
{"Question": "yordam puli", "RightAnswer": "subsidy", "options": ["rubbish","revenue","retail"]},
{"Question": "savdo bitimi", "RightAnswer": "transaction", "options": ["subsidy","rubbish","revenue"]},
{"Question": "buzmoq", "RightAnswer": "violate", "options": ["transaction","subsidy","rubbish"]}],	
"level 125" : [
    {"Question": "baholamoq", "RightAnswer": "assess", "options": ["violate","transaction","subsidy"]},
{"Question": "ajablantirmoq", "RightAnswer": "astonish", "options": ["assess","violate","transaction"]},
{"Question": "boshlamoq", "RightAnswer": "commence", "options": ["astonish","assess","violate"]},
{"Question": "mohiyat", "RightAnswer": "essence", "options": ["commence","astonish","assess"]},
{"Question": "ajratmoq", "RightAnswer": "extract", "options": ["essence","commence","astonish"]},
{"Question": "ajoyib", "RightAnswer": "fabulous", "options": ["extract","essence","commence"]},
{"Question": "shoshqaloqlik", "RightAnswer": "haste", "options": ["fabulous","extract","essence"]},
{"Question": "impuls", "RightAnswer": "impulse", "options": ["haste","fabulous","extract"]},
{"Question": "ikkinchisi", "RightAnswer": "latter", "options": ["impulse","haste","fabulous"]},
{"Question": "molekula", "RightAnswer": "molecule", "options": ["latter","impulse","haste"]},
{"Question": "davom etayotgan", "RightAnswer": "ongoing", "options": ["molecule","latter","impulse"]},
{"Question": "farmatsevtika", "RightAnswer": "pharmaceutical", "options": ["ongoing","molecule","latter"]},
{"Question": "aniq", "RightAnswer": "precise", "options": ["pharmaceutical","ongoing","molecule"]},
{"Question": "yaqinlik", "RightAnswer": "proximity", "options": ["precise","pharmaceutical","ongoing"]},
{"Question": "oshkoralik", "RightAnswer": "publicity", "options": ["proximity","precise","pharmaceutical"]},
{"Question": "davolash vositasi", "RightAnswer": "remedy", "options": ["publicity","proximity","precise"]},
{"Question": "ahamiyat", "RightAnswer": "significance", "options": ["remedy","publicity","proximity"]},
{"Question": "navbatdagi", "RightAnswer": "subsequent", "options": ["significance","remedy","publicity"]},
{"Question": "sintetik", "RightAnswer": "synthetic", "options": ["subsequent","significance","remedy"]},
{"Question": "halokatli", "RightAnswer": "terminal", "options": ["synthetic","subsequent","significance"]}],	
"level 126" : [
    {"Question": "balandlik", "RightAnswer": "altitude", "options": ["terminal","synthetic","subsequent"]},
{"Question": "sohil bo'yi", "RightAnswer": "coastline", "options": ["altitude","terminal","synthetic"]},
{"Question": "oldini olish", "RightAnswer": "deter", "options": ["coastline","altitude","terminal"]},
{"Question": "o'ylab topmoq", "RightAnswer": "devise", "options": ["deter","coastline","altitude"]},
{"Question": "tajriba", "RightAnswer": "expertise", "options": ["devise","deter","coastline"]},
{"Question": "yoriq", "RightAnswer": "fracture", "options": ["expertise","devise","deter"]},
{"Question": "buzmoq", "RightAnswer": "impair", "options": ["fracture","expertise","devise"]},
{"Question": "amalga oshirish", "RightAnswer": "implement", "options": ["impair","fracture","expertise"]},
{"Question": "mahalliy", "RightAnswer": "indigenous", "options": ["implement","impair","fracture"]},
{"Question": "tushuncha", "RightAnswer": "insight", "options": ["indigenous","implement","impair"]},
{"Question": "oyoq-qo'l", "RightAnswer": "limb", "options": ["insight","indigenous","implement"]},
{"Question": "migren", "RightAnswer": "migraine", "options": ["limb","insight","indigenous"]},
{"Question": "nekbinlik", "RightAnswer": "optimism", "options": ["migraine","limb","insight"]},
{"Question": "g'alati", "RightAnswer": "peculiar", "options": ["optimism","migraine","limb"]},
{"Question": "malakali", "RightAnswer": "proficient", "options": ["peculiar","optimism","migraine"]},
{"Question": "izlanish", "RightAnswer": "quest", "options": ["proficient","peculiar","optimism"]},
{"Question": "tizma", "RightAnswer": "ridge", "options": ["quest","proficient","peculiar"]},
{"Question": "turmush o'rtog'i", "RightAnswer": "spouse", "options": ["ridge","quest","proficient"]},
{"Question": "surmoq", "RightAnswer": "thrust", "options": ["spouse","ridge","quest"]},
{"Question": "toqat qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "tolerate", "options": ["thrust","spouse","ridge"]}],	
"level 127" : [
    {"Question": "suvga oid", "RightAnswer": "aquatic", "options": ["tolerate","thrust","spouse"]},
{"Question": "biosfera", "RightAnswer": "biosphere", "options": ["aquatic","tolerate","thrust"]},
{"Question": "g'alati", "RightAnswer": "bizarre", "options": ["biosphere","aquatic","tolerate"]},
{"Question": "Selsiy", "RightAnswer": "Celsius", "options": ["bizarre","biosphere","aquatic"]},
{"Question": "dag'al", "RightAnswer": "coarse", "options": ["Celsius","bizarre","biosphere"]},
{"Question": "hamroh", "RightAnswer": "companion", "options": ["coarse","Celsius","bizarre"]},
{"Question": "hazm qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "digest", "options": ["companion","coarse","Celsius"]},
{"Question": "davomiylik", "RightAnswer": "duration", "options": ["digest","companion","coarse"]},
{"Question": "ekologiya", "RightAnswer": "ecology", "options": ["duration","digest","companion"]},
{"Question": "g'alaba", "RightAnswer": "feat", "options": ["ecology","duration","digest"]},
{"Question": "cheksiz", "RightAnswer": "infinite", "options": ["feat","ecology","duration"]},
{"Question": "yadro", "RightAnswer": "nucleus", "options": ["infinite","feat","ecology"]},
{"Question": "parazit", "RightAnswer": "parasite", "options": ["nucleus","infinite","feat"]},
{"Question": "taniqli", "RightAnswer": "prominent", "options": ["parasite","nucleus","infinite"]},
{"Question": "takrorlanadigan", "RightAnswer": "repetitive", "options": ["prominent","parasite","nucleus"]},
{"Question": "reproduktiv", "RightAnswer": "reproductive", "options": ["repetitive","prominent","parasite"]},
{"Question": "mo'tadil", "RightAnswer": "temperate", "options": ["reproductive","repetitive","prominent"]},
{"Question": "chidamlilik", "RightAnswer": "tolerance", "options": ["temperate","reproductive","repetitive"]},
{"Question": "boshdan kechirmoq", "RightAnswer": "undergo", "options": ["tolerance","temperate","reproductive"]},
{"Question": "zaif", "RightAnswer": "vulnerable", "options": ["undergo","tolerance","temperate"]}],	
"level 128" : [
    {"Question": "mohir", "RightAnswer": "adept", "options": ["vulnerable","undergo","tolerance"]},
{"Question": "biyobon", "RightAnswer": "barren", "options": ["adept","vulnerable","undergo"]},
{"Question": "keramika", "RightAnswer": "ceramic", "options": ["barren","adept","vulnerable"]},
{"Question": "oshxona", "RightAnswer": "culinary", "options": ["ceramic","barren","adept"]},
{"Question": "zich", "RightAnswer": "dense", "options": ["culinary","ceramic","barren"]},
{"Question": "qadr-qimmat", "RightAnswer": "dignity", "options": ["dense","culinary","ceramic"]},
{"Question": "hukmronlik qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "dominate", "options": ["dignity","dense","culinary"]},
{"Question": "yesa bo'ladigan", "RightAnswer": "edible", "options": ["dominate","dignity","dense"]},
{"Question": "g'azabli", "RightAnswer": "hostile", "options": ["edible","dominate","dignity"]},
{"Question": "qabul qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "intake", "options": ["hostile","edible","dominate"]},
{"Question": "xuddi shunday", "RightAnswer": "likewise", "options": ["intake","hostile","edible"]},
{"Question": "to'yib ovqatlanmaslik", "RightAnswer": "malnutrition", "options": ["likewise","intake","hostile"]},
{"Question": "dori-darmon", "RightAnswer": "medication", "options": ["malnutrition","likewise","intake"]},
{"Question": "noto'g'ri tushuncha", "RightAnswer": "misconception", "options": ["medication","malnutrition","likewise"]},
{"Question": "noma'lum", "RightAnswer": "obscure", "options": ["misconception","medication","malnutrition"]},
{"Question": "zulm qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "oppress", "options": ["obscure","misconception","medication"]},
{"Question": "shilmoq", "RightAnswer": "peel", "options": ["oppress","obscure","misconception"]},
{"Question": "shifokor retsepti", "RightAnswer": "prescription", "options": ["peel","oppress","obscure"]},
{"Question": "nafas olish qurilmasi", "RightAnswer": "respirator", "options": ["prescription","peel","oppress"]},
{"Question": "intilmoq", "RightAnswer": "strive", "options": ["respirator","prescription","peel"]}],	
"level 129" : [
    {"Question": "qadimiy", "RightAnswer": "archaic", "options": ["strive","respirator","prescription"]},
{"Question": "xayrixoh", "RightAnswer": "benevolent", "options": ["archaic","strive","respirator"]},
{"Question": "qalay", "RightAnswer": "brass", "options": ["benevolent","archaic","strive"]},
{"Question": "kapitalizm", "RightAnswer": "capitalism", "options": ["brass","benevolent","archaic"]},
{"Question": "qism", "RightAnswer": "component", "options": ["capitalism","brass","benevolent"]},
{"Question": "qaramlik", "RightAnswer": "dependence", "options": ["component","capitalism","brass"]},
{"Question": "kamaytirmoq", "RightAnswer": "diminish", "options": ["dependence","component","capitalism"]},
{"Question": "kamchilik", "RightAnswer": "drawback", "options": ["diminish","dependence","component"]},
{"Question": "urf", "RightAnswer": "fad", "options": ["drawback","diminish","dependence"]},
{"Question": "singdirmoq", "RightAnswer": "impose", "options": ["fad","drawback","diminish"]},
{"Question": "boshqaruv", "RightAnswer": "managerial", "options": ["impose","fad","drawback"]},
{"Question": "o'rta asrlar", "RightAnswer": "medieval", "options": ["managerial","impose","fad"]},
{"Question": "eskirgan", "RightAnswer": "obsolete", "options": ["medieval","managerial","impose"]},
{"Question": "yarim orol", "RightAnswer": "peninsula", "options": ["obsolete","medieval","managerial"]},
{"Question": "obro'-e'tibor", "RightAnswer": "prestige", "options": ["peninsula","obsolete","medieval"]},
{"Question": "mutanosiblik", "RightAnswer": "proportion", "options": ["prestige","peninsula","obsolete"]},
{"Question": "o'zgacha", "RightAnswer": "radical", "options": ["proportion","prestige","peninsula"]},
{"Question": "rad etmoq", "RightAnswer": "refute", "options": ["radical","proportion","prestige"]},
{"Question": "ajoyib", "RightAnswer": "spectacular", "options": ["refute","radical","proportion"]},
{"Question": "to'qimoq", "RightAnswer": "weave", "options": ["spectacular","refute","radical"]}],	
"level 130" : [
    {"Question": "hisobchi", "RightAnswer": "accountant", "options": ["weave","spectacular","refute"]},
{"Question": "sarmoyachi", "RightAnswer": "capitalist", "options": ["accountant","weave","spectacular"]},
{"Question": "nafrat", "RightAnswer": "contempt", "options": ["capitalist","accountant","weave"]},
{"Question": "bag'ishlamoq", "RightAnswer": "dedicate", "options": ["contempt","capitalist","accountant"]},
{"Question": "xandaq", "RightAnswer": "ditch", "options": ["dedicate","contempt","capitalist"]},
{"Question": "korxona", "RightAnswer": "enterprise", "options": ["ditch","dedicate","contempt"]},
{"Question": "nafis", "RightAnswer": "exquisite", "options": ["enterprise","ditch","dedicate"]},
{"Question": "moliyalashtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "finance", "options": ["exquisite","enterprise","ditch"]},
{"Question": "befarq", "RightAnswer": "indifferent", "options": ["finance","exquisite","enterprise"]},
{"Question": "sug'ormoq", "RightAnswer": "irrigate", "options": ["indifferent","finance","exquisite"]},
{"Question": "oshirmoq", "RightAnswer": "maximize", "options": ["irrigate","indifferent","finance"]},
{"Question": "pulga oid", "RightAnswer": "monetary", "options": ["maximize","irrigate","indifferent"]},
{"Question": "ehtiyot chorasi", "RightAnswer": "precaution", "options": ["monetary","maximize","irrigate"]},
{"Question": "dastlabki", "RightAnswer": "preliminary", "options": ["precaution","monetary","maximize"]},
{"Question": "to'yintirmoq", "RightAnswer": "saturate", "options": ["preliminary","precaution","monetary"]},
{"Question": "oddiylik", "RightAnswer": "simplicity", "options": ["saturate","preliminary","precaution"]},
{"Question": "ekmoq", "RightAnswer": "sow", "options": ["simplicity","saturate","preliminary"]},
{"Question": "soya o'somligi", "RightAnswer": "soy", "options": ["sow","simplicity","saturate"]},
{"Question": "belkurak", "RightAnswer": "spade", "options": ["soy","sow","simplicity"]},
{"Question": "kelgusi", "RightAnswer": "upcoming", "options": ["spade","soy","sow"]}],	
"level 131" : [
    {"Question": "kuchli", "RightAnswer": "acute", "options": ["upcoming","spade","soy"]},
{"Question": "tajovuz", "RightAnswer": "aggression", "options": ["acute","upcoming","spade"]},
{"Question": "ziyofat", "RightAnswer": "banquet", "options": ["aggression","acute","upcoming"]},
{"Question": "tarjimai hol", "RightAnswer": "biography", "options": ["banquet","aggression","acute"]},
{"Question": "kuchaytirish", "RightAnswer": "boost", "options": ["biography","banquet","aggression"]},
{"Question": "qarsak chalmoq", "RightAnswer": "clap", "options": ["boost","biography","banquet"]},
{"Question": "majburlamoq", "RightAnswer": "compel", "options": ["clap","boost","biography"]},
{"Question": "ustunlik", "RightAnswer": "dominance", "options": ["compel","clap","boost"]},
{"Question": "ajoyib", "RightAnswer": "gorgeous", "options": ["dominance","compel","clap"]},
{"Question": "muqarrar", "RightAnswer": "inevitable", "options": ["gorgeous","dominance","compel"]},
{"Question": "meros", "RightAnswer": "legacy", "options": ["inevitable","gorgeous","dominance"]},
{"Question": "Nodir asar, shoh asar", "RightAnswer": "masterpiece", "options": ["legacy","inevitable","gorgeous"]},
{"Question": "bir nechta", "RightAnswer": "multiple", "options": ["masterpiece","legacy","inevitable"]},
{"Question": "rivoyat qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "narrate", "options": ["multiple","masterpiece","legacy"]},
{"Question": "taniqli", "RightAnswer": "notorious", "options": ["narrate","multiple","masterpiece"]},
{"Question": "eskirgan", "RightAnswer": "outdated", "options": ["notorious","narrate","multiple"]},
{"Question": "umuman olganda", "RightAnswer": "overall", "options": ["outdated","notorious","narrate"]},
{"Question": "tarafdorlik", "RightAnswer": "partiality", "options": ["overall","outdated","notorious"]},
{"Question": "o'z-o'zidan", "RightAnswer": "spontaneous", "options": ["partiality","overall","outdated"]},
{"Question": "fazilat", "RightAnswer": "virtue", "options": ["spontaneous","partiality","overall"]}],	
"level 132" : [
    {"Question": "antropologiya", "RightAnswer": "anthropology", "options": ["virtue","spontaneous","partiality"]},
{"Question": "qarsak chalmoq", "RightAnswer": "applaud", "options": ["anthropology","virtue","spontaneous"]},
{"Question": "tayinlamoq", "RightAnswer": "appoint", "options": ["applaud","anthropology","virtue"]},
{"Question": "loyiq", "RightAnswer": "compatible", "options": ["appoint","applaud","anthropology"]},
{"Question": "mahorat", "RightAnswer": "competence", "options": ["compatible","appoint","applaud"]},
{"Question": "maslahat bermoq", "RightAnswer": "confer", "options": ["competence","compatible","appoint"]},
{"Question": "ketma-ket", "RightAnswer": "consecutive", "options": ["confer","competence","compatible"]},
{"Question": "xom", "RightAnswer": "crude", "options": ["consecutive","confer","competence"]},
{"Question": "kub", "RightAnswer": "cube", "options": ["crude","consecutive","confer"]},
{"Question": "mulohaza", "RightAnswer": "feedback", "options": ["cube","crude","consecutive"]},
{"Question": "beparvolik", "RightAnswer": "ignorance", "options": ["feedback","cube","crude"]},
{"Question": "erkakcha", "RightAnswer": "masculine", "options": ["ignorance","feedback","cube"]},
{"Question": "yodgorlik", "RightAnswer": "monument", "options": ["masculine","ignorance","feedback"]},
{"Question": "baquvvat", "RightAnswer": "muscular", "options": ["monument","masculine","ignorance"]},
{"Question": "holat", "RightAnswer": "posture", "options": ["muscular","monument","masculine"]},
{"Question": "o'rnatmoq", "RightAnswer": "situate", "options": ["posture","muscular","monument"]},
{"Question": "nazorat qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "supervise", "options": ["situate","posture","muscular"]},
{"Question": "simmetriya", "RightAnswer": "symmetry", "options": ["supervise","situate","posture"]},
{"Question": "tatuirovka", "RightAnswer": "tattoo", "options": ["symmetry","supervise","situate"]},
{"Question": "bakalavr", "RightAnswer": "undergraduate", "options": ["tattoo","symmetry","supervise"]}],	
"level 133" : [
    {"Question": "ariq", "RightAnswer": "brook", "options": ["undergraduate","tattoo","symmetry"]},
{"Question": "taminlamoq", "RightAnswer": "cater", "options": ["brook","undergraduate","tattoo"]},
{"Question": "xushmuomala", "RightAnswer": "considerate", "options": ["cater","brook","undergraduate"]},
{"Question": "iste'mol", "RightAnswer": "consumption", "options": ["considerate","cater","brook"]},
{"Question": "mezonlar", "RightAnswer": "criteria", "options": ["consumption","considerate","cater"]},
{"Question": "qobiq", "RightAnswer": "crust", "options": ["criteria","consumption","considerate"]},
{"Question": "uyaltirmoq", "RightAnswer": "degrade", "options": ["crust","criteria","consumption"]},
{"Question": "huquq bermoq", "RightAnswer": "entitle", "options": ["degrade","crust","criteria"]},
{"Question": "kuzatmoq", "RightAnswer": "escort", "options": ["entitle","degrade","crust"]},
{"Question": "tashqi", "RightAnswer": "external", "options": ["escort","entitle","degrade"]},
{"Question": "qulaylik", "RightAnswer": "facility", "options": ["external","escort","entitle"]},
{"Question": "qobiliyat", "RightAnswer": "faculty", "options": ["facility","external","escort"]},
{"Question": "uyum", "RightAnswer": "heap", "options": ["faculty","facility","external"]},
{"Question": "yarim shar", "RightAnswer": "hemisphere", "options": ["heap","faculty","facility"]},
{"Question": "ovchi it", "RightAnswer": "hound", "options": ["hemisphere","heap","faculty"]},
{"Question": "shaxssiz", "RightAnswer": "impersonal", "options": ["hound","hemisphere","heap"]},
{"Question": "bezak", "RightAnswer": "ornament", "options": ["impersonal","hound","hemisphere"]},
{"Question": "piyoda", "RightAnswer": "pedestrian", "options": ["ornament","impersonal","hound"]},
{"Question": "muqaddas joy", "RightAnswer": "sanctuary", "options": ["pedestrian","ornament","impersonal"]},
{"Question": "tomoshabin", "RightAnswer": "spectator", "options": ["sanctuary","pedestrian","ornament"]}],	
"level 134" : [
    {"Question": "afzallik", "RightAnswer": "asset", "options": ["spectator","sanctuary","pedestrian"]},
{"Question": "jihat", "RightAnswer": "aspect", "options": ["asset","spectator","sanctuary"]},
{"Question": "Brayl shrifti", "RightAnswer": "Braille", "options": ["aspect","asset","spectator"]},
{"Question": "kurtak", "RightAnswer": "bud", "options": ["Braille","aspect","asset"]},
{"Question": "muvofiqlashtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "coordinate", "options": ["bud","Braille","aspect"]},
{"Question": "inkor qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "disprove", "options": ["coordinate","bud","Braille"]},
{"Question": "gumanitar", "RightAnswer": "humanitarian", "options": ["disprove","coordinate","bud"]},
{"Question": "faraz", "RightAnswer": "hypothesis", "options": ["humanitarian","disprove","coordinate"]},
{"Question": "kechinma", "RightAnswer": "imprint", "options": ["hypothesis","humanitarian","disprove"]},
{"Question": "informatsion", "RightAnswer": "informative", "options": ["imprint","hypothesis","humanitarian"]},
{"Question": "ko'rishga oid", "RightAnswer": "optic", "options": ["informative","imprint","hypothesis"]},
{"Question": "tushuncha", "RightAnswer": "premise", "options": ["optic","informative","imprint"]},
{"Question": "tokcha", "RightAnswer": "rack", "options": ["premise","optic","informative"]},
{"Question": "Uyg'onish davri", "RightAnswer": "Renaissance", "options": ["rack","premise","optic"]},
{"Question": "hurmat qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "revere", "options": ["Renaissance","rack","premise"]},
{"Question": "bir vaqtda", "RightAnswer": "simultaneous", "options": ["revere","Renaissance","rack"]},
{"Question": "shubhachi", "RightAnswer": "skeptic", "options": ["simultaneous","revere","Renaissance"]},
{"Question": "fazoviy", "RightAnswer": "spatial", "options": ["skeptic","simultaneous","revere"]},
{"Question": "tasvirlamoq", "RightAnswer": "specify", "options": ["spatial","skeptic","simultaneous"]},
{"Question": "mum", "RightAnswer": "wax", "options": ["specify","spatial","skeptic"]}],	
"level 135" : [
    {"Question": "aksessuar", "RightAnswer": "accessory", "options": ["wax","specify","spatial"]},
{"Question": "egalik", "RightAnswer": "acquisition", "options": ["accessory","wax","specify"]},
{"Question": "mos keladigan", "RightAnswer": "adequate", "options": ["acquisition","accessory","wax"]},
{"Question": "karton", "RightAnswer": "cardboard", "options": ["adequate","acquisition","accessory"]},
{"Question": "jumboq", "RightAnswer": "dilemma", "options": ["cardboard","adequate","acquisition"]},
{"Question": "izchil", "RightAnswer": "elaborate", "options": ["dilemma","cardboard","adequate"]},
{"Question": "osonlashtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "facilitate", "options": ["elaborate","dilemma","cardboard"]},
{"Question": "flot", "RightAnswer": "fleet", "options": ["facilitate","elaborate","dilemma"]},
{"Question": "panjara", "RightAnswer": "grid", "options": ["fleet","facilitate","elaborate"]},
{"Question": "chetdan sotib olmoq", "RightAnswer": "import", "options": ["grid","fleet","facilitate"]},
{"Question": "xulosa qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "infer", "options": ["import","grid","fleet"]},
{"Question": "shishirmoq", "RightAnswer": "inflate", "options": ["infer","import","grid"]},
{"Question": "tug'ma", "RightAnswer": "innate", "options": ["inflate","infer","import"]},
{"Question": "marmar", "RightAnswer": "marble", "options": ["innate","inflate","infer"]},
{"Question": "machta", "RightAnswer": "mast", "options": ["marble","innate","inflate"]},
{"Question": "ko'ngil aynishi", "RightAnswer": "nausea", "options": ["mast","marble","innate"]},
{"Question": "dengiz kuchlari", "RightAnswer": "naval", "options": ["nausea","mast","marble"]},
{"Question": "qop", "RightAnswer": "pouch", "options": ["naval","nausea","mast"]},
{"Question": "to'yingan", "RightAnswer": "saturated", "options": ["pouch","naval","nausea"]},
{"Question": "yangilangan", "RightAnswer": "update", "options": ["saturated","pouch","naval"]}],	
"level 136" : [
    {"Question": "giyohvand", "RightAnswer": "addict", "options": ["update","saturated","pouch"]},
{"Question": "arxeologik", "RightAnswer": "archeological", "options": ["addict","update","saturated"]},
{"Question": "arxeologiya", "RightAnswer": "archeology", "options": ["archeological","addict","update"]},
{"Question": "aqliy hujum", "RightAnswer": "brainstorm", "options": ["archeology","archeological","addict"]},
{"Question": "byudjet", "RightAnswer": "budget", "options": ["brainstorm","archeology","archeological"]},
{"Question": "tartibsiz", "RightAnswer": "chaotic", "options": ["budget","brainstorm","archeology"]},
{"Question": "takidlamoq", "RightAnswer": "cite", "options": ["chaotic","budget","brainstorm"]},
{"Question": "mos kelmoq", "RightAnswer": "correspond", "options": ["cite","chaotic","budget"]},
{"Question": "hovli", "RightAnswer": "courtyard", "options": ["correspond","cite","chaotic"]},
{"Question": "mulk", "RightAnswer": "estate", "options": ["courtyard","correspond","cite"]},
{"Question": "firibgarlik", "RightAnswer": "fraud", "options": ["estate","courtyard","correspond"]},
{"Question": "vodorod", "RightAnswer": "hydrogen", "options": ["fraud","estate","courtyard"]},
{"Question": "vijdon", "RightAnswer": "integrity", "options": ["hydrogen","fraud","estate"]},
{"Question": "to'qimoq", "RightAnswer": "knit", "options": ["integrity","hydrogen","fraud"]},
{"Question": "mulohaza", "RightAnswer": "outlook", "options": ["knit","integrity","hydrogen"]},
{"Question": "parashyut", "RightAnswer": "parachute", "options": ["outlook","knit","integrity"]},
{"Question": "tarixdan oldingi", "RightAnswer": "prehistoric", "options": ["parachute","outlook","knit"]},
{"Question": "tarafdor", "RightAnswer": "proponent", "options": ["prehistoric","parachute","outlook"]},
{"Question": "takomillashtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "refine", "options": ["proponent","prehistoric","parachute"]},
{"Question": "cheklamoq", "RightAnswer": "restrict", "options": ["refine","proponent","prehistoric"]}],	
"level 137" : [
    {"Question": "advokat", "RightAnswer": "attorney", "options": ["restrict","refine","proponent"]},
{"Question": "surunkali", "RightAnswer": "chronic", "options": ["attorney","restrict","refine"]},
{"Question": "intizom", "RightAnswer": "discipline", "options": ["chronic","attorney","restrict"]},
{"Question": "donor", "RightAnswer": "donor", "options": ["discipline","chronic","attorney"]},
{"Question": "o'rtoq", "RightAnswer": "fellow", "options": ["donor","discipline","chronic"]},
{"Question": "g'iybat", "RightAnswer": "gossip", "options": ["fellow","donor","discipline"]},
{"Question": "bitirmoq", "RightAnswer": "graduate", "options": ["gossip","fellow","donor"]},
{"Question": "grafiti", "RightAnswer": "graffiti", "options": ["graduate","gossip","fellow"]},
{"Question": "vasiy", "RightAnswer": "guardian", "options": ["graffiti","graduate","gossip"]},
{"Question": "ayblamoq", "RightAnswer": "implicate", "options": ["guardian","graffiti","graduate"]},
{"Question": "qarindosh", "RightAnswer": "kin", "options": ["implicate","guardian","graffiti"]},
{"Question": "hakam", "RightAnswer": "referee", "options": ["kin","implicate","guardian"]},
{"Question": "uzmoq", "RightAnswer": "sever", "options": ["referee","kin","implicate"]},
{"Question": "dasta", "RightAnswer": "shaft", "options": ["sever","referee","kin"]},
{"Question": "pichoq urmoq", "RightAnswer": "stab", "options": ["shaft","sever","referee"]},
{"Question": "stimul", "RightAnswer": "stimulus", "options": ["stab","shaft","sever"]},
{"Question": "shubha", "RightAnswer": "suspicion", "options": ["stimulus","stab","shaft"]},
{"Question": "tugatmoq", "RightAnswer": "terminate", "options": ["suspicion","stimulus","stab"]},
{"Question": "mavzu", "RightAnswer": "theme", "options": ["terminate","suspicion","stimulus"]},
{"Question": "o'qish puli", "RightAnswer": "tuition", "options": ["theme","terminate","suspicion"]}],	
"level 138" : [
    {"Question": "tajovuzkor", "RightAnswer": "aggressive", "options": ["tuition","theme","terminate"]},
{"Question": "amnistiya", "RightAnswer": "amnesty", "options": ["aggressive","tuition","theme"]},
{"Question": "maydon", "RightAnswer": "arena", "options": ["amnesty","aggressive","tuition"]},
{"Question": "auditoriya", "RightAnswer": "auditorium", "options": ["arena","amnesty","aggressive"]},
{"Question": "asir", "RightAnswer": "captive", "options": ["auditorium","arena","amnesty"]},
{"Question": "jang", "RightAnswer": "combat", "options": ["captive","auditorium","arena"]},
{"Question": "oddiy", "RightAnswer": "commonplace", "options": ["combat","captive","auditorium"]},
{"Question": "hudud", "RightAnswer": "compound", "options": ["commonplace","combat","captive"]},
{"Question": "bo'linma", "RightAnswer": "corps", "options": ["compound","commonplace","combat"]},
{"Question": "chalg'itmoq", "RightAnswer": "distract", "options": ["corps","compound","commonplace"]},
{"Question": "soqov", "RightAnswer": "dumb", "options": ["distract","corps","compound"]},
{"Question": "dushman", "RightAnswer": "foe", "options": ["dumb","distract","corps"]},
{"Question": "buzmoq", "RightAnswer": "hack", "options": ["foe","dumb","distract"]},
{"Question": "meditatsiya qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "meditate", "options": ["hack","foe","dumb"]},
{"Question": "tilmoq", "RightAnswer": "nick", "options": ["meditate","hack","foe"]},
{"Question": "qo'zg'atmoq", "RightAnswer": "provoke", "options": ["nick","meditate","hack"]},
{"Question": "dunyo", "RightAnswer": "realm", "options": ["provoke","nick","meditate"]},
{"Question": "hukmronlik", "RightAnswer": "reign", "options": ["realm","provoke","nick"]},
{"Question": "zang", "RightAnswer": "rust", "options": ["reign","realm","provoke"]},
{"Question": "muqaddas", "RightAnswer": "sacred", "options": ["rust","reign","realm"]}],	
"level 139" : [
    {"Question": "muvofiq", "RightAnswer": "accordingly", "options": ["sacred","rust","reign"]},
{"Question": "langar", "RightAnswer": "anchor", "options": ["accordingly","sacred","rust"]},
{"Question": "suzgich", "RightAnswer": "buoy", "options": ["anchor","accordingly","sacred"]},
{"Question": "falokat", "RightAnswer": "catastrophe", "options": ["buoy","anchor","accordingly"]},
{"Question": "kontekst", "RightAnswer": "context", "options": ["catastrophe","buoy","anchor"]},
{"Question": "tasvirlamoq", "RightAnswer": "designate", "options": ["context","catastrophe","buoy"]},
{"Question": "aldamoq", "RightAnswer": "distort", "options": ["designate","context","catastrophe"]},
{"Question": "port", "RightAnswer": "dock", "options": ["distort","designate","context"]},
{"Question": "oldi", "RightAnswer": "fore", "options": ["dock","distort","designate"]},
{"Question": "tez-tez", "RightAnswer": "frequent", "options": ["fore","dock","distort"]},
{"Question": "haqiqiy", "RightAnswer": "genuine", "options": ["frequent","fore","dock"]},
{"Question": "surtma", "RightAnswer": "grease", "options": ["genuine","frequent","fore"]},
{"Question": "murakkab", "RightAnswer": "intricate", "options": ["grease","genuine","frequent"]},
{"Question": "yumshatmoq", "RightAnswer": "offset", "options": ["intricate","grease","genuine"]},
{"Question": "qoplamoq", "RightAnswer": "overlap", "options": ["offset","intricate","grease"]},
{"Question": "tezlashtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "precipitate", "options": ["overlap","offset","intricate"]},
{"Question": "ishlatilgan", "RightAnswer": "secondhand", "options": ["precipitate","overlap","offset"]},
{"Question": "tuynuk", "RightAnswer": "slot", "options": ["secondhand","precipitate","overlap"]},
{"Question": "botirmoq", "RightAnswer": "submerge", "options": ["slot","secondhand","precipitate"]},
{"Question": "reja", "RightAnswer": "tactic", "options": ["submerge","slot","secondhand"]}],	
"level 140" : [
    {"Question": "yig'ma", "RightAnswer": "aggregate", "options": ["tactic","submerge","slot"]},
{"Question": "antibiotik", "RightAnswer": "antibiotic", "options": ["aggregate","tactic","submerge"]},
{"Question": "o'tkazgich", "RightAnswer": "circuit", "options": ["antibiotic","aggregate","tactic"]},
{"Question": "qo'shimcha", "RightAnswer": "complement", "options": ["circuit","antibiotic","aggregate"]},
{"Question": "siqmoq", "RightAnswer": "compress", "options": ["complement","circuit","antibiotic"]},
{"Question": "ma'lumotlar bazasi", "RightAnswer": "database", "options": ["compress","complement","circuit"]},
{"Question": "teng", "RightAnswer": "equivalent", "options": ["database","compress","complement"]},
{"Question": "immunitetga ega", "RightAnswer": "immune", "options": ["equivalent","database","compress"]},
{"Question": "kiritma", "RightAnswer": "input", "options": ["immune","equivalent","database"]},
{"Question": "yaqin", "RightAnswer": "intimate", "options": ["input","immune","equivalent"]},
{"Question": "magnit", "RightAnswer": "magnet", "options": ["intimate","input","immune"]},
{"Question": "metabolizm", "RightAnswer": "metabolism", "options": ["magnet","intimate","input"]},
{"Question": "mikrochip", "RightAnswer": "microchip", "options": ["metabolism","magnet","intimate"]},
{"Question": "bosqich", "RightAnswer": "phase", "options": ["microchip","metabolism","magnet"]},
{"Question": "chimchilamoq", "RightAnswer": "pinch", "options": ["phase","microchip","metabolism"]},
{"Question": "keng tarqalgan", "RightAnswer": "prevalent", "options": ["pinch","phase","microchip"]},
{"Question": "kvant", "RightAnswer": "quantum", "options": ["prevalent","pinch","phase"]},
{"Question": "nisbat", "RightAnswer": "ratio", "options": ["quantum","prevalent","pinch"]},
{"Question": "spiral", "RightAnswer": "spiral", "options": ["ratio","quantum","prevalent"]},
{"Question": "virusli", "RightAnswer": "viral", "options": ["spiral","ratio","quantum"]}],	
"level 141" : [
    {"Question": "hayratda qolmoq", "RightAnswer": "astounded", "options": ["viral","spiral","ratio"]},
{"Question": "xususiyat", "RightAnswer": "attribute", "options": ["astounded","viral","spiral"]},
{"Question": "ikki tilli", "RightAnswer": "bilingual", "options": ["attribute","astounded","viral"]},
{"Question": "nusxa", "RightAnswer": "clone", "options": ["bilingual","attribute","astounded"]},
{"Question": "so'zlashuv", "RightAnswer": "colloquial", "options": ["clone","bilingual","attribute"]},
{"Question": "kosmetika", "RightAnswer": "cosmetics", "options": ["colloquial","clone","bilingual"]},
{"Question": "tez harakatlanmoq", "RightAnswer": "dash", "options": ["cosmetics","colloquial","clone"]},
{"Question": "nafrat", "RightAnswer": "disgust", "options": ["dash","cosmetics","colloquial"]},
{"Question": "yorqin", "RightAnswer": "fluorescent", "options": ["disgust","dash","cosmetics"]},
{"Question": "g'azablangan", "RightAnswer": "furious", "options": ["fluorescent","disgust","dash"]},
{"Question": "ko'rfaz", "RightAnswer": "gulf", "options": ["furious","fluorescent","disgust"]},
{"Question": "gumanitar fanlar", "RightAnswer": "humanities", "options": ["gulf","furious","fluorescent"]},
{"Question": "tugun", "RightAnswer": "knot", "options": ["humanities","gulf","furious"]},
{"Question": "tilshunos", "RightAnswer": "linguist", "options": ["knot","humanities","gulf"]},
{"Question": "ishtirokchi", "RightAnswer": "participant", "options": ["linguist","knot","humanities"]},
{"Question": "ishonarli", "RightAnswer": "plausible", "options": ["participant","linguist","knot"]},
{"Question": "marosim", "RightAnswer": "ritual", "options": ["plausible","participant","linguist"]},
{"Question": "qardosh", "RightAnswer": "sibling", "options": ["ritual","plausible","participant"]},
{"Question": "oriq", "RightAnswer": "skinny", "options": ["sibling","ritual","plausible"]},
{"Question": "noaniq", "RightAnswer": "vague", "options": ["skinny","sibling","ritual"]}],	
"level 142" : [
    {"Question": "kislota", "RightAnswer": "acid", "options": ["vague","skinny","sibling"]},
{"Question": "ma'muriyat", "RightAnswer": "administration", "options": ["acid","vague","skinny"]},
{"Question": "ma'muriy", "RightAnswer": "administrative", "options": ["administration","acid","vague"]},
{"Question": "biotexnologiya", "RightAnswer": "biotechnology", "options": ["administrative","administration","acid"]},
{"Question": "xolesterin", "RightAnswer": "cholesterol", "options": ["biotechnology","administrative","administration"]},
{"Question": "ittifoq", "RightAnswer": "coalition", "options": ["cholesterol","biotechnology","administrative"]},
{"Question": "aldamchi", "RightAnswer": "deceptive", "options": ["coalition","cholesterol","biotechnology"]},
{"Question": "diabet", "RightAnswer": "diabetes", "options": ["deceptive","coalition","cholesterol"]},
{"Question": "yo'q qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "eliminate", "options": ["diabetes","deceptive","coalition"]},
{"Question": "eroziya", "RightAnswer": "erosion", "options": ["eliminate","diabetes","deceptive"]},
{"Question": "axloq", "RightAnswer": "ethics", "options": ["erosion","eliminate","diabetes"]},
{"Question": "aniq", "RightAnswer": "explicit", "options": ["ethics","erosion","eliminate"]},
{"Question": "ramka", "RightAnswer": "framework", "options": ["explicit","ethics","erosion"]},
{"Question": "ishlab chiqarmoq", "RightAnswer": "manufacture", "options": ["framework","explicit","ethics"]},
{"Question": "mexanizm", "RightAnswer": "mechanism", "options": ["manufacture","framework","explicit"]},
{"Question": "minimallashtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "minimize", "options": ["mechanism","manufacture","framework"]},
{"Question": "nektar", "RightAnswer": "nectar", "options": ["minimize","mechanism","manufacture"]},
{"Question": "tushuncha", "RightAnswer": "notion", "options": ["nectar","minimize","mechanism"]},
{"Question": "moyil", "RightAnswer": "prone", "options": ["notion","nectar","minimize"]},
{"Question": "to'g'ri", "RightAnswer": "straightforward", "options": ["prone","notion","nectar"]}],	
"level 143" : [
    {"Question": "ulkan", "RightAnswer": "astronomical", "options": ["straightforward","prone","notion"]},
{"Question": "atom", "RightAnswer": "atom", "options": ["astronomical","straightforward","prone"]},
{"Question": "kenglik", "RightAnswer": "breadth", "options": ["atom","astronomical","straightforward"]},
{"Question": "atrofi", "RightAnswer": "circumference", "options": ["breadth","atom","astronomical"]},
{"Question": "kometa", "RightAnswer": "comet", "options": ["circumference","breadth","atom"]},
{"Question": "krater", "RightAnswer": "crater", "options": ["comet","circumference","breadth"]},
{"Question": "yarim oy", "RightAnswer": "crescent", "options": ["crater","comet","circumference"]},
{"Question": "qoldiqlar", "RightAnswer": "debris", "options": ["crescent","crater","comet"]},
{"Question": "umidsizlik", "RightAnswer": "despair", "options": ["debris","crescent","crater"]},
{"Question": "o'rnatmoq", "RightAnswer": "embed", "options": ["despair","debris","crescent"]},
{"Question": "parcha", "RightAnswer": "fragment", "options": ["embed","despair","debris"]},
{"Question": "galaktika", "RightAnswer": "galaxy", "options": ["fragment","embed","despair"]},
{"Question": "ulkan", "RightAnswer": "gigantic", "options": ["galaxy","fragment","embed"]},
{"Question": "xira", "RightAnswer": "gloom", "options": ["gigantic","galaxy","fragment"]},
{"Question": "nurlanmoq", "RightAnswer": "radiate", "options": ["gloom","gigantic","galaxy"]},
{"Question": "sag'imoq", "RightAnswer": "roam", "options": ["radiate","gloom","gigantic"]},
{"Question": "yolg'iz", "RightAnswer": "solitary", "options": ["roam","radiate","gloom"]},
{"Question": "spektr", "RightAnswer": "spectrum", "options": ["solitary","roam","radiate"]},
{"Question": "sfera", "RightAnswer": "sphere", "options": ["spectrum","solitary","roam"]},
{"Question": "holat", "RightAnswer": "status", "options": ["sphere","spectrum","solitary"]}],	
"level 144" : [
    {"Question": "bankrot", "RightAnswer": "bankrupt", "options": ["status","sphere","spectrum"]},
{"Question": "itoat qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "conform", "options": ["bankrupt","status","sphere"]},
{"Question": "ishga olmoq", "RightAnswer": "employ", "options": ["conform","bankrupt","status"]},
{"Question": "quvib yubormoq", "RightAnswer": "expel", "options": ["employ","conform","bankrupt"]},
{"Question": "kengaytma", "RightAnswer": "extension", "options": ["expel","employ","conform"]},
{"Question": "kelayotgan", "RightAnswer": "forthcoming", "options": ["extension","expel","employ"]},
{"Question": "jihozlamoq", "RightAnswer": "furnish", "options": ["forthcoming","extension","expel"]},
{"Question": "gigiena", "RightAnswer": "hygiene", "options": ["furnish","forthcoming","extension"]},
{"Question": "gigienik", "RightAnswer": "hygienic", "options": ["hygiene","furnish","forthcoming"]},
{"Question": "uy egasi", "RightAnswer": "landlord", "options": ["hygienic","hygiene","furnish"]},
{"Question": "ijaraga bermoq", "RightAnswer": "lease", "options": ["landlord","hygienic","hygiene"]},
{"Question": "majburiy", "RightAnswer": "mandatory", "options": ["lease","landlord","hygienic"]},
{"Question": "tuzatmoq", "RightAnswer": "mend", "options": ["mandatory","lease","landlord"]},
{"Question": "ipoteka", "RightAnswer": "mortgage", "options": ["mend","mandatory","lease"]},
{"Question": "xodimlar", "RightAnswer": "personnel", "options": ["mortgage","mend","mandatory"]},
{"Question": "quvurlar", "RightAnswer": "plumbing", "options": ["personnel","mortgage","mend"]},
{"Question": "ijarachi", "RightAnswer": "tenant", "options": ["plumbing","personnel","mortgage"]},
{"Question": "ommalashgan", "RightAnswer": "trendy", "options": ["tenant","plumbing","personnel"]},
{"Question": "taminot", "RightAnswer": "utility", "options": ["trendy","tenant","plumbing"]},
{"Question": "shu bilan", "RightAnswer": "whereby", "options": ["utility","trendy","tenant"]}],	
"level 145" : [
    {"Question": "estetik", "RightAnswer": "aesthetic", "options": ["whereby","utility","trendy"]},
{"Question": "dimog'dor", "RightAnswer": "arrogant", "options": ["aesthetic","whereby","utility"]},
{"Question": "moyillik", "RightAnswer": "bias", "options": ["arrogant","aesthetic","whereby"]},
{"Question": "kanyon", "RightAnswer": "canyon", "options": ["bias","arrogant","aesthetic"]},
{"Question": "soy", "RightAnswer": "creek", "options": ["canyon","bias","arrogant"]},
{"Question": "burg'ulagich", "RightAnswer": "drill", "options": ["creek","canyon","bias"]},
{"Question": "boshliq", "RightAnswer": "executive", "options": ["drill","creek","canyon"]},
{"Question": "charchoq", "RightAnswer": "fatigue", "options": ["executive","drill","creek"]},
{"Question": "ko'tarilmoq", "RightAnswer": "incline", "options": ["fatigue","executive","drill"]},
{"Question": "yomon", "RightAnswer": "nasty", "options": ["incline","fatigue","executive"]},
{"Question": "sezmoq", "RightAnswer": "perceive", "options": ["nasty","incline","fatigue"]},
{"Question": "primat", "RightAnswer": "primate", "options": ["perceive","nasty","incline"]},
{"Question": "ibtidoiy", "RightAnswer": "primitive", "options": ["primate","perceive","nasty"]},
{"Question": "stereotip", "RightAnswer": "stereotype", "options": ["primitive","primate","perceive"]},
{"Question": "yopishqoq", "RightAnswer": "sticky", "options": ["stereotype","primitive","primate"]},
{"Question": "termit", "RightAnswer": "termite", "options": ["sticky","stereotype","primitive"]},
{"Question": "natijada", "RightAnswer": "thereby", "options": ["termite","sticky","stereotype"]},
{"Question": "iz", "RightAnswer": "trail", "options": ["thereby","termite","sticky"]},
{"Question": "novda", "RightAnswer": "twig", "options": ["trail","thereby","termite"]},
{"Question": "farovonlik", "RightAnswer": "welfare", "options": ["twig","trail","thereby"]}],	
"level 146" : [
    {"Question": "nomidan", "RightAnswer": "behalf", "options": ["welfare","twig","trail"]},
{"Question": "silkitmoq", "RightAnswer": "flap", "options": ["behalf","welfare","twig"]},
{"Question": "muzlik", "RightAnswer": "glacier", "options": ["flap","behalf","welfare"]},
{"Question": "globus", "RightAnswer": "globe", "options": ["glacier","flap","behalf"]},
{"Question": "gorizontal", "RightAnswer": "horizontal", "options": ["globe","glacier","flap"]},
{"Question": "g'o'ng'illamoq", "RightAnswer": "hum", "options": ["horizontal","globe","glacier"]},
{"Question": "taminot", "RightAnswer": "inventory", "options": ["hum","horizontal","globe"]},
{"Question": "ichki", "RightAnswer": "inward", "options": ["inventory","hum","horizontal"]},
{"Question": "non", "RightAnswer": "loaf", "options": ["inward","inventory","hum"]},
{"Question": "folbin", "RightAnswer": "oracle", "options": ["loaf","inward","inventory"]},
{"Question": "aylanmoq", "RightAnswer": "orbit", "options": ["oracle","loaf","inward"]},
{"Question": "umumiy ko'rinish", "RightAnswer": "overview", "options": ["orbit","oracle","loaf"]},
{"Question": "oldindan ko'rish", "RightAnswer": "preview", "options": ["overview","orbit","oracle"]},
{"Question": "oldingi", "RightAnswer": "previous", "options": ["preview","overview","orbit"]},
{"Question": "ta'minlash", "RightAnswer": "provide", "options": ["previous","preview","overview"]},
{"Question": "takrorlanmoq", "RightAnswer": "recur", "options": ["provide","previous","preview"]},
{"Question": "kerakli", "RightAnswer": "relevant", "options": ["recur","provide","previous"]},
{"Question": "marosim", "RightAnswer": "rite", "options": ["relevant","recur","provide"]},
{"Question": "to'xtatib turmoq", "RightAnswer": "stall", "options": ["rite","relevant","recur"]},
{"Question": "g'ayritabiiy", "RightAnswer": "supernatural", "options": ["stall","rite","relevant"]}],	
"level 147" : [
    {"Question": "moslashmoq", "RightAnswer": "adapt", "options": ["supernatural","stall","rite"]},
{"Question": "biologik", "RightAnswer": "biological", "options": ["adapt","supernatural","stall"]},
{"Question": "hujayrali", "RightAnswer": "cellular", "options": ["biological","adapt","supernatural"]},
{"Question": "faol", "RightAnswer": "dynamic", "options": ["cellular","biological","adapt"]},
{"Question": "xayol", "RightAnswer": "fantasy", "options": ["dynamic","cellular","biological"]},
{"Question": "irsiyat", "RightAnswer": "heredity", "options": ["fantasy","dynamic","cellular"]},
{"Question": "ichki", "RightAnswer": "internal", "options": ["heredity","fantasy","dynamic"]},
{"Question": "minimal", "RightAnswer": "minimal", "options": ["internal","heredity","fantasy"]},
{"Question": "kashfiyotchi", "RightAnswer": "pioneer", "options": ["minimal","internal","heredity"]},
{"Question": "tayinlamoq", "RightAnswer": "prescribe", "options": ["pioneer","minimal","internal"]},
{"Question": "tegishli", "RightAnswer": "respective", "options": ["prescribe","pioneer","minimal"]},
{"Question": "jonlantirmoq", "RightAnswer": "revive", "options": ["respective","prescribe","pioneer"]},
{"Question": "qattiq", "RightAnswer": "rigid", "options": ["revive","respective","prescribe"]},
{"Question": "ketma-ketlik", "RightAnswer": "sequence", "options": ["rigid","revive","respective"]},
{"Question": "o'rnini bosmoq", "RightAnswer": "substitute", "options": ["sequence","rigid","revive"]},
{"Question": "jarroh", "RightAnswer": "surgeon", "options": ["substitute","sequence","rigid"]},
{"Question": "terapiya", "RightAnswer": "therapy", "options": ["surgeon","substitute","sequence"]},
{"Question": "ko'chirmoq", "RightAnswer": "transfer", "options": ["therapy","surgeon","substitute"]},
{"Question": "o'tish", "RightAnswer": "transition", "options": ["transfer","therapy","surgeon"]},
{"Question": "a'zo ko'chirish", "RightAnswer": "transplant", "options": ["transition","transfer","therapy"]}],	
"level 148" : [
    {"Question": "akvarium", "RightAnswer": "aquarium", "options": ["transplant","transition","transfer"]},
{"Question": "o'zidan-o'zi", "RightAnswer": "arbitrary", "options": ["aquarium","transplant","transition"]},
{"Question": "tarjimai hol", "RightAnswer": "autobiography", "options": ["arbitrary","aquarium","transplant"]},
{"Question": "odatiy holat", "RightAnswer": "convention", "options": ["autobiography","arbitrary","aquarium"]},
{"Question": "mehribon", "RightAnswer": "gracious", "options": ["convention","autobiography","arbitrary"]},
{"Question": "takomillashtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "improve", "options": ["gracious","convention","autobiography"]},
{"Question": "himoyalamoq", "RightAnswer": "insulate", "options": ["improve","gracious","convention"]},
{"Question": "qiziqish uyg'otmoq", "RightAnswer": "intrigue", "options": ["insulate","improve","gracious"]},
{"Question": "uzoq umr", "RightAnswer": "longevity", "options": ["intrigue","insulate","improve"]},
{"Question": "yo'qotib qo'ymoq", "RightAnswer": "misplace", "options": ["longevity","intrigue","insulate"]},
{"Question": "quloqsiz", "RightAnswer": "naughty", "options": ["misplace","longevity","intrigue"]},
{"Question": "norma", "RightAnswer": "norm", "options": ["naughty","misplace","longevity"]},
{"Question": "orangutan", "RightAnswer": "orangutan", "options": ["norm","naughty","misplace"]},
{"Question": "ortiqcha yuklamoq", "RightAnswer": "overload", "options": ["orangutan","norm","naughty"]},
{"Question": "xayriya", "RightAnswer": "philanthropy", "options": ["overload","orangutan","norm"]},
{"Question": "surishtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "probe", "options": ["philanthropy","overload","orangutan"]},
{"Question": "qabul qiluvchi", "RightAnswer": "recipient", "options": ["probe","philanthropy","overload"]},
{"Question": "sudralib yuruvchi", "RightAnswer": "reptile", "options": ["recipient","probe","philanthropy"]},
{"Question": "yashnamoq", "RightAnswer": "thrive", "options": ["reptile","recipient","probe"]},
{"Question": "yakuniy", "RightAnswer": "ultimate", "options": ["thrive","reptile","recipient"]}],	
"level 149" : [
    {"Question": "antiqa", "RightAnswer": "antique", "options": ["ultimate","thrive","reptile"]},
{"Question": "ariza beruvchi", "RightAnswer": "applicant", "options": ["antique","ultimate","thrive"]},
{"Question": "artefakt", "RightAnswer": "artifact", "options": ["applicant","antique","ultimate"]},
{"Question": "haqiqiy", "RightAnswer": "authentic", "options": ["artifact","applicant","antique"]},
{"Question": "xronologiya", "RightAnswer": "chronology", "options": ["authentic","artifact","applicant"]},
{"Question": "diplomat", "RightAnswer": "diplomat", "options": ["chronology","authentic","artifact"]},
{"Question": "doston", "RightAnswer": "epic", "options": ["diplomat","chronology","authentic"]},
{"Question": "parcha", "RightAnswer": "excerpt", "options": ["epic","diplomat","chronology"]},
{"Question": "toshqotma", "RightAnswer": "fossil", "options": ["excerpt","epic","diplomat"]},
{"Question": "kamsitmoq", "RightAnswer": "humiliate", "options": ["fossil","excerpt","epic"]},
{"Question": "lirik", "RightAnswer": "lyric", "options": ["humiliate","fossil","excerpt"]},
{"Question": "ulug'vorlik", "RightAnswer": "majesty", "options": ["lyric","humiliate","fossil"]},
{"Question": "monarx", "RightAnswer": "monarch", "options": ["majesty","lyric","humiliate"]},
{"Question": "oldinda", "RightAnswer": "precede", "options": ["monarch","majesty","lyric"]},
{"Question": "punktual", "RightAnswer": "punctual", "options": ["precede","monarch","majesty"]},
{"Question": "yollamoq", "RightAnswer": "recruit", "options": ["punctual","precede","monarch"]},
{"Question": "pulni qaytarish", "RightAnswer": "refund", "options": ["recruit","punctual","precede"]},
{"Question": "ro'yxatdan o'tish", "RightAnswer": "register", "options": ["refund","recruit","punctual"]},
{"Question": "taniqli", "RightAnswer": "renown", "options": ["register","refund","recruit"]},
{"Question": "so'yloq", "RightAnswer": "tusk", "options": ["renown","register","refund"]}],	
"level 150" : [
    {"Question": "yuk", "RightAnswer": "burden", "options": ["tusk","renown","register"]},
{"Question": "murosaga kelmoq", "RightAnswer": "compromise", "options": ["burden","tusk","renown"]},
{"Question": "yasamoq", "RightAnswer": "craft", "options": ["compromise","burden","tusk"]},
{"Question": "yomon odam", "RightAnswer": "crook", "options": ["craft","compromise","burden"]},
{"Question": "valyuta", "RightAnswer": "currency", "options": ["crook","craft","compromise"]},
{"Question": "jumboq", "RightAnswer": "enigma", "options": ["currency","crook","craft"]},
{"Question": "mo'rt", "RightAnswer": "fragile", "options": ["enigma","currency","crook"]},
{"Question": "gibrid", "RightAnswer": "hybrid", "options": ["fragile","enigma","currency"]},
{"Question": "aybsizlik", "RightAnswer": "innocence", "options": ["hybrid","fragile","enigma"]},
{"Question": "birlashtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "merge", "options": ["innocence","hybrid","fragile"]},
{"Question": "o'rtacha", "RightAnswer": "moderate", "options": ["merge","innocence","hybrid"]},
{"Question": "oshib ketmoq", "RightAnswer": "overwhelm", "options": ["moderate","merge","innocence"]},
{"Question": "idrok", "RightAnswer": "perception", "options": ["overwhelm","moderate","merge"]},
{"Question": "uchrashuv", "RightAnswer": "reunion", "options": ["perception","overwhelm","moderate"]},
{"Question": "fitna tuzmoq", "RightAnswer": "rig", "options": ["reunion","perception","overwhelm"]},
{"Question": "titroq", "RightAnswer": "shiver", "options": ["rig","reunion","perception"]},
{"Question": "kirishimli", "RightAnswer": "sociable", "options": ["shiver","rig","reunion"]},
{"Question": "gapdon", "RightAnswer": "talkative", "options": ["sociable","shiver","rig"]},
{"Question": "tortish", "RightAnswer": "tow", "options": ["talkative","sociable","shiver"]},
{"Question": "qadam tashlamoq", "RightAnswer": "tramp", "options": ["tow","talkative","sociable"]}],	
"level 151" : [
    {"Question": "yengillatmoq", "RightAnswer": "alleviate", "options": ["tramp","tow","talkative"]},
{"Question": "astrologiya", "RightAnswer": "astrology", "options": ["alleviate","tramp","tow"]},
{"Question": "farqlash", "RightAnswer": "differentiate", "options": ["astrology","alleviate","tramp"]},
{"Question": "buzish", "RightAnswer": "disrupt", "options": ["differentiate","astrology","alleviate"]},
{"Question": "tenglama", "RightAnswer": "equation", "options": ["disrupt","differentiate","astrology"]},
{"Question": "xato", "RightAnswer": "err", "options": ["equation","disrupt","differentiate"]},
{"Question": "xato", "RightAnswer": "erroneous", "options": ["err","equation","disrupt"]},
{"Question": "g'azablangan", "RightAnswer": "frantic", "options": ["erroneous","err","equation"]},
{"Question": "korpus", "RightAnswer": "hull", "options": ["frantic","erroneous","err"]},
{"Question": "beixtiyor", "RightAnswer": "inadvertent", "options": ["hull","frantic","erroneous"]},
{"Question": "improvizatsiya qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "improvise", "options": ["inadvertent","hull","frantic"]},
{"Question": "kenglik", "RightAnswer": "latitude", "options": ["improvise","inadvertent","hull"]},
{"Question": "dengizchi", "RightAnswer": "mariner", "options": ["latitude","improvise","inadvertent"]},
{"Question": "ko'p", "RightAnswer": "multitude", "options": ["mariner","latitude","improvise"]},
{"Question": "bezovtalik", "RightAnswer": "nuisance", "options": ["multitude","mariner","latitude"]},
{"Question": "doimiylik", "RightAnswer": "permanence", "options": ["nuisance","multitude","mariner"]},
{"Question": "aylanmoq", "RightAnswer": "revolve", "options": ["permanence","nuisance","multitude"]},
{"Question": "tinchlantirmoq", "RightAnswer": "soothe", "options": ["revolve","permanence","nuisance"]},
{"Question": "qolib ketgan", "RightAnswer": "stranded", "options": ["soothe","revolve","permanence"]},
{"Question": "uchuvchan", "RightAnswer": "volatile", "options": ["stranded","soothe","revolve"]}],	
"level 152" : [
    {"Question": "mashaqqatli", "RightAnswer": "arduous", "options": ["volatile","stranded","soothe"]},
{"Question": "erishish", "RightAnswer": "attain", "options": ["arduous","volatile","stranded"]},
{"Question": "birga yashash", "RightAnswer": "coexist", "options": ["attain","arduous","volatile"]},
{"Question": "tasavvur qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "conceive", "options": ["coexist","attain","arduous"]},
{"Question": "shubhali", "RightAnswer": "dubious", "options": ["conceive","coexist","attain"]},
{"Question": "ego", "RightAnswer": "ego", "options": ["dubious","conceive","coexist"]},
{"Question": "elastik", "RightAnswer": "elastic", "options": ["ego","dubious","conceive"]},
{"Question": "harakat qilish", "RightAnswer": "endeavor", "options": ["elastic","ego","dubious"]},
{"Question": "o'yib yozmoq", "RightAnswer": "engrave", "options": ["endeavor","elastic","ego"]},
{"Question": "qazmoq", "RightAnswer": "excavate", "options": ["engrave","endeavor","elastic"]},
{"Question": "tishli", "RightAnswer": "jagged", "options": ["excavate","engrave","endeavor"]},
{"Question": "mahalliy", "RightAnswer": "locale", "options": ["jagged","excavate","engrave"]},
{"Question": "mog'or", "RightAnswer": "mold", "options": ["locale","jagged","excavate"]},
{"Question": "to'g'ridan-to'g'ri", "RightAnswer": "outright", "options": ["mold","locale","jagged"]},
{"Question": "periferiya", "RightAnswer": "periphery", "options": ["outright","mold","locale"]},
{"Question": "gips", "RightAnswer": "plaster", "options": ["periphery","outright","mold"]},
{"Question": "belkurak", "RightAnswer": "shovel", "options": ["plaster","periphery","outright"]},
{"Question": "skelet", "RightAnswer": "skeletal", "options": ["shovel","plaster","periphery"]},
{"Question": "yerdagi", "RightAnswer": "terrestrial", "options": ["skeletal","shovel","plaster"]},
{"Question": "shafqatsiz", "RightAnswer": "vicious", "options": ["terrestrial","skeletal","shovel"]}],	
"level 153" : [
    {"Question": "absurd", "RightAnswer": "absurd", "options": ["vicious","terrestrial","skeletal"]},
{"Question": "anemiya", "RightAnswer": "anemia", "options": ["absurd","vicious","terrestrial"]},
{"Question": "aristokratiya", "RightAnswer": "aristocracy", "options": ["anemia","absurd","vicious"]},
{"Question": "aristokrat", "RightAnswer": "aristocrat", "options": ["aristocracy","anemia","absurd"]},
{"Question": "kiyinmoq", "RightAnswer": "attire", "options": ["aristocrat","aristocracy","anemia"]},
{"Question": "jinnilik", "RightAnswer": "craze", "options": ["attire","aristocrat","aristocracy"]},
{"Question": "kattalashtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "enlarge", "options": ["craze","attire","aristocrat"]},
{"Question": "ortiqcha", "RightAnswer": "excess", "options": ["enlarge","craze","attire"]},
{"Question": "ayollik", "RightAnswer": "feminine", "options": ["excess","enlarge","craze"]},
{"Question": "belgi", "RightAnswer": "hallmark", "options": ["feminine","excess","enlarge"]},
{"Question": "pad", "RightAnswer": "pad", "options": ["hallmark","feminine","excess"]},
{"Question": "ustunlik qiladi", "RightAnswer": "predominant", "options": ["pad","hallmark","feminine"]},
{"Question": "nufuzli", "RightAnswer": "reputable", "options": ["predominant","pad","hallmark"]},
{"Question": "rouge", "RightAnswer": "rouge", "options": ["reputable","predominant","pad"]},
{"Question": "bildirmoq", "RightAnswer": "signify", "options": ["rouge","reputable","predominant"]},
{"Question": "tasma", "RightAnswer": "strap", "options": ["signify","rouge","reputable"]},
{"Question": "chalkash", "RightAnswer": "tangle", "options": ["strap","signify","rouge"]},
{"Question": "bema'nilik", "RightAnswer": "vanity", "options": ["tangle","strap","signify"]},
{"Question": "vie", "RightAnswer": "vie", "options": ["vanity","tangle","strap"]},
{"Question": "qo'pol", "RightAnswer": "vulgar", "options": ["vie","vanity","tangle"]}],	
"level 154" : [
    {"Question": "chordoq", "RightAnswer": "attic", "options": ["vulgar","vie","vanity"]},
{"Question": "bo'lak", "RightAnswer": "chunk", "options": ["attic","vulgar","vie"]},
{"Question": "fuqarolik", "RightAnswer": "civic", "options": ["chunk","attic","vulgar"]},
{"Question": "tushish", "RightAnswer": "descent", "options": ["civic","chunk","attic"]},
{"Question": "din", "RightAnswer": "din", "options": ["descent","civic","chunk"]},
{"Question": "qoniqtirmaslik", "RightAnswer": "dissatisfy", "options": ["din","descent","civic"]},
{"Question": "shov-shuv", "RightAnswer": "fuss", "options": ["dissatisfy","din","descent"]},
{"Question": "gurme", "RightAnswer": "gourmet", "options": ["fuss","dissatisfy","din"]},
{"Question": "shuning uchun", "RightAnswer": "hence", "options": ["gourmet","fuss","dissatisfy"]},
{"Question": "ichki", "RightAnswer": "intrinsic", "options": ["hence","gourmet","fuss"]},
{"Question": "choynak", "RightAnswer": "kettle", "options": ["intrinsic","hence","gourmet"]},
{"Question": "vazirlik", "RightAnswer": "ministry", "options": ["kettle","intrinsic","hence"]},
{"Question": "sinov", "RightAnswer": "ordeal", "options": ["ministry","kettle","intrinsic"]},
{"Question": "ochiqchasiga", "RightAnswer": "outspoken", "options": ["ordeal","ministry","kettle"]},
{"Question": "ortiqcha ish", "RightAnswer": "overwork", "options": ["outspoken","ordeal","ministry"]},
{"Question": "alohida", "RightAnswer": "particular", "options": ["overwork","outspoken","ordeal"]},
{"Question": "o'tkir", "RightAnswer": "pungent", "options": ["particular","overwork","outspoken"]},
{"Question": "horlama", "RightAnswer": "snore", "options": ["pungent","particular","overwork"]},
{"Question": "sog'lom", "RightAnswer": "soundly", "options": ["snore","pungent","particular"]},
{"Question": "boshliq", "RightAnswer": "superintendent", "options": ["soundly","snore","pungent"]}],	
"level 155" : [
    {"Question": "muqobil", "RightAnswer": "alternate", "options": ["superintendent","soundly","snore"]},
{"Question": "kechirim so'ragan", "RightAnswer": "apologetic", "options": ["alternate","superintendent","soundly"]},
{"Question": "yaxshi xulqli", "RightAnswer": "benign", "options": ["apologetic","alternate","superintendent"]},
{"Question": "char", "RightAnswer": "char", "options": ["benign","apologetic","alternate"]},
{"Question": "aniqlashtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "clarify", "options": ["char","benign","apologetic"]},
{"Question": "qayg'u", "RightAnswer": "distress", "options": ["clarify","char","benign"]},
{"Question": "qattiqqo'l", "RightAnswer": "dogged", "options": ["distress","clarify","char"]},
{"Question": "kelib chiqadi", "RightAnswer": "ensue", "options": ["dogged","distress","clarify"]},
{"Question": "nafas olish", "RightAnswer": "gasp", "options": ["ensue","dogged","distress"]},
{"Question": "muzokara qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "negotiate", "options": ["gasp","ensue","dogged"]},
{"Question": "dozani oshirib yubormoq", "RightAnswer": "overdose", "options": ["negotiate","gasp","ensue"]},
{"Question": "ishontirish", "RightAnswer": "persuasion", "options": ["overdose","negotiate","gasp"]},
{"Question": "rele", "RightAnswer": "relay", "options": ["persuasion","overdose","negotiate"]},
{"Question": "istamaslik", "RightAnswer": "reluctance", "options": ["relay","persuasion","overdose"]},
{"Question": "qayta ayting", "RightAnswer": "restate", "options": ["reluctance","relay","persuasion"]},
{"Question": "kunjut", "RightAnswer": "sesame", "options": ["restate","reluctance","relay"]},
{"Question": "qultum", "RightAnswer": "sip", "options": ["sesame","restate","reluctance"]},
{"Question": "chegara", "RightAnswer": "verge", "options": ["sip","sesame","restate"]},
{"Question": "ehtiyotkor", "RightAnswer": "wary", "options": ["verge","sip","sesame"]},
{"Question": "tebranish", "RightAnswer": "waver", "options": ["wary","verge","sip"]}],	
"level 156" : [
    {"Question": "qirg'oqqa", "RightAnswer": "ashore", "options": ["waver","wary","verge"]},
{"Question": "zid", "RightAnswer": "contradict", "options": ["ashore","waver","wary"]},
{"Question": "hamkasbi", "RightAnswer": "counterpart", "options": ["contradict","ashore","waver"]},
{"Question": "mahrum", "RightAnswer": "devoid", "options": ["counterpart","contradict","ashore"]},
{"Question": "ajralmoq", "RightAnswer": "diverge", "options": ["devoid","counterpart","contradict"]},
{"Question": "qochmoq", "RightAnswer": "elude", "options": ["diverge","devoid","counterpart"]},
{"Question": "embrion", "RightAnswer": "embryo", "options": ["elude","diverge","devoid"]},
{"Question": "qaramoq", "RightAnswer": "fend", "options": ["embryo","elude","diverge"]},
{"Question": "xayoliy", "RightAnswer": "fictitious", "options": ["fend","embryo","elude"]},
{"Question": "gazeta", "RightAnswer": "gazette", "options": ["fictitious","fend","embryo"]},
{"Question": "bir hil", "RightAnswer": "homogeneous", "options": ["gazette","fictitious","fend"]},
{"Question": "to'sqinlik qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "obstruct", "options": ["homogeneous","gazette","fictitious"]},
{"Question": "cho'kmoq", "RightAnswer": "plunge", "options": ["obstruct","homogeneous","gazette"]},
{"Question": "uzaytirmoq", "RightAnswer": "prolong", "options": ["plunge","obstruct","homogeneous"]},
{"Question": "ommalashtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "publicize", "options": ["prolong","plunge","obstruct"]},
{"Question": "siyrak", "RightAnswer": "sparse", "options": ["publicize","prolong","plunge"]},
{"Question": "ortiqcha", "RightAnswer": "surplus", "options": ["sparse","publicize","prolong"]},
{"Question": "nazariya qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "theorize", "options": ["surplus","sparse","publicize"]},
{"Question": "tekshirmoq", "RightAnswer": "verify", "options": ["theorize","surplus","sparse"]},
{"Question": "kuchli", "RightAnswer": "vigorous", "options": ["verify","theorize","surplus"]}],	
"level 157" : [
    {"Question": "qurbongoh", "RightAnswer": "altar", "options": ["vigorous","verify","theorize"]},
{"Question": "artrit", "RightAnswer": "arthritis", "options": ["altar","vigorous","verify"]},
{"Question": "botanika", "RightAnswer": "botany", "options": ["arthritis","altar","vigorous"]},
{"Question": "ishonchli", "RightAnswer": "credible", "options": ["botany","arthritis","altar"]},
{"Question": "vafot etgan", "RightAnswer": "deceased", "options": ["credible","botany","arthritis"]},
{"Question": "aldash", "RightAnswer": "deception", "options": ["deceased","credible","botany"]},
{"Question": "shifrlash", "RightAnswer": "decipher", "options": ["deception","deceased","credible"]},
{"Question": "go'ng", "RightAnswer": "dung", "options": ["decipher","deception","deceased"]},
{"Question": "oqshom", "RightAnswer": "dusk", "options": ["dung","decipher","deception"]},
{"Question": "mamnun qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "gratify", "options": ["dusk","dung","decipher"]},
{"Question": "bilaman", "RightAnswer": "hone", "options": ["gratify","dusk","dung"]},
{"Question": "mash", "RightAnswer": "mash", "options": ["hone","gratify","dusk"]},
{"Question": "bezakli", "RightAnswer": "ornate", "options": ["mash","hone","gratify"]},
{"Question": "zotiljam", "RightAnswer": "pneumonia", "options": ["ornate","mash","hone"]},
{"Question": "ruhiy", "RightAnswer": "psychic", "options": ["pneumonia","ornate","mash"]},
{"Question": "psixotik", "RightAnswer": "psychotic", "options": ["psychic","pneumonia","ornate"]},
{"Question": "qamrovi", "RightAnswer": "scope", "options": ["psychotic","psychic","pneumonia"]},
{"Question": "dahshatli", "RightAnswer": "sinister", "options": ["scope","psychotic","psychic"]},
{"Question": "janjal", "RightAnswer": "strife", "options": ["sinister","scope","psychotic"]},
{"Question": "terapevtik", "RightAnswer": "therapeutic", "options": ["strife","sinister","scope"]}],	
"level 158" : [
    {"Question": "tiqilib qolgan", "RightAnswer": "congested", "options": ["therapeutic","strife","sinister"]},
{"Question": "kurer", "RightAnswer": "courier", "options": ["congested","therapeutic","strife"]},
{"Question": "deformatsiya", "RightAnswer": "deform", "options": ["courier","congested","therapeutic"]},
{"Question": "odob-axloq qoidalari", "RightAnswer": "etiquette", "options": ["deform","courier","congested"]},
{"Question": "eksklyuziv", "RightAnswer": "exclusive", "options": ["etiquette","deform","courier"]},
{"Question": "yuk tashish", "RightAnswer": "freight", "options": ["exclusive","etiquette","deform"]},
{"Question": "kiyim", "RightAnswer": "garment", "options": ["freight","exclusive","etiquette"]},
{"Question": "uyqusizlik", "RightAnswer": "insomnia", "options": ["garment","freight","exclusive"]},
{"Question": "intuitiv", "RightAnswer": "intuitive", "options": ["insomnia","garment","freight"]},
{"Question": "javobgar", "RightAnswer": "liable", "options": ["intuitive","insomnia","garment"]},
{"Question": "obsess", "RightAnswer": "obsess", "options": ["liable","intuitive","insomnia"]},
{"Question": "dengizdan tashqarida", "RightAnswer": "overboard", "options": ["obsess","liable","intuitive"]},
{"Question": "premium", "RightAnswer": "premium", "options": ["overboard","obsess","liable"]},
{"Question": "imtiyoz", "RightAnswer": "privilege", "options": ["premium","overboard","obsess"]},
{"Question": "surtish", "RightAnswer": "propel", "options": ["privilege","premium","overboard"]},
{"Question": "ijtimoiylashmoq", "RightAnswer": "socialize", "options": ["propel","privilege","premium"]},
{"Question": "bostirish", "RightAnswer": "suppress", "options": ["socialize","propel","privilege"]},
{"Question": "tramvay", "RightAnswer": "tram", "options": ["suppress","socialize","propel"]},
{"Question": "bezovta qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "unsettle", "options": ["tram","suppress","socialize"]},
{"Question": "burish", "RightAnswer": "warp", "options": ["unsettle","tram","suppress"]}],	
"level 159" : [
    {"Question": "arteriya", "RightAnswer": "artery", "options": ["warp","unsettle","tram"]},
{"Question": "buzilish", "RightAnswer": "deterioration", "options": ["artery","warp","unsettle"]},
{"Question": "qiyin", "RightAnswer": "elusive", "options": ["deterioration","artery","warp"]},
{"Question": "em-xashak", "RightAnswer": "forage", "options": ["elusive","deterioration","artery"]},
{"Question": "to'sqinlik qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "impede", "options": ["forage","elusive","deterioration"]},
{"Question": "qo'zg'atmoq", "RightAnswer": "induce", "options": ["impede","forage","elusive"]},
{"Question": "ajralmas", "RightAnswer": "inseparable", "options": ["induce","impede","forage"]},
{"Question": "yaroqsiz", "RightAnswer": "invalid", "options": ["inseparable","induce","impede"]},
{"Question": "kattalashtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "magnify", "options": ["invalid","inseparable","induce"]},
{"Question": "asosiy oqim", "RightAnswer": "mainstream", "options": ["magnify","invalid","inseparable"]},
{"Question": "mikrob", "RightAnswer": "microbe", "options": ["mainstream","magnify","invalid"]},
{"Question": "ahamiyatsiz", "RightAnswer": "negligible", "options": ["microbe","mainstream","magnify"]},
{"Question": "falaj", "RightAnswer": "paralysis", "options": ["negligible","microbe","mainstream"]},
{"Question": "zararkunanda", "RightAnswer": "pest", "options": ["paralysis","negligible","microbe"]},
{"Question": "ustunlik qiladi", "RightAnswer": "prevail", "options": ["pest","paralysis","negligible"]},
{"Question": "nafas olish", "RightAnswer": "respiration", "options": ["prevail","pest","paralysis"]},
{"Question": "yorilmoq", "RightAnswer": "rupture", "options": ["respiration","prevail","pest"]},
{"Question": "vahshiy", "RightAnswer": "savage", "options": ["rupture","respiration","prevail"]},
{"Question": "hayratda qoldirmoq", "RightAnswer": "stun", "options": ["savage","rupture","respiration"]},
{"Question": "sezgir", "RightAnswer": "susceptible", "options": ["stun","savage","rupture"]}],	
"level 160" : [
    {"Question": "to'plash", "RightAnswer": "accumulate", "options": ["susceptible","stun","savage"]},
{"Question": "havo", "RightAnswer": "aerial", "options": ["accumulate","susceptible","stun"]},
{"Question": "apparat", "RightAnswer": "apparatus", "options": ["aerial","accumulate","susceptible"]},
{"Question": "qor ko'chkisi", "RightAnswer": "avalanche", "options": ["apparatus","aerial","accumulate"]},
{"Question": "mustahkamlik", "RightAnswer": "consistency", "options": ["avalanche","apparatus","aerial"]},
{"Question": "konvektsiya", "RightAnswer": "convection", "options": ["consistency","avalanche","apparatus"]},
{"Question": "tushirmoq", "RightAnswer": "discharge", "options": ["convection","consistency","avalanche"]},
{"Question": "buzilmagan", "RightAnswer": "intact", "options": ["discharge","convection","consistency"]},
{"Question": "o'lik", "RightAnswer": "mortal", "options": ["intact","discharge","convection"]},
{"Question": "alomat", "RightAnswer": "omen", "options": ["mortal","intact","discharge"]},
{"Question": "bulutli", "RightAnswer": "overcast", "options": ["omen","mortal","intact"]},
{"Question": "achchiq", "RightAnswer": "poignant", "options": ["overcast","omen","mortal"]},
{"Question": "qo'riqchi", "RightAnswer": "ranger", "options": ["poignant","overcast","omen"]},
{"Question": "vayronalar", "RightAnswer": "rubble", "options": ["ranger","poignant","overcast"]},
{"Question": "tanho", "RightAnswer": "seclude", "options": ["rubble","ranger","poignant"]},
{"Question": "yon tomonga", "RightAnswer": "sideways", "options": ["seclude","rubble","ranger"]},
{"Question": "yig'lamoq", "RightAnswer": "sob", "options": ["sideways","seclude","rubble"]},
{"Question": "hushyor", "RightAnswer": "sober", "options": ["sob","sideways","seclude"]},
{"Question": "dog'", "RightAnswer": "speck", "options": ["sober","sob","sideways"]},
{"Question": "tarbiya", "RightAnswer": "upbringing", "options": ["speck","sober","sob"]}],	
"level 161" : [
    {"Question": "himoyachi", "RightAnswer": "advocate", "options": ["upbringing","speck","sober"]},
{"Question": "ruxsat bermoq", "RightAnswer": "authorize", "options": ["advocate","upbringing","speck"]},
{"Question": "fuqarolik", "RightAnswer": "civilian", "options": ["authorize","advocate","upbringing"]},
{"Question": "tovar", "RightAnswer": "commodity", "options": ["civilian","authorize","advocate"]},
{"Question": "zabt etish", "RightAnswer": "conquest", "options": ["commodity","civilian","authorize"]},
{"Question": "oshkor qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "disclose", "options": ["conquest","commodity","civilian"]},
{"Question": "dinamikasi", "RightAnswer": "dynamics", "options": ["disclose","conquest","commodity"]},
{"Question": "ro'yxatdan o'tish", "RightAnswer": "enroll", "options": ["dynamics","disclose","conquest"]},
{"Question": "hasadgo'y", "RightAnswer": "envious", "options": ["enroll","dynamics","disclose"]},
{"Question": "eyforiya", "RightAnswer": "euphoria", "options": ["envious","enroll","dynamics"]},
{"Question": "bayramona", "RightAnswer": "festive", "options": ["euphoria","envious","enroll"]},
{"Question": "quvnoq", "RightAnswer": "jolly", "options": ["festive","euphoria","envious"]},
{"Question": "yasmiq", "RightAnswer": "lentil", "options": ["jolly","festive","euphoria"]},
{"Question": "marshal", "RightAnswer": "marshal", "options": ["lentil","jolly","festive"]},
{"Question": "ruhiy holat", "RightAnswer": "morale", "options": ["marshal","lentil","jolly"]},
{"Question": "bashorat", "RightAnswer": "prophecy", "options": ["morale","marshal","lentil"]},
{"Question": "adaçayı", "RightAnswer": "sage", "options": ["prophecy","morale","marshal"]},
{"Question": "senat", "RightAnswer": "senate", "options": ["sage","prophecy","morale"]},
{"Question": "hissiyot", "RightAnswer": "sentiment", "options": ["senate","sage","prophecy"]},
{"Question": "tartibsizlik", "RightAnswer": "unrest", "options": ["sentiment","senate","sage"]}],	
"level 162" : [
    {"Question": "bezash", "RightAnswer": "adorn", "options": ["unrest","sentiment","senate"]},
{"Question": "baxt", "RightAnswer": "bliss", "options": ["adorn","unrest","sentiment"]},
{"Question": "butler", "RightAnswer": "butler", "options": ["bliss","adorn","unrest"]},
{"Question": "kramp", "RightAnswer": "cramp", "options": ["butler","bliss","adorn"]},
{"Question": "eskirgan", "RightAnswer": "dilapidated", "options": ["cramp","butler","bliss"]},
{"Question": "uyg'otmoq", "RightAnswer": "evoke", "options": ["dilapidated","cramp","butler"]},
{"Question": "xayr", "RightAnswer": "farewell", "options": ["evoke","dilapidated","cramp"]},
{"Question": "kran", "RightAnswer": "faucet", "options": ["farewell","evoke","dilapidated"]},
{"Question": "iflos", "RightAnswer": "filth", "options": ["faucet","farewell","evoke"]},
{"Question": "kamchilik", "RightAnswer": "flaw", "options": ["filth","faucet","farewell"]},
{"Question": "jilmayish", "RightAnswer": "grin", "options": ["flaw","filth","faucet"]},
{"Question": "uy xo'jaligi", "RightAnswer": "housekeeping", "options": ["grin","flaw","filth"]},
{"Question": "tepalik", "RightAnswer": "mound", "options": ["housekeeping","grin","flaw"]},
{"Question": "xiralashgan", "RightAnswer": "numb", "options": ["mound","housekeeping","grin"]},
{"Question": "beparvo", "RightAnswer": "reckless", "options": ["numb","mound","housekeeping"]},
{"Question": "shifer", "RightAnswer": "slate", "options": ["reckless","numb","mound"]},
{"Question": "tabure", "RightAnswer": "stool", "options": ["slate","reckless","numb"]},
{"Question": "vasiyatnoma", "RightAnswer": "testament", "options": ["stool","slate","reckless"]},
{"Question": "yog'och", "RightAnswer": "timber", "options": ["testament","stool","slate"]},
{"Question": "valf", "RightAnswer": "valve", "options": ["timber","testament","stool"]}],	
"level 163" : [
    {"Question": "sertifikatlash", "RightAnswer": "certify", "options": ["valve","timber","testament"]},
{"Question": "hamkorlik qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "collaborate", "options": ["certify","valve","timber"]},
{"Question": "kompilyatsiya qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "compile", "options": ["collaborate","certify","valve"]},
{"Question": "qarshi harakat qilish", "RightAnswer": "counteract", "options": ["compile","collaborate","certify"]},
{"Question": "jilovlash", "RightAnswer": "curb", "options": ["counteract","compile","collaborate"]},
{"Question": "tashxis qo'ymoq", "RightAnswer": "diagnose", "options": ["curb","counteract","compile"]},
{"Question": "qabul qilish", "RightAnswer": "enact", "options": ["diagnose","curb","counteract"]},
{"Question": "federatsiya", "RightAnswer": "federation", "options": ["enact","diagnose","curb"]},
{"Question": "yalpi", "RightAnswer": "gross", "options": ["federation","enact","diagnose"]},
{"Question": "insonparvar", "RightAnswer": "humane", "options": ["gross","federation","enact"]},
{"Question": "chidab bo'lmas", "RightAnswer": "intolerable", "options": ["humane","gross","federation"]},
{"Question": "muhtoj", "RightAnswer": "needy", "options": ["intolerable","humane","gross"]},
{"Question": "boshlanishi", "RightAnswer": "onset", "options": ["needy","intolerable","humane"]},
{"Question": "garov", "RightAnswer": "pledge", "options": ["onset","needy","intolerable"]},
{"Question": "taqiqlash", "RightAnswer": "prohibit", "options": ["pledge","onset","needy"]},
{"Question": "toshma", "RightAnswer": "rash", "options": ["prohibit","pledge","onset"]},
{"Question": "ko'rsatish", "RightAnswer": "render", "options": ["rash","prohibit","pledge"]},
{"Question": "chechak", "RightAnswer": "smallpox", "options": ["render","rash","prohibit"]},
{"Question": "uzatish", "RightAnswer": "transmit", "options": ["smallpox","render","rash"]},
{"Question": "qasam", "RightAnswer": "vow", "options": ["transmit","smallpox","render"]}],	
"level 164" : [
    {"Question": "kamuflyaj", "RightAnswer": "camouflage", "options": ["vow","transmit","smallpox"]},
{"Question": "tafakkur qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "contemplate", "options": ["camouflage","vow","transmit"]},
{"Question": "kurashmoq", "RightAnswer": "contend", "options": ["contemplate","camouflage","vow"]},
{"Question": "krovat", "RightAnswer": "cot", "options": ["contend","contemplate","camouflage"]},
{"Question": "ro'yxatga olish", "RightAnswer": "enlist", "options": ["cot","contend","contemplate"]},
{"Question": "chegara", "RightAnswer": "frontier", "options": ["enlist","cot","contend"]},
{"Question": "qo'llanma", "RightAnswer": "handbook", "options": ["frontier","enlist","cot"]},
{"Question": "ikkilangan", "RightAnswer": "hesitant", "options": ["handbook","frontier","enlist"]},
{"Question": "yam-yashil", "RightAnswer": "lush", "options": ["hesitant","handbook","frontier"]},
{"Question": "ilik", "RightAnswer": "marrow", "options": ["lush","hesitant","handbook"]},
{"Question": "kiyim", "RightAnswer": "outfit", "options": ["marrow","lush","hesitant"]},
{"Question": "panja", "RightAnswer": "paw", "options": ["outfit","marrow","lush"]},
{"Question": "titroq", "RightAnswer": "quiver", "options": ["paw","outfit","marrow"]},
{"Question": "ajoyib", "RightAnswer": "splendid", "options": ["quiver","paw","outfit"]},
{"Question": "adashgan", "RightAnswer": "stray", "options": ["splendid","quiver","paw"]},
{"Question": "muhim", "RightAnswer": "substantial", "options": ["stray","splendid","quiver"]},
{"Question": "mash'al", "RightAnswer": "torch", "options": ["substantial","stray","splendid"]},
{"Question": "trakt", "RightAnswer": "tract", "options": ["torch","substantial","stray"]},
{"Question": "hushyorlik", "RightAnswer": "vigil", "options": ["tract","torch","substantial"]},
{"Question": "charchagan", "RightAnswer": "weary", "options": ["vigil","tract","torch"]}],	
"level 165" : [
    {"Question": "rioya qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "adhere", "options": ["weary","vigil","tract"]},
{"Question": "boshqarmoq", "RightAnswer": "administer", "options": ["adhere","weary","vigil"]},
{"Question": "rahmdil", "RightAnswer": "compassionate", "options": ["administer","adhere","weary"]},
{"Question": "ifloslantirmoq", "RightAnswer": "contaminate", "options": ["compassionate","administer","adhere"]},
{"Question": "etishmovchilik", "RightAnswer": "deficiency", "options": ["contaminate","compassionate","administer"]},
{"Question": "epidemiya", "RightAnswer": "epidemic", "options": ["deficiency","contaminate","compassionate"]},
{"Question": "xavf", "RightAnswer": "hazard", "options": ["epidemic","deficiency","contaminate"]},
{"Question": "imperativ", "RightAnswer": "imperative", "options": ["hazard","epidemic","deficiency"]},
{"Question": "ichaklar", "RightAnswer": "intestines", "options": ["imperative","hazard","epidemic"]},
{"Question": "namoyon", "RightAnswer": "manifest", "options": ["intestines","imperative","hazard"]},
{"Question": "metabolik", "RightAnswer": "metabolic", "options": ["manifest","intestines","imperative"]},
{"Question": "gavjum", "RightAnswer": "overcrowded", "options": ["metabolic","manifest","intestines"]},
{"Question": "eng muhimi", "RightAnswer": "paramount", "options": ["overcrowded","metabolic","manifest"]},
{"Question": "amaliyotchi", "RightAnswer": "practitioner", "options": ["paramount","overcrowded","metabolic"]},
{"Question": "ta'minlash", "RightAnswer": "provision", "options": ["practitioner","paramount","overcrowded"]},
{"Question": "to'ldirish", "RightAnswer": "replenish", "options": ["provision","practitioner","paramount"]},
{"Question": "steril", "RightAnswer": "sterile", "options": ["replenish","provision","practitioner"]},
{"Question": "yangilash", "RightAnswer": "upgrade", "options": ["sterile","replenish","provision"]},
{"Question": "yashovchan", "RightAnswer": "viable", "options": ["upgrade","sterile","replenish"]},
{"Question": "ixtiyoriy", "RightAnswer": "voluntary", "options": ["viable","upgrade","sterile"]}],	
"level 166" : [
    {"Question": "orasida", "RightAnswer": "amid", "options": ["voluntary","viable","upgrade"]},
{"Question": "sahna orqasida", "RightAnswer": "backstage", "options": ["amid","voluntary","viable"]},
{"Question": "milliarder", "RightAnswer": "billionaire", "options": ["backstage","amid","voluntary"]},
{"Question": "qo'pol", "RightAnswer": "brute", "options": ["billionaire","backstage","amid"]},
{"Question": "qo'pol", "RightAnswer": "clumsy", "options": ["brute","billionaire","backstage"]},
{"Question": "to'qnashmoq", "RightAnswer": "collide", "options": ["clumsy","brute","billionaire"]},
{"Question": "aybdor", "RightAnswer": "culprit", "options": ["collide","clumsy","brute"]},
{"Question": "evakuatsiya qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "evacuate", "options": ["culprit","collide","clumsy"]},
{"Question": "yonuvchan", "RightAnswer": "flammable", "options": ["evacuate","culprit","collide"]},
{"Question": "olomon", "RightAnswer": "mob", "options": ["flammable","evacuate","culprit"]},
{"Question": "muddatidan oldin", "RightAnswer": "premature", "options": ["mob","flammable","evacuate"]},
{"Question": "norozi", "RightAnswer": "resent", "options": ["premature","mob","flammable"]},
{"Question": "satira", "RightAnswer": "satire", "options": ["resent","premature","mob"]},
{"Question": "tekshirish", "RightAnswer": "scrutiny", "options": ["satire","resent","premature"]},
{"Question": "ajratmoq", "RightAnswer": "segregate", "options": ["scrutiny","satire","resent"]},
{"Question": "mavzu", "RightAnswer": "subject", "options": ["segregate","scrutiny","satire"]},
{"Question": "guvohlik bermoq", "RightAnswer": "testify", "options": ["subject","segregate","scrutiny"]},
{"Question": "g'alayon", "RightAnswer": "tumult", "options": ["testify","subject","segregate"]},
{"Question": "kam baho bermoq", "RightAnswer": "underestimate", "options": ["tumult","testify","subject"]},
{"Question": "shov-shuv", "RightAnswer": "uproar", "options": ["underestimate","tumult","testify"]}],	
"level 167" : [
    {"Question": "tezlashtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "accelerate", "options": ["uproar","underestimate","tumult"]},
{"Question": "yangidan", "RightAnswer": "anew", "options": ["accelerate","uproar","underestimate"]},
{"Question": "nuqson", "RightAnswer": "defect", "options": ["anew","accelerate","uproar"]},
{"Question": "qayg'uli", "RightAnswer": "dreary", "options": ["defect","anew","accelerate"]},
{"Question": "dublikat", "RightAnswer": "duplicate", "options": ["dreary","defect","anew"]},
{"Question": "elektromagnit", "RightAnswer": "electromagnetic", "options": ["duplicate","dreary","defect"]},
{"Question": "elektron", "RightAnswer": "electron", "options": ["electromagnetic","duplicate","dreary"]},
{"Question": "sirpanmoq", "RightAnswer": "glide", "options": ["electron","electromagnetic","duplicate"]},
{"Question": "zukko", "RightAnswer": "ingenious", "options": ["glide","electron","electromagnetic"]},
{"Question": "innovatsiya", "RightAnswer": "innovation", "options": ["ingenious","glide","electron"]},
{"Question": "innovatsion", "RightAnswer": "innovative", "options": ["innovation","ingenious","glide"]},
{"Question": "ishga tushirish", "RightAnswer": "launch", "options": ["innovative","innovation","ingenious"]},
{"Question": "meteorologik", "RightAnswer": "meteorological", "options": ["launch","innovative","innovation"]},
{"Question": "meteorologiya", "RightAnswer": "meteorology", "options": ["meteorological","launch","innovative"]},
{"Question": "kirib bormoq", "RightAnswer": "penetrate", "options": ["meteorology","meteorological","launch"]},
{"Question": "harakatga keltirish", "RightAnswer": "propulsion", "options": ["penetrate","meteorology","meteorological"]},
{"Question": "simulyatsiya qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "simulate", "options": ["propulsion","penetrate","meteorology"]},
{"Question": "shnur", "RightAnswer": "spur", "options": ["simulate","propulsion","penetrate"]},
{"Question": "rag'batlantirmoq", "RightAnswer": "stimulate", "options": ["spur","simulate","propulsion"]},
{"Question": "qat'iyatli", "RightAnswer": "tenacious", "options": ["stimulate","spur","simulate"]}],	
"level 168" : [
    {"Question": "oldindan", "RightAnswer": "beforehand", "options": ["tenacious","stimulate","spur"]},
{"Question": "santigrad", "RightAnswer": "centigrade", "options": ["beforehand","tenacious","stimulate"]},
{"Question": "suhbatlashish", "RightAnswer": "chatter", "options": ["centigrade","beforehand","tenacious"]},
{"Question": "konsert", "RightAnswer": "concerto", "options": ["chatter","centigrade","beforehand"]},
{"Question": "zichlash", "RightAnswer": "condense", "options": ["concerto","chatter","centigrade"]},
{"Question": "koy", "RightAnswer": "cove", "options": ["condense","concerto","chatter"]},
{"Question": "yomonlashadi", "RightAnswer": "deteriorate", "options": ["cove","condense","concerto"]},
{"Question": "tashqi", "RightAnswer": "exterior", "options": ["deteriorate","cove","condense"]},
{"Question": "Avtomagistral", "RightAnswer": "freeway", "options": ["exterior","deteriorate","cove"]},
{"Question": "samimiy", "RightAnswer": "hearty", "options": ["freeway","exterior","deteriorate"]},
{"Question": "mehmondo'st", "RightAnswer": "hospitable", "options": ["hearty","freeway","exterior"]},
{"Question": "mulk", "RightAnswer": "manor", "options": ["hospitable","hearty","freeway"]},
{"Question": "monastir", "RightAnswer": "monastery", "options": ["manor","hospitable","hearty"]},
{"Question": "bolalar bog'chasi", "RightAnswer": "nursery", "options": ["monastery","manor","hospitable"]},
{"Question": "cho'zilgan", "RightAnswer": "outstretched", "options": ["nursery","monastery","manor"]},
{"Question": "posilka", "RightAnswer": "parcel", "options": ["outstretched","nursery","monastery"]},
{"Question": "profil", "RightAnswer": "profile", "options": ["parcel","outstretched","nursery"]},
{"Question": "jonli", "RightAnswer": "vivacious", "options": ["profile","parcel","outstretched"]},
{"Question": "o'rash", "RightAnswer": "winding", "options": ["vivacious","profile","parcel"]},
{"Question": "zip", "RightAnswer": "zip", "options": ["winding","vivacious","profile"]}],	
"level 169" : [
    {"Question": "havo yo'li", "RightAnswer": "airway", "options": ["zip","winding","vivacious"]},
{"Question": "Qodir", "RightAnswer": "Almighty", "options": ["airway","zip","winding"]},
{"Question": "kelishi", "RightAnswer": "advent", "options": ["Almighty","airway","zip"]},
{"Question": "yulduz turkumi", "RightAnswer": "constellation", "options": ["advent","Almighty","airway"]},
{"Question": "aniq", "RightAnswer": "definitive", "options": ["constellation","advent","Almighty"]},
{"Question": "tenglashtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "equate", "options": ["definitive","constellation","advent"]},
{"Question": "nafas olmoq", "RightAnswer": "inhale", "options": ["equate","definitive","constellation"]},
{"Question": "chaqirmoq", "RightAnswer": "invoke", "options": ["inhale","equate","definitive"]},
{"Question": "oy", "RightAnswer": "lunar", "options": ["invoke","inhale","equate"]},
{"Question": "yangilik", "RightAnswer": "novelty", "options": ["lunar","invoke","inhale"]},
{"Question": "eskirgan", "RightAnswer": "outmoded", "options": ["novelty","lunar","invoke"]},
{"Question": "shaxsiylashtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "personalize", "options": ["outmoded","novelty","lunar"]},
{"Question": "tegishli", "RightAnswer": "pertain", "options": ["personalize","outmoded","novelty"]},
{"Question": "asosiy", "RightAnswer": "primal", "options": ["pertain","personalize","outmoded"]},
{"Question": "psixiatrik", "RightAnswer": "psychiatric", "options": ["primal","pertain","personalize"]},
{"Question": "psixiatriya", "RightAnswer": "psychiatry", "options": ["psychiatric","primal","pertain"]},
{"Question": "refleks", "RightAnswer": "reflex", "options": ["psychiatry","psychiatric","primal"]},
{"Question": "tutilmoq", "RightAnswer": "seizure", "options": ["reflex","psychiatry","psychiatric"]},
{"Question": "sessiya", "RightAnswer": "session", "options": ["seizure","reflex","psychiatry"]},
{"Question": "idish", "RightAnswer": "utensil", "options": ["session","seizure","reflex"]}],	
"level 170" : [
    {"Question": "yopishtiruvchi", "RightAnswer": "adhesive", "options": ["utensil","session","seizure"]},
{"Question": "salbiy", "RightAnswer": "adverse", "options": ["adhesive","utensil","session"]},
{"Question": "qaramlik", "RightAnswer": "dependency", "options": ["adverse","adhesive","utensil"]},
{"Question": "axlatxona", "RightAnswer": "dump", "options": ["dependency","adverse","adhesive"]},
{"Question": "abadiy", "RightAnswer": "eternal", "options": ["dump","dependency","adverse"]},
{"Question": "tebranmoq", "RightAnswer": "fluctuate", "options": ["eternal","dump","dependency"]},
{"Question": "fro", "RightAnswer": "fro", "options": ["fluctuate","eternal","dump"]},
{"Question": "kiritish", "RightAnswer": "inclusion", "options": ["fro","fluctuate","eternal"]},
{"Question": "oraliq", "RightAnswer": "intermediate", "options": ["inclusion","fro","fluctuate"]},
{"Question": "intervalgacha", "RightAnswer": "intermittent", "options": ["intermediate","inclusion","fro"]},
{"Question": "ustoz", "RightAnswer": "mentor", "options": ["intermittent","intermediate","inclusion"]},
{"Question": "feniks", "RightAnswer": "phoenix", "options": ["mentor","intermittent","intermediate"]},
{"Question": "fotosintez", "RightAnswer": "photosynthesis", "options": ["phoenix","mentor","intermittent"]},
{"Question": "gulchanglar", "RightAnswer": "pollen", "options": ["photosynthesis","phoenix","mentor"]},
{"Question": "qaytarib olish", "RightAnswer": "regain", "options": ["pollen","photosynthesis","phoenix"]},
{"Question": "teskari", "RightAnswer": "reverse", "options": ["regain","pollen","photosynthesis"]},
{"Question": "to'da", "RightAnswer": "swarm", "options": ["reverse","regain","pollen"]},
{"Question": "tekstura", "RightAnswer": "texture", "options": ["swarm","reverse","regain"]},
{"Question": "qitiqlash", "RightAnswer": "tickle", "options": ["texture","swarm","reverse"]},
{"Question": "jonli", "RightAnswer": "vibrant", "options": ["tickle","texture","swarm"]}],	
"level 171" : [
    {"Question": "bekor qilish", "RightAnswer": "abolish", "options": ["vibrant","tickle","texture"]},
{"Question": "tuzatish", "RightAnswer": "amend", "options": ["abolish","vibrant","tickle"]},
{"Question": "intilmoq", "RightAnswer": "aspire", "options": ["amend","abolish","vibrant"]},
{"Question": "tsenzura", "RightAnswer": "censor", "options": ["aspire","amend","abolish"]},
{"Question": "nizom", "RightAnswer": "charter", "options": ["censor","aspire","amend"]},
{"Question": "konstitutsiya", "RightAnswer": "constitution", "options": ["charter","censor","aspire"]},
{"Question": "kosmopolit", "RightAnswer": "cosmopolitan", "options": ["constitution","charter","censor"]},
{"Question": "tarqatmoq", "RightAnswer": "disseminate", "options": ["cosmopolitan","constitution","charter"]},
{"Question": "xushomadgo'y", "RightAnswer": "flatter", "options": ["disseminate","cosmopolitan","constitution"]},
{"Question": "mashxur", "RightAnswer": "infamous", "options": ["flatter","disseminate","cosmopolitan"]},
{"Question": "oqsoq", "RightAnswer": "lame", "options": ["infamous","flatter","disseminate"]},
{"Question": "oqsoq", "RightAnswer": "limp", "options": ["lame","infamous","flatter"]},
{"Question": "portlash", "RightAnswer": "outburst", "options": ["limp","lame","infamous"]},
{"Question": "patologik", "RightAnswer": "pathological", "options": ["outburst","limp","lame"]},
{"Question": "fenomenal", "RightAnswer": "phenomenal", "options": ["pathological","outburst","limp"]},
{"Question": "so'rov", "RightAnswer": "poll", "options": ["phenomenal","pathological","outburst"]},
{"Question": "pushaymonlik", "RightAnswer": "remorse", "options": ["poll","phenomenal","pathological"]},
{"Question": "maxfiylik", "RightAnswer": "secrecy", "options": ["remorse","poll","phenomenal"]},
{"Question": "hal qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "tackle", "options": ["secrecy","remorse","poll"]},
{"Question": "trans", "RightAnswer": "trance", "options": ["tackle","secrecy","remorse"]}],	
"level 172" : [
    {"Question": "qo'rqoq", "RightAnswer": "coward", "options": ["trance","tackle","secrecy"]},
{"Question": "o'chirmoq", "RightAnswer": "delete", "options": ["coward","trance","tackle"]},
{"Question": "birinchi qo'l", "RightAnswer": "firsthand", "options": ["delete","coward","trance"]},
{"Question": "jiddiy", "RightAnswer": "earnest", "options": ["firsthand","delete","coward"]},
{"Question": "etnik", "RightAnswer": "ethnic", "options": ["earnest","firsthand","delete"]},
{"Question": "istisno qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "exclude", "options": ["ethnic","earnest","firsthand"]},
{"Question": "ravon", "RightAnswer": "fluent", "options": ["exclude","ethnic","earnest"]},
{"Question": "imperator", "RightAnswer": "imperial", "options": ["fluent","exclude","ethnic"]},
{"Question": "inklyuziv", "RightAnswer": "inclusive", "options": ["imperial","fluent","exclude"]},
{"Question": "qonun chiqaruvchi organ", "RightAnswer": "legislature", "options": ["inclusive","imperial","fluent"]},
{"Question": "lingvistik", "RightAnswer": "linguistic", "options": ["legislature","inclusive","imperial"]},
{"Question": "bir tilli", "RightAnswer": "monolingual", "options": ["linguistic","legislature","inclusive"]},
{"Question": "millati", "RightAnswer": "nationality", "options": ["monolingual","linguistic","legislature"]},
{"Question": "vatanparvar", "RightAnswer": "patriot", "options": ["nationality","monolingual","linguistic"]},
{"Question": "jinoiy javobgarlikka tortmoq", "RightAnswer": "prosecute", "options": ["patriot","nationality","monolingual"]},
{"Question": "irqiy", "RightAnswer": "racial", "options": ["prosecute","patriot","nationality"]},
{"Question": "tantanali", "RightAnswer": "solemn", "options": ["racial","prosecute","patriot"]},
{"Question": "birdamlik", "RightAnswer": "solidarity", "options": ["solemn","racial","prosecute"]},
{"Question": "xushmuomalalik", "RightAnswer": "tact", "options": ["solidarity","solemn","racial"]},
{"Question": "buzmoq", "RightAnswer": "undermine", "options": ["tact","solidarity","solemn"]}],	
"level 173" : [
    {"Question": "ajratmoq", "RightAnswer": "allocate", "options": ["undermine","tact","solidarity"]},
{"Question": "ishtahani ochuvchi", "RightAnswer": "appetizing", "options": ["allocate","undermine","tact"]},
{"Question": "bo'ron", "RightAnswer": "blizzard", "options": ["appetizing","allocate","undermine"]},
{"Question": "bo'shliq", "RightAnswer": "cavity", "options": ["blizzard","appetizing","allocate"]},
{"Question": "soat yo'nalishi bo'yicha", "RightAnswer": "clockwise", "options": ["cavity","blizzard","appetizing"]},
{"Question": "konsentrik", "RightAnswer": "concentric", "options": ["clockwise","cavity","blizzard"]},
{"Question": "xushmuomalalik", "RightAnswer": "courtesy", "options": ["concentric","clockwise","cavity"]},
{"Question": "tiniq", "RightAnswer": "crisp", "options": ["courtesy","concentric","clockwise"]},
{"Question": "kelishmovchilik", "RightAnswer": "discord", "options": ["crisp","courtesy","concentric"]},
{"Question": "sovuq", "RightAnswer": "frigid", "options": ["discord","crisp","courtesy"]},
{"Question": "hosil qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "generate", "options": ["frigid","discord","crisp"]},
{"Question": "muzlik", "RightAnswer": "glacial", "options": ["generate","frigid","discord"]},
{"Question": "almashmoq", "RightAnswer": "interchange", "options": ["glacial","generate","frigid"]},
{"Question": "shkaf", "RightAnswer": "locker", "options": ["interchange","glacial","generate"]},
{"Question": "ko'p madaniyatli", "RightAnswer": "multicultural", "options": ["locker","interchange","glacial"]},
{"Question": "e'tiborsizlik", "RightAnswer": "omission", "options": ["multicultural","locker","interchange"]},
{"Question": "nazorat qiladi", "RightAnswer": "oversee", "options": ["omission","multicultural","locker"]},
{"Question": "teshmoq", "RightAnswer": "pierce", "options": ["oversee","omission","multicultural"]},
{"Question": "takrorlash", "RightAnswer": "replicate", "options": ["pierce","oversee","omission"]},
{"Question": "to'lqinli", "RightAnswer": "wavy", "options": ["replicate","pierce","oversee"]}],	
"level 174" : [
    {"Question": "turmoq", "RightAnswer": "abide", "options": ["wavy","replicate","pierce"]},
{"Question": "konvertatsiya", "RightAnswer": "conversion", "options": ["abide","wavy","replicate"]},
{"Question": "tiqmoq", "RightAnswer": "cram", "options": ["conversion","abide","wavy"]},
{"Question": "kechiktirish", "RightAnswer": "defer", "options": ["cram","conversion","abide"]},
{"Question": "eksport", "RightAnswer": "export", "options": ["defer","cram","conversion"]},
{"Question": "tutun", "RightAnswer": "fume", "options": ["export","defer","cram"]},
{"Question": "odatiy", "RightAnswer": "habitual", "options": ["fume","export","defer"]},
{"Question": "oqlash", "RightAnswer": "justify", "options": ["habitual","fume","export"]},
{"Question": "chiqish", "RightAnswer": "output", "options": ["justify","habitual","fume"]},
{"Question": "aholining haddan tashqari ko'payishi", "RightAnswer": "overpopulation", "options": ["output","justify","habitual"]},
{"Question": "patent", "RightAnswer": "patent", "options": ["overpopulation","output","justify"]},
{"Question": "jazolash", "RightAnswer": "penalize", "options": ["patent","overpopulation","output"]},
{"Question": "neft", "RightAnswer": "petroleum", "options": ["penalize","patent","overpopulation"]},
{"Question": "prototip", "RightAnswer": "prototype", "options": ["petroleum","penalize","patent"]},
{"Question": "hurda", "RightAnswer": "scrap", "options": ["prototype","petroleum","penalize"]},
{"Question": "sektor", "RightAnswer": "sector", "options": ["scrap","prototype","petroleum"]},
{"Question": "obuna bo'ling", "RightAnswer": "subscribe", "options": ["sector","scrap","prototype"]},
{"Question": "yashash", "RightAnswer": "subsist", "options": ["subscribe","sector","scrap"]},
{"Question": "to'xtatib turish", "RightAnswer": "suspend", "options": ["subsist","subscribe","sector"]},
{"Question": "sintez", "RightAnswer": "synthesis", "options": ["suspend","subsist","subscribe"]}],	
"level 175" : [
    {"Question": "akrobat", "RightAnswer": "acrobat", "options": ["synthesis","suspend","subsist"]},
{"Question": "himoya qilish", "RightAnswer": "advocacy", "options": ["acrobat","synthesis","suspend"]},
{"Question": "kommunal", "RightAnswer": "communal", "options": ["advocacy","acrobat","synthesis"]},
{"Question": "suyuqlik", "RightAnswer": "fluid", "options": ["communal","advocacy","acrobat"]},
{"Question": "uyg'unlashtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "harmonize", "options": ["fluid","communal","advocacy"]},
{"Question": "mehnatkash", "RightAnswer": "industrious", "options": ["harmonize","fluid","communal"]},
{"Question": "ixtirochi", "RightAnswer": "inventive", "options": ["industrious","harmonize","fluid"]},
{"Question": "sud", "RightAnswer": "judicial", "options": ["inventive","industrious","harmonize"]},
{"Question": "Mandarin", "RightAnswer": "Mandarin", "options": ["judicial","inventive","industrious"]},
{"Question": "metropoliten", "RightAnswer": "metropolitan", "options": ["Mandarin","judicial","inventive"]},
{"Question": "taqlid qilish", "RightAnswer": "mimic", "options": ["metropolitan","Mandarin","judicial"]},
{"Question": "adashgan", "RightAnswer": "misguided", "options": ["mimic","metropolitan","Mandarin"]},
{"Question": "mashq qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "rehearse", "options": ["misguided","mimic","metropolitan"]},
{"Question": "nafrat", "RightAnswer": "scorn", "options": ["rehearse","misguided","mimic"]},
{"Question": "hissiy", "RightAnswer": "sensory", "options": ["scorn","rehearse","misguided"]},
{"Question": "shtapel", "RightAnswer": "staple", "options": ["sensory","scorn","rehearse"]},
{"Question": "nizom", "RightAnswer": "statute", "options": ["staple","sensory","scorn"]},
{"Question": "faxriy", "RightAnswer": "veteran", "options": ["statute","staple","sensory"]},
{"Question": "yovuz odam", "RightAnswer": "villain", "options": ["veteran","statute","staple"]},
{"Question": "tok", "RightAnswer": "vine", "options": ["villain","veteran","statute"]}],	
"level 176" : [
    {"Question": "cheklash", "RightAnswer": "constrain", "options": ["vine","villain","veteran"]},
{"Question": "depo", "RightAnswer": "depot", "options": ["constrain","vine","villain"]},
{"Question": "taqlid qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "emulate", "options": ["depot","constrain","vine"]},
{"Question": "ko'rsatkich barmog'i", "RightAnswer": "forefinger", "options": ["emulate","depot","constrain"]},
{"Question": "jasorat", "RightAnswer": "guts", "options": ["forefinger","emulate","depot"]},
{"Question": "xos", "RightAnswer": "inherent", "options": ["guts","forefinger","emulate"]},
{"Question": "qo'rqitmoq", "RightAnswer": "intimidate", "options": ["inherent","guts","forefinger"]},
{"Question": "farrosh", "RightAnswer": "janitor", "options": ["intimidate","inherent","guts"]},
{"Question": "nam", "RightAnswer": "moist", "options": ["janitor","intimidate","inherent"]},
{"Question": "yo'q", "RightAnswer": "nope", "options": ["moist","janitor","intimidate"]},
{"Question": "ishlab chiqarish", "RightAnswer": "prod", "options": ["nope","moist","janitor"]},
{"Question": "to'lov", "RightAnswer": "ransom", "options": ["prod","nope","moist"]},
{"Question": "cheklash", "RightAnswer": "restrain", "options": ["ransom","prod","nope"]},
{"Question": "tupurik", "RightAnswer": "saliva", "options": ["restrain","ransom","prod"]},
{"Question": "tupurmoq", "RightAnswer": "spit", "options": ["saliva","restrain","ransom"]},
{"Question": "sprint", "RightAnswer": "sprint", "options": ["spit","saliva","restrain"]},
{"Question": "kaskadyorlik", "RightAnswer": "stunt", "options": ["sprint","spit","saliva"]},
{"Question": "bardoshli", "RightAnswer": "tolerant", "options": ["stunt","sprint","spit"]},
{"Question": "vampir", "RightAnswer": "vampire", "options": ["tolerant","stunt","sprint"]},
{"Question": "esnamoq", "RightAnswer": "yawn", "options": ["vampire","tolerant","stunt"]}],	
"level 177" : [
    {"Question": "analogiya", "RightAnswer": "analogy", "options": ["yawn","vampire","tolerant"]},
{"Question": "nasl-nasabi", "RightAnswer": "ancestry", "options": ["analogy","yawn","vampire"]},
{"Question": "kamonchi", "RightAnswer": "archer", "options": ["ancestry","analogy","yawn"]},
{"Question": "fitna", "RightAnswer": "conspiracy", "options": ["archer","ancestry","analogy"]},
{"Question": "o'rinbosari", "RightAnswer": "deputy", "options": ["conspiracy","archer","ancestry"]},
{"Question": "graf", "RightAnswer": "earl", "options": ["deputy","conspiracy","archer"]},
{"Question": "xushbo'y", "RightAnswer": "fragrant", "options": ["earl","deputy","conspiracy"]},
{"Question": "voronka", "RightAnswer": "funnel", "options": ["fragrant","earl","deputy"]},
{"Question": "irsiy", "RightAnswer": "hereditary", "options": ["funnel","fragrant","earl"]},
{"Question": "madhiya", "RightAnswer": "hymn", "options": ["hereditary","funnel","fragrant"]},
{"Question": "invert", "RightAnswer": "invert", "options": ["hymn","hereditary","funnel"]},
{"Question": "o'lja", "RightAnswer": "prey", "options": ["invert","hymn","hereditary"]},
{"Question": "kortej", "RightAnswer": "procession", "options": ["prey","invert","hymn"]},
{"Question": "payg'ambar", "RightAnswer": "prophet", "options": ["procession","prey","invert"]},
{"Question": "kinoyali", "RightAnswer": "sarcastic", "options": ["prophet","procession","prey"]},
{"Question": "ziravorlar", "RightAnswer": "seasoning", "options": ["sarcastic","prophet","procession"]},
{"Question": "natriy", "RightAnswer": "sodium", "options": ["seasoning","sarcastic","prophet"]},
{"Question": "zulm", "RightAnswer": "tyranny", "options": ["sodium","seasoning","sarcastic"]},
{"Question": "zolim", "RightAnswer": "tyrant", "options": ["tyranny","sodium","seasoning"]},
{"Question": "sirka", "RightAnswer": "vinegar", "options": ["tyrant","tyranny","sodium"]}],	
"level 178" : [
    {"Question": "qo'shni", "RightAnswer": "adjoining", "options": ["vinegar","tyrant","tyranny"]},
{"Question": "da'vo qilmoq", "RightAnswer": "allege", "options": ["adjoining","vinegar","tyrant"]},
{"Question": "arch", "RightAnswer": "arch", "options": ["allege","adjoining","vinegar"]},
{"Question": "yig'moq", "RightAnswer": "assemble", "options": ["arch","allege","adjoining"]},
{"Question": "qurbon", "RightAnswer": "casualty", "options": ["assemble","arch","allege"]},
{"Question": "tik, qad ko'targan", "RightAnswer": "erect", "options": ["casualty","assemble","arch"]},
{"Question": "yomon", "RightAnswer": "foul", "options": ["erect","casualty","assemble"]},
{"Question": "gektar", "RightAnswer": "hectare", "options": ["foul","erect","casualty"]},
{"Question": "balandlamoq, kuchaymoq", "RightAnswer": "heighten", "options": ["hectare","foul","erect"]},
{"Question": "mehmondo'stlik", "RightAnswer": "hospitality", "options": ["heighten","hectare","foul"]},
{"Question": "qasr", "RightAnswer": "mansion", "options": ["hospitality","heighten","hectare"]},
{"Question": "oshib ketmoq", "RightAnswer": "outnumber", "options": ["mansion","hospitality","heighten"]},
{"Question": "juda xursand bo'lgan", "RightAnswer": "overjoyed", "options": ["outnumber","mansion","hospitality"]},
{"Question": "yaylov", "RightAnswer": "pasture", "options": ["overjoyed","outnumber","mansion"]},
{"Question": "ariza", "RightAnswer": "petition", "options": ["pasture","overjoyed","outnumber"]},
{"Question": "ta'mirlash", "RightAnswer": "renovate", "options": ["petition","pasture","overjoyed"]},
{"Question": "qayta ko'rib chiqmoq", "RightAnswer": "revise", "options": ["renovate","petition","pasture"]},
{"Question": "plita", "RightAnswer": "slab", "options": ["revise","renovate","petition"]},
{"Question": "teraska", "RightAnswer": "terrace", "options": ["slab","revise","renovate"]},
{"Question": "chim", "RightAnswer": "turf", "options": ["terrace","slab","revise"]}],	
"level 179" : [
    {"Question": "o'xshash", "RightAnswer": "analogous", "options": ["turf","terrace","slab"]},
{"Question": "durbin", "RightAnswer": "binoculars", "options": ["analogous","turf","terrace"]},
{"Question": "ommaviy", "RightAnswer": "bulk", "options": ["binoculars","analogous","turf"]},
{"Question": "o'z ichiga olmoq", "RightAnswer": "comprise", "options": ["bulk","binoculars","analogous"]},
{"Question": "tasvirlash", "RightAnswer": "depict", "options": ["comprise","bulk","binoculars"]},
{"Question": "ikkilik", "RightAnswer": "dual", "options": ["depict","comprise","bulk"]},
{"Question": "Farengeyt", "RightAnswer": "Fahrenheit", "options": ["dual","depict","comprise"]},
{"Question": "bajarish", "RightAnswer": "fulfill", "options": ["Fahrenheit","dual","depict"]},
{"Question": "to'qay", "RightAnswer": "grove", "options": ["fulfill","Fahrenheit","dual"]},
{"Question": "ruda", "RightAnswer": "ore", "options": ["grove","fulfill","Fahrenheit"]},
{"Question": "tashqarida", "RightAnswer": "outback", "options": ["ore","grove","fulfill"]},
{"Question": "og'irroq", "RightAnswer": "outweigh", "options": ["outback","ore","grove"]},
{"Question": "paradoks", "RightAnswer": "paradox", "options": ["outweigh","outback","ore"]},
{"Question": "qirg‘oqdan suvga qarab qurilgan yo'g'och yo'lak", "RightAnswer": "pier", "options": ["paradox","outweigh","outback"]},
{"Question": "yorliq", "RightAnswer": "shortcut", "options": ["pier","paradox","outweigh"]},
{"Question": "tarif", "RightAnswer": "tariff", "options": ["shortcut","pier","paradox"]},
{"Question": "termometr", "RightAnswer": "thermometer", "options": ["tariff","shortcut","pier"]},
{"Question": "egilish", "RightAnswer": "tilt", "options": ["thermometer","tariff","shortcut"]},
{"Question": "aksincha", "RightAnswer": "vice versa", "options": ["tilt","thermometer","tariff"]},
{"Question": "qayerdaligi", "RightAnswer": "whereabouts", "options": ["vice versa","tilt","thermometer"]}],	
"level 180" : [
    {"Question": "qahrabo", "RightAnswer": "amber", "options": ["whereabouts","vice versa","tilt"]},
{"Question": "ko'mir", "RightAnswer": "charcoal", "options": ["amber","whereabouts","vice versa"]},
{"Question": "sharhlovchi", "RightAnswer": "columnist", "options": ["charcoal","amber","whereabouts"]},
{"Question": "xushmuomala", "RightAnswer": "courteous", "options": ["columnist","charcoal","amber"]},
{"Question": "hisobga olish ma'lumotlari", "RightAnswer": "credentials", "options": ["courteous","columnist","charcoal"]},
{"Question": "kriket", "RightAnswer": "cricket", "options": ["credentials","courteous","columnist"]},
{"Question": "delta", "RightAnswer": "delta", "options": ["cricket","credentials","courteous"]},
{"Question": "yuvish vositasi", "RightAnswer": "detergent", "options": ["delta","cricket","credentials"]},
{"Question": "evfemizm", "RightAnswer": "euphemism", "options": ["detergent","delta","cricket"]},
{"Question": "muddati tugaydi", "RightAnswer": "expire", "options": ["euphemism","detergent","delta"]},
{"Question": "granit", "RightAnswer": "granite", "options": ["expire","euphemism","detergent"]},
{"Question": "shag'al", "RightAnswer": "gravel", "options": ["granite","expire","euphemism"]},
{"Question": "ta'qib qilish", "RightAnswer": "haunt", "options": ["gravel","granite","expire"]},
{"Question": "liberal", "RightAnswer": "liberal", "options": ["haunt","gravel","granite"]},
{"Question": "labirint", "RightAnswer": "maze", "options": ["liberal","haunt","gravel"]},
{"Question": "mox", "RightAnswer": "moss", "options": ["maze","liberal","haunt"]},
{"Question": "tosh", "RightAnswer": "pebble", "options": ["moss","maze","liberal"]},
{"Question": "cho'qimoq", "RightAnswer": "peck", "options": ["pebble","moss","maze"]},
{"Question": "suv ombori", "RightAnswer": "reservoir", "options": ["peck","pebble","moss"]},
{"Question": "chiziq", "RightAnswer": "streak", "options": ["reservoir","peck","pebble"]}]
}